1
00:01:43,407 --> 00:01:45,079
End of the century is coming, y'all.

2
00:01:45,247 --> 00:01:46,316
End of the millennium.

3
00:01:46,487 --> 00:01:47,806
A lot of lists being printed

4
00:01:47,967 --> 00:01:51,437
about who's the greatest person
of the past thousand years.

5
00:01:51,607 --> 00:01:53,916
By great they mean,
who had the most impact.

6
00:01:54,087 --> 00:01:56,123
Einstein, Edison, Freud.

7
00:01:56,287 --> 00:01:58,960
l can tell you one thing for sure:

8
00:01:59,127 --> 00:02:01,960
My name won't be on that list.

9
00:02:02,647 --> 00:02:04,842
And neither will anyone else's
here in Oz.

10
00:02:09,607 --> 00:02:10,960
Okay.

11
00:02:25,527 --> 00:02:27,119
Hey, Rebadow.

12
00:02:28,247 --> 00:02:32,126
You know, l think l got you.

13
00:02:32,287 --> 00:02:35,006
l think l got a piece of information
before you.

14
00:02:35,167 --> 00:02:36,680
Really?

15
00:02:37,967 --> 00:02:40,083
lt's about Glynn and his daughter.

16
00:02:40,247 --> 00:02:43,125
You mean that she was brutally raped
and is in the hospital?

17
00:02:43,287 --> 00:02:46,324
Shit. How'd you know that?

18
00:02:47,207 --> 00:02:50,882
Well, l know one thing
l know you don't know.

19
00:02:51,047 --> 00:02:54,244
- What's that?
- Who raped Glynn's daughter.

20
00:02:54,407 --> 00:02:57,797
- You're right, l don't.
- Yeah, l do.

21
00:02:58,967 --> 00:03:00,559
How do you know who did it?

22
00:03:00,727 --> 00:03:04,356
Oh, that's because
l was just talking to him on the phone.

23
00:03:13,247 --> 00:03:14,760
Come in.

24
00:03:19,447 --> 00:03:20,800
Richie.

25
00:03:21,447 --> 00:03:22,960
Father.

26
00:03:24,087 --> 00:03:25,520
What's up?

27
00:03:31,007 --> 00:03:33,362
l love to take it in the ass.

28
00:03:37,007 --> 00:03:39,646
Now, lots of people think
that's perverse.

29
00:03:40,007 --> 00:03:43,602
But it's my choice.
So l say fuck them, right?

30
00:03:45,047 --> 00:03:49,404
- Are we going someplace with all this?
- l choose to take it up the ass.

31
00:03:50,087 --> 00:03:51,759
But rape, man...

32
00:03:51,927 --> 00:03:55,442
- Did somebody rape you?
- Yeah, sure.

33
00:03:55,607 --> 00:03:57,643
But that's not why l'm here.

34
00:03:58,167 --> 00:04:00,635
l got some information
on another rape.

35
00:04:00,807 --> 00:04:02,604
Yes, l knew about his daughter.

36
00:04:02,767 --> 00:04:06,237
- And you didn't tell me?
- Well, he asked me not to.

37
00:04:07,607 --> 00:04:09,040
Hey.

38
00:04:09,447 --> 00:04:12,086
- You needed to see me?
- Yeah, Leo.

39
00:04:12,607 --> 00:04:14,518
lt's about Ardeth.

40
00:04:19,887 --> 00:04:21,400
You're gonna tell me
everything you know.

41
00:04:21,567 --> 00:04:24,286
- About what?
- My daughter.

42
00:04:24,447 --> 00:04:26,483
Your daughter was raped
and beaten.

43
00:04:26,647 --> 00:04:28,717
And because of that
you took it out on me.

44
00:04:28,887 --> 00:04:31,845
- Tell me who raped her.
- l ain't telling you dick.

45
00:04:32,007 --> 00:04:34,282
You got all the power, huh?

46
00:04:34,447 --> 00:04:37,007
l mean, you think
that you can just shit on people?

47
00:04:37,167 --> 00:04:39,362
Shit on people
and you get away with it?

48
00:04:39,807 --> 00:04:41,559
Not this time.

49
00:04:41,727 --> 00:04:43,046
And you can go fuck yourself.

50
00:04:43,207 --> 00:04:44,242
Miguel, for God's sake,

51
00:04:44,407 --> 00:04:46,363
tell him what you heard
about his daughter.

52
00:04:46,527 --> 00:04:50,406
What? That she's a lousy lay?

53
00:04:56,967 --> 00:04:59,640
Chain him up.

54
00:04:59,807 --> 00:05:02,480
Father, we're gonna need
some privacy.

55
00:05:02,647 --> 00:05:03,762
l'll be out here.

56
00:05:03,927 --> 00:05:05,406
Do it.

57
00:05:07,127 --> 00:05:08,845
Do it.

58
00:05:10,487 --> 00:05:11,920
- Leo.
- Get out.

59
00:05:12,087 --> 00:05:13,315
- Go ahead.
- Get him out of here!

60
00:05:13,487 --> 00:05:14,476
- Leo.
- Do it.

61
00:05:14,647 --> 00:05:16,603
- No!
- Do it.

62
00:05:30,967 --> 00:05:34,004
That motherfucker
deserves this shit.

63
00:05:40,767 --> 00:05:42,485
Listen, are you sure?

64
00:05:42,647 --> 00:05:46,322
This call was made in the past week
from Em City by Miguel Alvarez.

65
00:05:46,487 --> 00:05:50,639
Warden, you know as well as l do,
we monitor prisoners' calls randomly.

66
00:05:50,807 --> 00:05:53,275
We didn't catch that particular one.

67
00:05:55,127 --> 00:05:56,401
Fuck.

68
00:06:00,247 --> 00:06:01,441
Leo.

69
00:06:02,127 --> 00:06:06,120
Leo, l'm sorry
to hear about your daughter.

70
00:06:06,287 --> 00:06:09,165
- Does everybody know?
- Pretty much, yeah.

71
00:06:09,327 --> 00:06:11,124
Look, l can persuade Alvarez

72
00:06:11,287 --> 00:06:13,721
to give up the name of the prick
who did this.

73
00:06:13,887 --> 00:06:17,163
- No, thanks.
- Why not?

74
00:06:17,967 --> 00:06:21,926
Hey, why not? Why not?

75
00:06:22,647 --> 00:06:25,400
First, l don't wanna owe you
any more favours.

76
00:06:25,567 --> 00:06:30,004
Second, and l know you won't
understand this, but it's not right.

77
00:06:30,167 --> 00:06:33,364
Right, wrong, right, wrong.
There's such a fine line between it.

78
00:06:33,527 --> 00:06:35,279
Not for me.

79
00:06:39,447 --> 00:06:44,521
Bad men have their impact too.
But you gotta be really bad

80
00:06:44,687 --> 00:06:48,885
like lvan the Terrible,
Jack the Ripper, Adolf Hitler.

81
00:06:49,367 --> 00:06:51,801
Yeah, old Adolf was an evil fuck.

82
00:06:51,967 --> 00:06:53,195
And let's face it,

83
00:06:53,367 --> 00:06:56,598
evil is the only thing
that has survived intact

84
00:06:56,767 --> 00:07:00,043
these past thousand years.

85
00:08:18,327 --> 00:08:21,000
Prisoner number 98B2 42,

86
00:08:21,167 --> 00:08:26,116
Agamemnon Busmalis,
a.k.a. The Mole.

87
00:08:48,807 --> 00:08:50,798
Convicted March 1 0th, '98,

88
00:08:50,967 --> 00:08:53,435
grand theft larceny,
breaking and entering.

89
00:08:53,607 --> 00:08:55,916
Sentence: ten years.

90
00:08:56,087 --> 00:08:59,921
Up for parole in four.

91
00:09:03,927 --> 00:09:06,157
Busmalis, what are you doing?

92
00:09:06,327 --> 00:09:08,795
l told you, digging my way out.

93
00:09:08,967 --> 00:09:11,401
You can't. lt's impossible.

94
00:09:11,567 --> 00:09:12,761
Watch me.

95
00:09:12,927 --> 00:09:15,316
How long do you think
it's gonna take?

96
00:09:15,487 --> 00:09:16,715
l don't know.

97
00:09:16,887 --> 00:09:19,481
But l figure l got four years
till my first parole hearing.

98
00:09:19,647 --> 00:09:23,799
- You're gonna dig for four years?
- Only if l have to.

99
00:09:24,927 --> 00:09:26,326
The CO's coming.

100
00:09:34,247 --> 00:09:35,760
Thanks.

101
00:09:36,247 --> 00:09:37,566
Don't mention it.

102
00:09:40,967 --> 00:09:43,606
- Oh, fuck.
- What?

103
00:09:43,767 --> 00:09:45,997
- Beecher.
- What?

104
00:09:46,167 --> 00:09:48,237
- You farted.
- l didn't.

105
00:09:48,407 --> 00:09:51,683
- P-fucking-yew.
- l didn't fart.

106
00:09:51,847 --> 00:09:53,041
Damn, man.

107
00:09:53,487 --> 00:09:54,476
Five hours till dawn,

108
00:09:54,647 --> 00:09:58,162
and l gotta be in a goddamn glass box
with the king of stink.

109
00:09:58,327 --> 00:10:00,238
l'm gonna get
Gulf-fucking-War syndrome.

110
00:10:00,407 --> 00:10:01,840
You farted.

111
00:10:02,007 --> 00:10:03,440
- Oh, me?
- Yeah.

112
00:10:03,607 --> 00:10:05,199
You're saying l farted
to cover your tracks.

113
00:10:05,367 --> 00:10:08,803
No, you're saying l'm covering
my tracks to cover yours.

114
00:10:08,967 --> 00:10:10,685
Ginger broke the window
Broke the window, crack

115
00:10:10,847 --> 00:10:12,917
Baker came out to give him a clout
And landed on his back

116
00:10:13,087 --> 00:10:15,601
- Fuck you.
- Light a match.

117
00:10:16,167 --> 00:10:18,556
l swear, Beecher,
you need to go see a doctor, man.

118
00:10:18,727 --> 00:10:22,322
Smelly farts is a sign of something
seriously wrong on the inside.

119
00:10:22,487 --> 00:10:25,843
l didn't fart.

120
00:10:28,527 --> 00:10:30,643
Oh, fuck, man!

121
00:10:36,447 --> 00:10:38,961
- Hey.
- Hey.

122
00:10:39,887 --> 00:10:42,355
l'm about to start my shift.

123
00:10:42,967 --> 00:10:45,356
First day back in Em City.

124
00:10:46,367 --> 00:10:47,402
l was thinking,

125
00:10:47,567 --> 00:10:50,479
tonight l would let you
take me out to dinner to celebrate.

126
00:10:51,727 --> 00:10:53,718
Gee, l can't.

127
00:10:54,847 --> 00:10:56,724
Why? You got a date?

128
00:10:56,887 --> 00:10:59,082
Actually, yeah.

129
00:10:59,607 --> 00:11:01,325
Well, okay.

130
00:11:01,487 --> 00:11:04,126
- Have fun.
- Yeah, welcome back.

131
00:11:04,287 --> 00:11:05,720
Thanks.

132
00:11:08,447 --> 00:11:10,881
Life frustrated me the other day

133
00:11:11,047 --> 00:11:13,686
Pushed all my wrong buttons

134
00:11:13,847 --> 00:11:15,724
So l bit its ear off

135
00:11:15,887 --> 00:11:17,843
Pushed it up against the ropes
Told it, ''Stop

136
00:11:18,007 --> 00:11:20,885
Stop fucking head-butting me
When the ref ain't looking''

137
00:11:21,367 --> 00:11:23,323
l threw my--
Threw my hands around its neck

138
00:11:23,487 --> 00:11:26,479
Told it, ''Stop
Stop fucking yelling at me

139
00:11:26,647 --> 00:11:28,717
Before l start left-hooking''

140
00:11:28,887 --> 00:11:32,596
Threw my shank to its throat
Told it, ''Stop fucking playing me

141
00:11:32,767 --> 00:11:35,281
- Before l start choking''
- Oh, baby, l like this song.

142
00:11:35,447 --> 00:11:37,563
Because l got too many rope burns
Around my neck

143
00:11:37,727 --> 00:11:39,524
Too many cotton cuts
ln my fingernails

144
00:11:39,687 --> 00:11:43,475
l spent thousands of years
Thousands in jail

145
00:11:44,047 --> 00:11:46,163
Mostly for shit l didn't even do

146
00:11:46,887 --> 00:11:49,003
Mostly for shit
l didn't even know was wrong

147
00:11:49,567 --> 00:11:51,603
Mostly for shit

148
00:11:51,767 --> 00:11:53,883
You know what l'm saying?

149
00:12:19,567 --> 00:12:22,320
Take a look
at the Tiger Woods article in there.

150
00:12:24,567 --> 00:12:26,046
That dog is making
some serious dough.

151
00:12:26,207 --> 00:12:27,925
Oh, forget it. A fortune.

152
00:12:28,087 --> 00:12:29,839
See what it says there
about his parents?

153
00:12:30,007 --> 00:12:31,838
- No, where?
- Right there, second paragraph.

154
00:12:32,007 --> 00:12:33,725
Starts right there.

155
00:12:37,367 --> 00:12:40,439
''The biggest inf--''

156
00:12:40,607 --> 00:12:42,643
- ''lnfluence.''
- ''lnfluence

157
00:12:42,807 --> 00:12:49,485
in my life is my parents.''

158
00:12:49,647 --> 00:12:51,285
That's very good. Keep going.

159
00:12:51,447 --> 00:12:54,996
- ''Their pa--''
- ''Patience.''

160
00:12:55,167 --> 00:12:57,283
''Patience

161
00:12:58,487 --> 00:13:01,206
- has given me the--''
- ''Resources.''

162
00:13:01,367 --> 00:13:08,364
''Resources to be
a great champion.''

163
00:13:09,047 --> 00:13:10,958
- Excellent.
- That's my man.

164
00:13:11,127 --> 00:13:13,641
Little nigger can read.

165
00:13:14,407 --> 00:13:16,398
- You been practising, huh?
- Yeah, a little bit.

166
00:13:16,567 --> 00:13:19,639
That's great. Listen, keep the article,
you can read it after class, all right?

167
00:13:19,807 --> 00:13:21,126
Thanks, man. l appreciate it.

168
00:13:21,287 --> 00:13:22,766
Let's get started, huh?

169
00:13:38,327 --> 00:13:40,443
Coushaine tells me
that you did very well today,

170
00:13:40,607 --> 00:13:42,962
reading out loud in class.

171
00:13:43,607 --> 00:13:46,075
Well, he gave me
a sports magazine, so...

172
00:13:46,247 --> 00:13:50,525
Well, l figure
that you deserve something,

173
00:13:50,687 --> 00:13:53,838
since you've been putting in
so much hard work.

174
00:13:55,687 --> 00:13:56,756
''Up From Sl--''

175
00:13:56,927 --> 00:13:58,645
- ''Slavery. ''
- ''Slavery. ''

176
00:13:58,807 --> 00:14:00,923
Booker T. Washington.
You know who that is?

177
00:14:01,087 --> 00:14:02,645
Yeah. Booker T. and the MGs.

178
00:14:02,807 --> 00:14:04,604
No, it's a different guy.

179
00:14:04,767 --> 00:14:08,237
He was one of the most influential
African-Americans of his time.

180
00:14:08,407 --> 00:14:12,559
He believed that education was the key
to success for any man's life.

181
00:14:12,727 --> 00:14:13,842
This the dude with the peanuts?

182
00:14:14,007 --> 00:14:15,486
No, that's
George Washington Carver.

183
00:14:15,647 --> 00:14:19,276
This book influenced my life.

184
00:14:21,767 --> 00:14:22,995
Hey, McManus.

185
00:14:23,527 --> 00:14:25,358
You know that deal we made
about me going to school

186
00:14:25,527 --> 00:14:28,599
instead of working the kitchen?

187
00:14:29,687 --> 00:14:32,884
l don't miss that mop at all, man.

188
00:14:42,927 --> 00:14:47,443
- Got something in there for me?
- You going to class, Adebisi?

189
00:14:48,527 --> 00:14:51,837
Got a full schedule. Real busy.

190
00:14:52,007 --> 00:14:55,079
Well, you know what?
You should really come by my office.

191
00:14:55,247 --> 00:14:59,798
We'll check your records.
You really should be back in school.

192
00:15:02,127 --> 00:15:04,721
Yeah, l'll be there real soon.

193
00:15:04,887 --> 00:15:06,605
You bet.

194
00:15:11,527 --> 00:15:12,880
What's up?

195
00:15:17,607 --> 00:15:20,075
You suck his cock
when l'm not here?

196
00:15:20,247 --> 00:15:23,045
Get the fuck out of here. He just
brought me some shit to read, man.

197
00:15:23,367 --> 00:15:24,880
Read, eh?

198
00:15:25,167 --> 00:15:26,156
What's this?

199
00:15:28,047 --> 00:15:30,880
Maybe you can read me
a nice bedtime story, huh?

200
00:15:33,367 --> 00:15:35,198
That cocksucker
doesn't come in here again

201
00:15:35,367 --> 00:15:37,005
unless you ask me.

202
00:15:37,167 --> 00:15:39,397
How the fuck am l supposed
to stop him from coming in?

203
00:15:39,927 --> 00:15:43,715
You're not listening.
Come here. Come here.

204
00:15:46,527 --> 00:15:49,246
He doesn't come in here.

205
00:15:50,367 --> 00:15:53,916
Do you understand?

206
00:15:54,087 --> 00:15:56,476
Yeah, man. Yeah.

207
00:15:57,327 --> 00:15:58,806
See.

208
00:16:01,527 --> 00:16:03,836
You're a really smart kid, huh?

209
00:16:13,527 --> 00:16:17,156
Booker T. Washington.
Now, he belongs on that list.

210
00:16:17,327 --> 00:16:20,160
Born a slave,
he rose up and shook the tree.

211
00:16:20,327 --> 00:16:23,558
Everyone knew who he was.
Everyone all around the world.

212
00:16:23,727 --> 00:16:27,925
Even the president of the United
States asked for his advice.

213
00:16:28,967 --> 00:16:30,639
Now, how the fuck
did Booker T. do that?

214
00:16:32,407 --> 00:16:34,875
There's some bullshit going on.

215
00:16:35,927 --> 00:16:37,645
Yo, Si, that's fucked up

216
00:16:37,807 --> 00:16:40,480
that Glynn handed the kitchen over
to Schibetta and shit.

217
00:16:40,647 --> 00:16:44,196
- The brother tell you why?
- He don't have to tell me why. l know.

218
00:16:44,367 --> 00:16:45,356
Say word, you do?

219
00:16:47,327 --> 00:16:50,603
He's trying to start a war with us
and those guineas.

220
00:16:50,767 --> 00:16:53,839
- Glynn?
- Yeah.

221
00:16:54,007 --> 00:16:57,761
- Why would he wanna start a war?
- Because he hates them too.

222
00:16:57,927 --> 00:17:01,840
Holy shit. lt's the little Nino.

223
00:17:02,007 --> 00:17:05,636
You know,
you look just like your father.

224
00:17:05,807 --> 00:17:10,517
- Only you're still breathing.
- You trying to tell me something?

225
00:17:12,287 --> 00:17:14,039
Yes.

226
00:17:14,207 --> 00:17:16,243
l miss your father.

227
00:17:18,087 --> 00:17:19,839
Why don't you lazy fucks
get back to work?

228
00:17:20,007 --> 00:17:20,996
Come on, come on.

229
00:17:22,047 --> 00:17:25,517
Next. Come on, darling.

230
00:17:36,567 --> 00:17:39,843
Hey, a little afternoon tittie fuck.

231
00:17:41,727 --> 00:17:43,479
Hey, what's your problem?

232
00:17:43,647 --> 00:17:47,435
- l got no problem, man.
- Shakedown! Shakedown!

233
00:17:47,607 --> 00:17:49,006
What the fuck are you doing?

234
00:17:49,167 --> 00:17:51,601
- Shakedown, shakedown!
- Hey, hey, what's the problem?

235
00:17:51,767 --> 00:17:53,200
- Officer Wittlesey.
- Let's go, out.

236
00:17:53,367 --> 00:17:54,880
Hands on the rail.

237
00:17:55,047 --> 00:17:57,436
You know the routine.
Hands on the rail.

238
00:18:10,847 --> 00:18:12,246
- They're clean.
- So's the cell.

239
00:18:12,407 --> 00:18:13,999
Clean.

240
00:18:20,607 --> 00:18:22,165
Give it to me.

241
00:18:26,327 --> 00:18:28,045
l tell you what.

242
00:18:28,727 --> 00:18:30,957
Now it's my book.

243
00:18:31,127 --> 00:18:36,759
- My book is for my tits.
- What the fuck are you doing?

244
00:18:36,927 --> 00:18:40,237
You're an ugly bastard,
but l love him.

245
00:18:40,727 --> 00:18:44,083
- ''Booker T., Up From Slavery. ''
- Fuck you, man!

246
00:18:45,767 --> 00:18:46,756
Shit.

247
00:18:46,927 --> 00:18:49,236
Forgetting who you are,
little brother.

248
00:18:49,407 --> 00:18:51,557
McManus, this book shit,
going to class?

249
00:18:51,727 --> 00:18:54,639
You think
you can disrespect me, huh?

250
00:18:56,167 --> 00:18:58,965
Don't forget
who your friends are, Kenny.

251
00:18:59,127 --> 00:19:02,961
Because if you're not my friend,
then you're my enemy.

252
00:19:03,127 --> 00:19:05,038
- Understand?
- Yeah.

253
00:19:05,207 --> 00:19:07,596
- Understand?
- Yeah, l said l fucking understand.

254
00:19:07,767 --> 00:19:08,756
Good.

255
00:19:09,647 --> 00:19:11,797
Now l need to get high.

256
00:19:13,127 --> 00:19:14,958
l hear that.

257
00:19:43,967 --> 00:19:45,923
Why aren't you in class?

258
00:19:48,007 --> 00:19:49,963
What the fuck is your problem,
McManus?

259
00:19:50,127 --> 00:19:52,846
- All right.
- No. Come on, come on.

260
00:19:53,007 --> 00:19:55,396
Oh, shit.

261
00:20:01,327 --> 00:20:02,965
Shit.

262
00:20:05,207 --> 00:20:07,038
Now, why did you stop
going to class?

263
00:20:08,647 --> 00:20:11,957
You were doing so well.
What happened?

264
00:20:13,047 --> 00:20:14,366
Nothing.

265
00:20:14,527 --> 00:20:17,599
- Somebody pressuring you?
- Yeah.

266
00:20:17,767 --> 00:20:18,756
You.

267
00:20:18,927 --> 00:20:21,646
You tell me what's going on, Kenny!

268
00:20:26,407 --> 00:20:28,318
ls Adebisi giving you shit
about going to school?

269
00:20:35,247 --> 00:20:38,478
You get the fuck out of here.
l'm having a conversation.

270
00:20:40,567 --> 00:20:42,285
Taxi.

271
00:20:45,687 --> 00:20:47,598
l'm gonna transfer this fucker
to gen pop. How's that?

272
00:20:47,767 --> 00:20:48,836
No, don't do that.

273
00:20:49,007 --> 00:20:52,079
Because then he'll think l asked you to,
and then that'll be my ass.

274
00:20:52,247 --> 00:20:54,078
Then l'm gonna move you
to another pod.

275
00:20:54,247 --> 00:20:55,566
No, just don't.

276
00:20:55,727 --> 00:20:57,604
Look, you're gonna go back
to school, Kenny.

277
00:20:57,767 --> 00:20:58,756
You're going back to school

278
00:20:58,927 --> 00:21:01,725
or l'll have you mopping that kitchen
24 hours a day.

279
00:21:01,887 --> 00:21:04,117
l'm gonna have you mopping
this whole fucking prison.

280
00:21:04,287 --> 00:21:06,005
Do you hear me?

281
00:21:09,087 --> 00:21:10,998
What's it gonna be, Kenny?

282
00:21:15,567 --> 00:21:17,285
What's it gonna be?

283
00:21:20,487 --> 00:21:22,796
- l'll go back to class.
- Okay.

284
00:21:23,527 --> 00:21:25,324
Let's go. You're late.

285
00:21:29,287 --> 00:21:31,721
Mr. Booker T. Washington
writes in his book:

286
00:21:31,887 --> 00:21:34,799
''l have great faith
in the power and influence of fact.

287
00:21:34,967 --> 00:21:37,242
lt is seldom that anything
is permanently gained

288
00:21:37,407 --> 00:21:39,921
by holding back fact. ''

289
00:21:40,087 --> 00:21:41,202
You want some facts?

290
00:21:41,367 --> 00:21:42,959
The U.S. Department of Justice
reports

291
00:21:43,127 --> 00:21:44,879
that the typical prisoner in America

292
00:21:45,047 --> 00:21:47,686
is an undereducated,
young male minority,

293
00:21:47,847 --> 00:21:49,485
but you could've guessed that.

294
00:21:52,087 --> 00:21:54,282
lf that undereducated,
young male minority

295
00:21:54,447 --> 00:21:57,996
receives his GED in prison,
he is far less likely to come back.

296
00:21:58,167 --> 00:22:02,160
Anybody wanna read out loud?
W.E.B. Du Bois.

297
00:22:02,327 --> 00:22:04,283
Let's have Kenny...
Why don't you give it a shot?

298
00:22:04,447 --> 00:22:07,678
lf that same kid manages to go
to college while he's inside,

299
00:22:07,847 --> 00:22:10,315
he'll almost definitely
never see a prison cell again.

300
00:22:10,487 --> 00:22:12,239
Just pick any page you want.

301
00:22:13,367 --> 00:22:15,278
Last year, one state, California,

302
00:22:15,447 --> 00:22:19,235
spent more money on its penal system
than it did on higher education.

303
00:22:19,407 --> 00:22:20,726
These are the facts and figures.

304
00:22:20,887 --> 00:22:24,243
You ain't got to be that smart
to add them up.

305
00:22:30,487 --> 00:22:34,366
- l'd fuck Dr. Nathan in a second.
- Me too.

306
00:22:34,527 --> 00:22:36,085
- How about Wittlesey?
- Shit, yeah.

307
00:22:37,047 --> 00:22:38,719
Me too.

308
00:22:39,127 --> 00:22:43,006
You know who l think is sexy?
Sister Peter Marie.

309
00:22:43,647 --> 00:22:45,080
Yeah.

310
00:22:45,247 --> 00:22:46,726
That's disgusting. She's a nun.

311
00:22:46,887 --> 00:22:47,956
Wasn't always a nun.

312
00:22:48,367 --> 00:22:49,595
She was married.

313
00:22:50,047 --> 00:22:51,719
What? Nuns can't be married.

314
00:22:51,887 --> 00:22:54,003
They're brides of Christ.

315
00:22:54,167 --> 00:22:56,078
Before she became a nun.

316
00:22:56,247 --> 00:22:58,681
Her husband died.
She told me once in passing.

317
00:22:58,847 --> 00:23:01,042
l wonder how he died, her husband.

318
00:23:01,527 --> 00:23:02,755
She didn't say.

319
00:23:03,607 --> 00:23:05,040
An accident, l heard.

320
00:23:05,207 --> 00:23:07,004
He fell off the back of a truck,
broke his neck.

321
00:23:07,167 --> 00:23:09,044
That's true, but it wasn't an accident.

322
00:23:09,207 --> 00:23:10,356
Why do you think she works here?

323
00:23:10,527 --> 00:23:13,963
Her husband was pushed off the truck.
He was murdered.

324
00:23:19,207 --> 00:23:21,198
Peter, Peter Marie.

325
00:23:23,607 --> 00:23:25,484
Peter.

326
00:23:26,447 --> 00:23:27,596
Peter Marie.

327
00:23:27,767 --> 00:23:29,519
- Hey, Leo.
- Peter.

328
00:23:29,687 --> 00:23:32,042
- You know William Giles?
- No.

329
00:23:32,207 --> 00:23:33,640
Peter Marie, Peter Marie. Peter...

330
00:23:33,807 --> 00:23:36,037
l think his mind has snapped
and we think he's asking for you.

331
00:23:36,207 --> 00:23:39,722
Peter Marie, Peter Marie.

332
00:23:39,887 --> 00:23:43,277
Peter Marie, Peter Marie,
Peter Marie.

333
00:23:46,887 --> 00:23:50,357
Hello, William.
You wanna talk with me?

334
00:23:51,887 --> 00:23:53,445
Sick.

335
00:23:53,847 --> 00:23:55,644
You're sick?

336
00:24:04,887 --> 00:24:06,320
Love.

337
00:24:10,967 --> 00:24:12,400
Broom.

338
00:24:12,567 --> 00:24:14,922
You want a broom?

339
00:24:15,967 --> 00:24:17,639
No.

340
00:24:23,847 --> 00:24:25,724
Okay, William.

341
00:24:27,007 --> 00:24:28,759
William?

342
00:24:33,247 --> 00:24:34,965
You wanna talk to me?

343
00:24:35,127 --> 00:24:36,845
Peter Marie, Peter Marie!

344
00:24:37,487 --> 00:24:39,921
- Peter Marie!
- Stop. lt's all right.

345
00:24:40,087 --> 00:24:42,123
- Peter! Peter Marie! Peter!
- Calm down.

346
00:24:42,287 --> 00:24:45,802
Tobias, would you bring up the file
on William Giles for me, please?

347
00:24:45,967 --> 00:24:48,083
G-l-L-E-S.

348
00:24:48,247 --> 00:24:49,521
Sure.

349
00:24:52,207 --> 00:24:54,516
We voted you sexiest.

350
00:24:55,047 --> 00:24:57,925
Sexiest? Sexiest what?

351
00:24:58,487 --> 00:25:01,797
- Woman in prison.
- Oh, come on.

352
00:25:03,567 --> 00:25:05,080
Really?

353
00:25:07,087 --> 00:25:08,725
There it is.

354
00:25:25,967 --> 00:25:29,516
Prisoner number 58G 7 1 4,
William Giles.

355
00:25:30,847 --> 00:25:34,840
Convicted February 6, 1 958,
second-degree murder.

356
00:25:35,367 --> 00:25:39,804
Sentenced to life.
Up for parole in 60 years.

357
00:25:39,967 --> 00:25:44,165
Leo, l really need you
to get Giles out of solitary

358
00:25:44,327 --> 00:25:45,760
so that we can start
therapy sessions.

359
00:25:45,927 --> 00:25:48,725
- You know why he's in solitary?
- Yeah, l read the report.

360
00:25:48,887 --> 00:25:51,606
Two years ago, he stole
some toothpaste from another inmate.

361
00:25:51,767 --> 00:25:54,042
The inmate caught him
and Giles killed the guy.

362
00:25:54,207 --> 00:25:56,846
- He's dangerous and he's crazy.
- Yeah, but he needs my help.

363
00:25:57,007 --> 00:25:58,679
l'm not putting you
in that kind of situation.

364
00:25:58,847 --> 00:26:00,724
- Leo, Leo--
- No. No.

365
00:26:00,887 --> 00:26:03,037
l'm going to the hospital
to visit my daughter. Good night.

366
00:26:03,207 --> 00:26:04,560
Le--

367
00:26:18,687 --> 00:26:20,279
Peter.

368
00:26:22,327 --> 00:26:24,124
Peter Marie.

369
00:26:27,207 --> 00:26:29,323
Peter Marie.

370
00:26:37,207 --> 00:26:39,516
Peter, Peter Marie.

371
00:26:39,687 --> 00:26:41,040
Peter.

372
00:26:41,527 --> 00:26:43,643
Peter, Peter Marie!

373
00:26:44,927 --> 00:26:46,519
Peter.

374
00:26:48,247 --> 00:26:52,684
Do you think that when the first
millennium ended back in 999,

375
00:26:52,847 --> 00:26:54,758
that they made lists?

376
00:26:54,927 --> 00:26:58,602
Did they even know
the millennium was ending?

377
00:27:02,607 --> 00:27:04,359
Said.

378
00:27:07,487 --> 00:27:09,045
You are disturbing
our morning prayer.

379
00:27:09,207 --> 00:27:11,767
Yeah, well, you got mail. Sign here.

380
00:27:12,287 --> 00:27:15,279
- l will sign for it later.
- Look, l haven't got time for this.

381
00:27:15,447 --> 00:27:17,802
Schillinger's in the hole
so we're short-staffed in the mailroom.

382
00:27:17,967 --> 00:27:19,923
l gotta get back.

383
00:27:20,807 --> 00:27:24,163
Now this, l will gladly sign for.

384
00:27:24,327 --> 00:27:28,081
Yeah? Well, l'm fucking thrilled.

385
00:27:38,087 --> 00:27:41,363
- My brothers.
- Your book about the riot.

386
00:27:41,527 --> 00:27:47,318
This is proof that the truth
cannot be silenced.

387
00:27:57,407 --> 00:28:01,685
The Annotated Code?
You giving up God for the law?

388
00:28:02,167 --> 00:28:04,442
God's laws are clear to me.

389
00:28:04,607 --> 00:28:06,837
lt's those of man that are not.

390
00:28:07,887 --> 00:28:10,242
l've been studying legal books
for the last eight months.

391
00:28:10,967 --> 00:28:13,037
Trying to see if God's laws
and those of the white man

392
00:28:13,207 --> 00:28:15,163
have anything in common.

393
00:28:17,527 --> 00:28:19,677
What have you discovered?

394
00:28:20,087 --> 00:28:23,079
That these are nothing but words
on a page.

395
00:28:23,607 --> 00:28:26,440
The annotated code exists
solely to be circumvented.

396
00:28:26,967 --> 00:28:29,481
Without law, we have anarchy.

397
00:28:30,447 --> 00:28:32,915
You should read
your morning paper, old man.

398
00:28:33,087 --> 00:28:35,123
We have anarchy anyway.

399
00:28:35,767 --> 00:28:38,884
l would have thought after the riot,
you would have learned.

400
00:28:39,527 --> 00:28:41,438
You can't overthrow the system.

401
00:28:41,607 --> 00:28:43,279
Oh, l learned.

402
00:28:43,447 --> 00:28:46,359
And l have no interest
in seeing more men die.

403
00:28:46,527 --> 00:28:48,040
No.

404
00:28:49,207 --> 00:28:52,483
l intend to use the tools
that were used against me.

405
00:28:52,887 --> 00:28:57,836
l intend to make the law
devour itself.

406
00:28:58,527 --> 00:29:02,440
Judge Richard Kibler was sentenced
today to 1 6 months in prison.

407
00:29:02,607 --> 00:29:04,086
The veteran
of the state criminal court

408
00:29:04,247 --> 00:29:06,886
was convicted of taking bribes
in exchange for leniency

409
00:29:07,047 --> 00:29:08,400
in three murder cases...

410
00:29:08,567 --> 00:29:10,319
You hear this?

411
00:29:10,487 --> 00:29:13,365
Cocksucker Kibler was the judge
at my fucking trial.

412
00:29:13,527 --> 00:29:16,200
- For real?
- Shit, yeah.

413
00:29:16,367 --> 00:29:19,882
lf l'd have known he was up for bribes,
l'd have put my two dollars down.

414
00:29:20,047 --> 00:29:23,801
- That shit ain't fair.
- You're right, it's not.

415
00:29:23,967 --> 00:29:26,162
- You know what you ought to do, Hill?
- What?

416
00:29:26,327 --> 00:29:28,079
Talk to Said.

417
00:29:29,487 --> 00:29:34,038
Now, it says here in this article
that Kibler took bribes in November.

418
00:29:34,207 --> 00:29:38,200
And you weren't approached by him
or anyone else about taking bribes?

419
00:29:38,367 --> 00:29:42,758
- Nobody said dick to me.
- Did he talk to your lawyer?

420
00:29:44,567 --> 00:29:47,639
lf they did,
he never said word one to me.

421
00:29:47,807 --> 00:29:50,196
Good. That's good.

422
00:29:50,727 --> 00:29:54,766
- l think we have a case.
- A case?

423
00:29:55,087 --> 00:29:56,076
Yeah.

424
00:29:56,247 --> 00:30:00,126
You were denied your right
to a fair trial by an impartial judge.

425
00:30:00,567 --> 00:30:04,196
So... So you're saying
that we could go to court

426
00:30:04,367 --> 00:30:05,766
and have the verdict overturned?

427
00:30:07,647 --> 00:30:09,319
My friend,

428
00:30:10,247 --> 00:30:14,718
you have a real shot at going free.

429
00:30:20,287 --> 00:30:21,356
Now, let me get this straight.

430
00:30:21,527 --> 00:30:24,405
Judge Kibler did not take a bribe
in Hill's case.

431
00:30:24,567 --> 00:30:25,716
That is correct.

432
00:30:25,887 --> 00:30:28,526
- And he didn't ask for a bribe either.
- That is also correct.

433
00:30:28,687 --> 00:30:30,359
Then what exactly
are we talking about?

434
00:30:30,527 --> 00:30:33,644
The judge was lenient
with those who did give bribes.

435
00:30:33,807 --> 00:30:35,559
So he may have been harsh
with those who did not.

436
00:30:36,367 --> 00:30:37,846
Look, all we ask
is for the opportunity

437
00:30:38,007 --> 00:30:39,645
to explore the merits of the case.

438
00:30:39,807 --> 00:30:42,162
What opportunities
are we talking about?

439
00:30:42,327 --> 00:30:43,521
Yeah, and for how long?

440
00:30:43,687 --> 00:30:47,362
Look, we're gonna need
more time for visitations.

441
00:30:47,527 --> 00:30:50,405
l'm gonna need to talk to the lawyer
who originally represented Augustus.

442
00:30:50,567 --> 00:30:53,479
And anybody that offered bribes,
their lawyers.

443
00:30:53,647 --> 00:30:56,605
The prosecution at Judge Kibler's trial,
et cetera.

444
00:30:57,567 --> 00:31:00,081
You've stayed pretty quiet
through all this.

445
00:31:00,527 --> 00:31:01,562
Kareem said he'd be talking.

446
00:31:01,727 --> 00:31:05,197
l'd be a idiot not to keep
my fucking mouth shut.

447
00:31:08,567 --> 00:31:09,920
- You lying.
- l...

448
00:31:10,087 --> 00:31:12,476
Clifford, l sat next to you
through all those hearings,

449
00:31:12,647 --> 00:31:13,921
all those days of the trial.

450
00:31:14,087 --> 00:31:17,318
l got so l could tell when you was lying.
You get that little twitch.

451
00:31:17,487 --> 00:31:18,636
l do?

452
00:31:18,807 --> 00:31:20,445
That's probably why
you such a shit lawyer.

453
00:31:20,607 --> 00:31:23,758
Augustus, please.
lnsults do us no good at all.

454
00:31:23,927 --> 00:31:25,280
They sure as hell
make me feel better.

455
00:31:25,447 --> 00:31:26,960
Look, l did the best l could for you.

456
00:31:27,127 --> 00:31:29,322
Yeah, l know.
That's why l'm saying you shit.

457
00:31:29,487 --> 00:31:32,524
Can we get back
to the point, please?

458
00:31:34,367 --> 00:31:38,519
Now, you knew others
were giving bribes.

459
00:31:39,367 --> 00:31:41,927
l heard stuff
in the courthouse hallways. That's all.

460
00:31:42,087 --> 00:31:43,884
Then why didn't you jump,
you motherfucker?

461
00:31:44,047 --> 00:31:45,844
Call me naive,
l thought l'd get a ''not guilty''

462
00:31:46,007 --> 00:31:47,406
based on the strength of the case.

463
00:31:47,567 --> 00:31:49,080
Mr. Sprague,
if you knew what was going on,

464
00:31:49,247 --> 00:31:51,238
why did you not go
to the state judicial commission?

465
00:31:51,407 --> 00:31:54,365
Come on. l go to the state
commission and nothing happens.

466
00:31:54,527 --> 00:31:56,404
Except, the next time
l'm in front of Kibler,

467
00:31:56,567 --> 00:31:58,797
he cuts off my balls.

468
00:32:01,367 --> 00:32:02,720
Well?

469
00:32:03,567 --> 00:32:05,205
Marilyn Crenshaw.

470
00:32:05,367 --> 00:32:08,245
The assistant district attorney
who prosecuted Kibler.

471
00:32:08,407 --> 00:32:11,365
- She will meet with us tomorrow.
- Cool.

472
00:32:11,527 --> 00:32:15,202
Unfortunately, though, the lawyers
who gave bribes won't take my calls.

473
00:32:15,367 --> 00:32:17,244
The secretaries say,
''l'll get back to you.''

474
00:32:17,407 --> 00:32:19,125
l say, ''You can't get back to me.''

475
00:32:19,287 --> 00:32:20,481
Hey, you know what you should do?

476
00:32:20,647 --> 00:32:23,480
You should check if any of those three
murderers are doing their time in Oz.

477
00:32:23,647 --> 00:32:25,080
l did. They're not.

478
00:32:25,247 --> 00:32:27,886
- They're in different prisons.
- So, what do we do?

479
00:32:28,047 --> 00:32:30,959
Well, l'm gonna write to each one,
but l don't expect any response.

480
00:32:31,127 --> 00:32:33,925
- So we're fucked.
- No, no, no.

481
00:32:34,087 --> 00:32:37,284
Good things don't come easy,
my brother.

482
00:32:37,687 --> 00:32:38,961
Got it.

483
00:32:39,287 --> 00:32:41,357
Count!

484
00:32:42,047 --> 00:32:43,765
Until tomorrow.

485
00:32:44,407 --> 00:32:46,477
Asalaam alaikum, brother.

486
00:32:47,367 --> 00:32:49,927
Straight line,
you know how we do this. Move it.

487
00:32:59,447 --> 00:33:02,883
When you were gathering evidence
to prosecute Judge Kibler,

488
00:33:03,287 --> 00:33:05,642
did you ever hear
Augustus Hill's name mentioned?

489
00:33:05,807 --> 00:33:07,286
No.

490
00:33:07,487 --> 00:33:10,001
ln reference to the murder convictions
that Kibler was lenient with,

491
00:33:10,167 --> 00:33:11,919
did you perceive any sort of pattern?

492
00:33:13,327 --> 00:33:14,760
No.

493
00:33:14,927 --> 00:33:16,645
So nothing about these three men
was consistent?

494
00:33:16,807 --> 00:33:21,358
They share the same style of murder,
same lawyer, same skin tone?

495
00:33:22,327 --> 00:33:24,522
You're not gonna be able
to turn this into something racial.

496
00:33:24,687 --> 00:33:25,722
That is not my intention.

497
00:33:25,887 --> 00:33:27,286
Bullshit.

498
00:33:27,447 --> 00:33:29,563
The only two elements that are similar
in these murders

499
00:33:29,727 --> 00:33:31,126
is they were men
and they were guilty.

500
00:33:31,287 --> 00:33:32,879
Oh, so you're saying
the bribes were random?

501
00:33:33,047 --> 00:33:34,480
- Yes.
- Would you testify to that?

502
00:33:34,647 --> 00:33:36,205
l never said that l would
testify in court.

503
00:33:36,367 --> 00:33:38,085
lf you try to compel me,
l'll take you to court.

504
00:33:38,247 --> 00:33:40,203
Now, why would you do that?

505
00:33:40,367 --> 00:33:43,962
You're an assistant district attorney,
sworn to seeing justice done.

506
00:33:44,127 --> 00:33:46,960
Or doesn't your definition of justice
extend to my client?

507
00:33:47,127 --> 00:33:49,243
Your client? Please.

508
00:33:49,407 --> 00:33:52,319
The only place that you are a lawyer
is in your own head.

509
00:33:52,487 --> 00:33:53,681
l see what you're doing.

510
00:33:53,847 --> 00:33:56,281
Strutting around,
thumbing your nose at the system.

511
00:33:56,447 --> 00:33:59,405
Thumbing your nose
at everything that l believe in.

512
00:34:00,647 --> 00:34:03,366
lt's not him that l won't help. lt's you.

513
00:34:04,607 --> 00:34:05,756
Look, you could win this case,

514
00:34:05,927 --> 00:34:07,485
but let me give you
some free legal advice.

515
00:34:07,647 --> 00:34:10,684
Get yourself a lawyer.
A real fucking lawyer.

516
00:34:18,567 --> 00:34:21,525
- You know that woman?
- Why do you ask?

517
00:34:21,687 --> 00:34:24,485
You two seem awful familiar.

518
00:34:24,647 --> 00:34:26,603
That's not the bitch
that prosecuted you, is she?

519
00:34:27,887 --> 00:34:33,086
Marilyn and l, before l found Allah,

520
00:34:36,407 --> 00:34:38,762
we were engaged to be married.

521
00:34:41,487 --> 00:34:43,079
l need more access to the phones.

522
00:34:43,247 --> 00:34:45,522
l need to be able to get calls
as well as make them.

523
00:34:45,687 --> 00:34:49,646
Well, why don't we just run
a switchboard into your pod?

524
00:34:51,087 --> 00:34:53,078
Answer a legitimate request
with sarcasm.

525
00:34:53,247 --> 00:34:54,441
- Legitimate request?
- Yes.

526
00:34:54,607 --> 00:34:57,565
Said, you're an inmate
in a maximum-security prison.

527
00:34:57,727 --> 00:34:58,876
Now, if l say yes to you,

528
00:34:59,047 --> 00:35:00,958
what's to stop the next guy
asking for the same thing?

529
00:35:01,127 --> 00:35:03,687
- These are special circumstances.
- No, they're not.

530
00:35:03,847 --> 00:35:07,681
l hate to break the news to you, pal,
but in here, you're nobody special.

531
00:35:07,847 --> 00:35:10,486
You deserve no more
than the next man.

532
00:35:12,687 --> 00:35:13,836
What is this about?

533
00:35:14,007 --> 00:35:16,316
ls this because you don't like
what l said about you in my book?

534
00:35:16,487 --> 00:35:20,275
No, this is about the fact
that you always ask for help

535
00:35:20,447 --> 00:35:22,642
and you're never willing
to do anything for me in return.

536
00:35:22,807 --> 00:35:26,083
Why does there have to be
a trade, a negotiation?

537
00:35:26,247 --> 00:35:28,841
l would have thought that doing
what's right would be enough for you.

538
00:35:42,167 --> 00:35:44,044
No go, huh?

539
00:35:47,767 --> 00:35:49,280
Damn.

540
00:35:51,247 --> 00:35:55,240
Yo, what was that you were saying
about nothing good coming easy?

541
00:35:56,207 --> 00:35:59,802
Life in prison is some tough shit
to wrap your mind around.

542
00:36:00,647 --> 00:36:03,320
Know what l'm saying? But l did
like everybody else in this cumhole.

543
00:36:03,487 --> 00:36:06,957
l settled in, l settled down.

544
00:36:07,127 --> 00:36:08,116
But then--

545
00:36:08,287 --> 00:36:12,360
But then, when you said the word
''free'' to me,

546
00:36:15,407 --> 00:36:18,444
yo, something inside me stirred,
you know?

547
00:36:19,887 --> 00:36:21,479
Freedom.

548
00:36:22,127 --> 00:36:24,402
l want my freedom.

549
00:36:25,687 --> 00:36:28,076
Then you shall have it, my brother.

550
00:36:28,687 --> 00:36:33,317
l swear to you, by almighty God
and everything that l hold holy,

551
00:36:34,527 --> 00:36:36,836
you will go free.

552
00:36:45,527 --> 00:36:47,245
Those files are confidential.

553
00:36:47,407 --> 00:36:51,559
Yeah, well, you know, l have this
natural curiosity about my fellow man.

554
00:36:55,727 --> 00:36:58,799
We got the results back
from your needle aspiration.

555
00:36:58,967 --> 00:37:01,276
Don't dance, doctor,
just give it to me straight.

556
00:37:01,807 --> 00:37:03,399
Okay.

557
00:37:04,367 --> 00:37:07,598
The lump under your nipple
is a stage two breast carcinoma.

558
00:37:10,767 --> 00:37:12,883
Stage two means
that we caught it relatively early.

559
00:37:13,047 --> 00:37:15,561
So your chances for survival
are good.

560
00:37:18,127 --> 00:37:20,641
The next step is surgery.

561
00:37:21,367 --> 00:37:23,244
Do you have any questions?

562
00:37:28,047 --> 00:37:30,117
You're married, right?

563
00:37:30,287 --> 00:37:31,959
- Yeah.
- Yeah, me too.

564
00:37:32,127 --> 00:37:34,595
You'd like my wife.
She's a real pisser.

565
00:37:34,767 --> 00:37:36,837
Does the doctor know
what he's talking about?

566
00:37:37,007 --> 00:37:38,918
- She.
- Give me the name of the bitch.

567
00:37:39,087 --> 00:37:40,725
- l'll talk to her.
- Would you fucking relax?

568
00:37:40,887 --> 00:37:41,956
Don't get pissy with me.

569
00:37:42,127 --> 00:37:43,526
l'm the one
who's thinking about you.

570
00:37:44,687 --> 00:37:47,406
We've known each other
all the way since back to high school.

571
00:37:47,567 --> 00:37:49,364
We'd fuck for days.

572
00:37:49,527 --> 00:37:52,883
And our friends, they were amazed

573
00:37:53,047 --> 00:37:54,321
because Shannon
never got pregnant.

574
00:37:55,127 --> 00:37:59,518
So one day before we got married,
she decided to get tested.

575
00:37:59,687 --> 00:38:02,155
And we find out that her tubes
or whatever are blocked,

576
00:38:02,327 --> 00:38:04,557
so she can't have any kids.

577
00:38:05,047 --> 00:38:09,802
l married her anyway,
because l knew she felt like shit.

578
00:38:10,767 --> 00:38:14,123
l knew that she didn't feel like
a woman anymore.

579
00:38:15,127 --> 00:38:17,960
- l can't stand it.
- No, no, hey.

580
00:38:18,127 --> 00:38:20,402
Hey, baby. Hey.

581
00:38:22,287 --> 00:38:23,800
Hey.

582
00:38:23,967 --> 00:38:27,880
But l cheated on her.

583
00:38:29,847 --> 00:38:31,405
A lot.

584
00:38:34,927 --> 00:38:37,043
Oh, man, l don't wanna die.

585
00:38:51,567 --> 00:38:53,080
lt's okay.

586
00:38:53,847 --> 00:38:54,996
So, what's next?

587
00:38:55,167 --> 00:38:58,284
l've scheduled O'Reily to have
a mastectomy at Benchley Memorial.

588
00:38:58,447 --> 00:39:00,005
We'll need transport and an officer.

589
00:39:00,167 --> 00:39:01,156
Or two.

590
00:39:01,327 --> 00:39:02,646
You think O'Reily
will try to escape?

591
00:39:03,687 --> 00:39:05,279
l'll be assisting Dr. Sophie Powell.

592
00:39:05,447 --> 00:39:07,244
She's the top breast-cancer surgeon
in the state.

593
00:39:07,407 --> 00:39:10,080
- All this sounds expensive.
- Well, it ain't gonna come cheap.

594
00:39:10,247 --> 00:39:11,919
- Will our insurance cover it?
- No.

595
00:39:12,087 --> 00:39:15,045
And the claims adjustor insists
O'Reily have a lumpectomy.

596
00:39:15,207 --> 00:39:17,437
That's where they remove the tumour
but not the breast, right?

597
00:39:17,607 --> 00:39:18,596
- Right.
- Now,

598
00:39:18,767 --> 00:39:20,485
if we can spare the breast
and save some money,

599
00:39:20,647 --> 00:39:21,636
why do a mastectomy?

600
00:39:21,807 --> 00:39:23,399
Well, lumpectomies
aren't always effective.

601
00:39:23,567 --> 00:39:26,035
They most often have to be
followed up with radiation or chemo.

602
00:39:26,207 --> 00:39:28,516
So then the prison is footing the bill
for this whole wingding?

603
00:39:28,687 --> 00:39:30,484
- Yeah.
- How much is that?

604
00:39:31,207 --> 00:39:35,086
The surgeon, staff and equipment...
ln all, $1 8,000.

605
00:39:36,527 --> 00:39:38,358
And a lumpectomy costs what?

606
00:39:38,767 --> 00:39:39,756
About half that.

607
00:39:41,647 --> 00:39:43,558
Well, give him the lumpectomy.

608
00:39:43,727 --> 00:39:45,957
A patient should be able to choose
his own medical procedure.

609
00:39:46,127 --> 00:39:47,719
- Don't you think?
- No, not at these prices.

610
00:39:47,887 --> 00:39:48,876
Not if he's a con.

611
00:39:49,047 --> 00:39:50,958
Look, Ryan O'Reily's
going through enough shit

612
00:39:51,127 --> 00:39:53,402
dealing with being a man
and having breast cancer.

613
00:39:53,807 --> 00:39:55,877
l mean, his survival depends
as much on a positive outlook

614
00:39:56,047 --> 00:39:57,036
as it does on the surgery.

615
00:39:57,207 --> 00:40:00,563
- Agreed.
- We can do a lot with that 1 8 grand.

616
00:40:00,727 --> 00:40:03,002
l don't mean to sound cold,
but whether Ryan O'Reily

617
00:40:03,167 --> 00:40:05,556
lives another two months or another
20 years means dick to me.

618
00:40:06,447 --> 00:40:08,244
Leo, ball's in your court.

619
00:40:09,087 --> 00:40:11,396
Give him the lumpectomy. Next item.

620
00:40:24,647 --> 00:40:26,080
Well...

621
00:40:27,167 --> 00:40:30,284
lf you die, what are we gonna do
about your brother?

622
00:40:44,207 --> 00:40:47,404
- Hey, bro.
- Hey, Cyril, come here.

623
00:40:47,567 --> 00:40:49,046
Hey.

624
00:40:52,207 --> 00:40:55,563
Hey, what's the matter?
Why are you so tense?

625
00:40:55,727 --> 00:40:57,604
l'm not tense.

626
00:40:57,807 --> 00:41:00,560
Yes, you are.
Your body's all stiff and shit.

627
00:41:01,327 --> 00:41:06,117
- Well, it's the gates and the guards.
- Yeah.

628
00:41:06,287 --> 00:41:09,040
- This place is scary.
- Yeah.

629
00:41:09,207 --> 00:41:12,995
- Yeah, you got that right.
- Why do you live here?

630
00:41:13,167 --> 00:41:15,886
- Because l was bad, remember?
- Oh, yeah.

631
00:41:16,047 --> 00:41:18,641
Yeah. And that's why
you're not bad anymore, right?

632
00:41:18,807 --> 00:41:20,763
- Right.
- Right.

633
00:41:21,887 --> 00:41:23,798
When are you coming home?

634
00:41:25,007 --> 00:41:27,043
Not for a while yet.

635
00:41:27,407 --> 00:41:29,841
l'm a little bit sick.

636
00:41:30,847 --> 00:41:34,681
- And l gotta have an operation.
- No, no operations.

637
00:41:34,847 --> 00:41:36,678
- Cyril.
- No operations.

638
00:41:36,847 --> 00:41:40,157
Mama died in an operation
Mama died in a hospital.

639
00:41:40,327 --> 00:41:41,362
- No, Cyril, stop it.
- No.

640
00:41:46,727 --> 00:41:50,766
Look, l'm gonna be fine. Okay?

641
00:41:52,447 --> 00:41:54,324
But if l'm not...

642
00:41:55,327 --> 00:41:58,478
Well, you know, Shannon,
she's gotta live her own life.

643
00:41:58,927 --> 00:42:00,565
So if she tells you
to move out of the house--

644
00:42:00,727 --> 00:42:03,844
- l like our apartment.
- l know you do.

645
00:42:05,167 --> 00:42:09,638
But, look, you may have to go
live with other people

646
00:42:10,567 --> 00:42:12,159
who are more like you.

647
00:42:13,807 --> 00:42:17,686
So if Shannon tells you
that you gotta go,

648
00:42:19,007 --> 00:42:20,759
l don't want you to cry,

649
00:42:20,927 --> 00:42:23,760
and l don't want you
to give Shannon a hard time.

650
00:42:23,927 --> 00:42:25,485
You got me?

651
00:42:25,647 --> 00:42:29,322
Because you gotta step up
and you gotta be a man, Cyril.

652
00:42:29,487 --> 00:42:30,556
Okay?

653
00:42:31,647 --> 00:42:33,877
lt's time to be a man.

654
00:43:12,927 --> 00:43:15,566
- Are you Dr. Nathan?
- No, no, l'm Dr. Nathan.

655
00:43:15,727 --> 00:43:18,639
Look, l know
he's just a criminal to you,

656
00:43:18,807 --> 00:43:21,002
but he's my fucking husband,
understand?

657
00:43:21,167 --> 00:43:22,486
Now, l asked around

658
00:43:22,647 --> 00:43:26,117
and this operation
is the cheapest thing that you can do.

659
00:43:27,767 --> 00:43:30,122
My husband's life ain't cheap.

660
00:43:30,287 --> 00:43:32,847
You make sure that Ryan's okay.

661
00:43:33,687 --> 00:43:35,757
You better make sure.

662
00:43:52,567 --> 00:43:53,966
Yes!

663
00:43:56,687 --> 00:43:57,722
l know who killed Dino.

664
00:44:02,127 --> 00:44:03,162
Fuck.

665
00:44:05,447 --> 00:44:07,199
- Hey.
- Hey.

666
00:44:07,367 --> 00:44:08,959
- You ready?
- Sure.

667
00:44:09,127 --> 00:44:12,836
- Let's fucking do this.
- Dr. Powell's scrubbing up.

668
00:44:13,007 --> 00:44:16,556
Been lying here thinking my life's
in the hands of a complete stranger.

669
00:44:16,727 --> 00:44:18,683
Well, she's the best.

670
00:44:19,087 --> 00:44:21,521
l feel better knowing you're around.

671
00:44:22,447 --> 00:44:25,166
- My guardian angel.
- Yeah, right.

672
00:44:25,327 --> 00:44:26,919
No, seriously.

673
00:44:27,367 --> 00:44:29,119
l can't figure out
why the fuck you care,

674
00:44:29,287 --> 00:44:31,562
but l'm glad you do.

675
00:44:31,727 --> 00:44:35,515
Nobody's ever done shit for me
my whole life.

676
00:44:36,047 --> 00:44:38,959
So l'm not very good
at saying thanks.

677
00:44:40,527 --> 00:44:42,438
l owe you.

678
00:44:42,887 --> 00:44:44,718
Bigtime.

679
00:44:55,447 --> 00:44:57,756
Now, you'd think a doctor or two
would be on the top of the list

680
00:44:57,927 --> 00:45:00,077
of the greatest person
of the millennium.

681
00:45:00,247 --> 00:45:03,080
l mean, doctors do research,
discover diseases, syndromes.

682
00:45:03,247 --> 00:45:05,477
But no one's gonna put
Drs. Epstein and Barr,

683
00:45:05,647 --> 00:45:07,080
Drs. Guillain and Barré,

684
00:45:07,247 --> 00:45:10,364
Dr. Down, or Dr. Alzheimer
on any list.

685
00:45:10,527 --> 00:45:15,203
Because for all their hard work,
hearing their names fills us with dread.

686
00:45:15,367 --> 00:45:17,642
Their names make us sick.

687
00:45:30,607 --> 00:45:32,518
You're being transferred
from Em City to Unit B.

688
00:45:33,687 --> 00:45:34,836
l'll miss you.

689
00:45:35,007 --> 00:45:37,282
Hey, l didn't bribe a CO
to kill Beecher. You did.

690
00:45:37,447 --> 00:45:38,516
The district-attorney's office

691
00:45:38,687 --> 00:45:42,316
has decided to charge you
with conspiracy to commit murder.

692
00:45:42,807 --> 00:45:43,796
The hearing's in two weeks.

693
00:45:43,967 --> 00:45:46,242
Do you want me to arrange
for a public defender?

694
00:45:48,847 --> 00:45:52,396
Yeah, yeah, l'd really like to have
some bleeding heart pleading my case.

695
00:45:52,567 --> 00:45:54,364
l'll get my own fucking lawyer.

696
00:45:54,527 --> 00:45:57,803
Well, if l were you,
l'd trade up from the last one.

697
00:45:58,047 --> 00:45:59,719
Jesus, you fucking cocksucker!

698
00:45:59,887 --> 00:46:01,479
You asked my advice,
l give you my advice.

699
00:46:01,647 --> 00:46:04,366
- You call me a fucking cocksucker.
- l don't want your advice.

700
00:46:04,527 --> 00:46:07,121
l want you to make this conspiracy-
to-commit-murder charge disappear.

701
00:46:07,287 --> 00:46:09,323
l'm a lawyer,
not the Amazing Kreskin.

702
00:46:09,487 --> 00:46:11,682
Look, the state's case is firm.

703
00:46:11,847 --> 00:46:14,236
The guard you bribed
is testifying against you.

704
00:46:14,407 --> 00:46:19,242
And call me crazy, l think that a law
officer has more credibility than you.

705
00:46:20,327 --> 00:46:24,240
- How much time am l looking at?
- Ten more years.

706
00:46:24,407 --> 00:46:25,999
Te--?

707
00:46:28,767 --> 00:46:30,758
All right, so l'll plead out.

708
00:46:31,367 --> 00:46:34,677
l'm not even sure the D.A.
would be willing to make a deal.

709
00:46:34,847 --> 00:46:36,644
What about Wittlesey?
l saw her murder Ross.

710
00:46:36,807 --> 00:46:40,004
l've informed the authorities
and demanded an investigation

711
00:46:40,167 --> 00:46:42,920
but frankly, that horse won't hunt.

712
00:46:44,767 --> 00:46:47,725
What about my sons?
Any word on them?

713
00:46:48,047 --> 00:46:50,436
Nope. But, you know, they'll turn up.

714
00:46:50,607 --> 00:46:52,677
Yeah, floating in a fucking river.

715
00:46:52,847 --> 00:46:55,919
lf they're out there somewhere, they're
doing crystal meth, for chrissakes.

716
00:46:56,087 --> 00:46:59,841
Will you please find my boys?

717
00:47:01,127 --> 00:47:02,640
You got it.

718
00:47:19,407 --> 00:47:22,683
Hey, Sister Peter Marie needs this
FedExed, Saturday delivery.

719
00:47:23,687 --> 00:47:26,759
Hey, Vern.
They let you out of the hole already?

720
00:47:30,087 --> 00:47:32,043
You're mad at me, aren't you?

721
00:47:32,527 --> 00:47:35,644
Sure, you're mad.
And l understand why.

722
00:47:35,807 --> 00:47:37,877
l fucked up your chances
for parole,

723
00:47:38,047 --> 00:47:41,039
you're facing ten more years in Oz,
all because of me.

724
00:47:41,567 --> 00:47:42,966
Oh, man.

725
00:47:43,207 --> 00:47:47,405
l manipulated you like the dumb-ass,
white-trash Neanderthal you are.

726
00:47:47,567 --> 00:47:50,240
You get to know a lot about a man
when he's fucking you in the ass.

727
00:47:53,487 --> 00:47:56,684
Getting slow there, sweet pea.
Getting a little soft.

728
00:48:09,807 --> 00:48:11,559
Hey, you got a smoke?

729
00:48:11,727 --> 00:48:13,001
Yo, you Schillinger?

730
00:48:16,207 --> 00:48:19,279
Schillinger. Yeah.

731
00:48:21,127 --> 00:48:23,766
l hear you used to run
the Aryan Brotherhood.

732
00:48:24,647 --> 00:48:25,966
Yeah.

733
00:48:27,087 --> 00:48:30,124
And you let Beecher
shit in your face?

734
00:48:47,087 --> 00:48:49,317
The Brotherhood's falling apart.

735
00:48:49,487 --> 00:48:51,637
When l ran the Brotherhood,
we were feared.

736
00:48:51,807 --> 00:48:54,002
Now even the fucking fags
look tougher.

737
00:48:54,167 --> 00:48:55,725
But listen, you and me, Mark,

738
00:48:55,887 --> 00:48:57,479
we can take things back
to the way they were.

739
00:48:57,647 --> 00:48:59,683
We can rule Oz.

740
00:49:00,607 --> 00:49:02,962
- Where do we start?
- We need a roadkill.

741
00:49:03,647 --> 00:49:06,002
Show everybody
we're back in the game.

742
00:49:07,647 --> 00:49:09,638
So who gets whacked first?

743
00:49:10,247 --> 00:49:13,000
The meanest motherfucking mutt
we can find.

744
00:49:29,127 --> 00:49:33,757
Prisoner number 98V238,
Alexander Vogel.

745
00:49:33,927 --> 00:49:36,725
Convicted June 1 st, '98.

746
00:49:41,287 --> 00:49:45,166
Two counts,
murder in the second degree, theft.

747
00:49:45,447 --> 00:49:49,440
Sentence: 50 years.
Up for parole in 30.

748
00:50:05,487 --> 00:50:08,559
So you don't know anything
about Alexander Vogel's murder?

749
00:50:09,287 --> 00:50:11,323
Well, if the Aryan Brotherhood's
not involved,

750
00:50:11,487 --> 00:50:14,160
why was ''Jew'' carved on his chest?

751
00:50:17,847 --> 00:50:20,884
Maybe some gang
is trying to lay the blame on us.

752
00:50:21,327 --> 00:50:24,125
We're not the only ones
that hate Jews, you know?

753
00:50:24,287 --> 00:50:26,642
l mean, your people do too.

754
00:50:27,007 --> 00:50:29,840
You're involved in this, Schillinger.
l know you are.

755
00:50:30,007 --> 00:50:31,406
Yeah?

756
00:50:32,087 --> 00:50:36,160
Well, if that's true, prove it.

757
00:50:36,327 --> 00:50:37,806
l will.

758
00:50:38,447 --> 00:50:40,278
Take him to his cell.

759
00:50:43,887 --> 00:50:49,564
Wish l was in the land of cotton
Old times there are not forgotten

760
00:50:52,487 --> 00:50:56,196
Hey, nice job on Vogel. Nice.

761
00:50:58,407 --> 00:51:01,479
Every inmate knows we did it.
That's what matters.

762
00:51:01,687 --> 00:51:06,522
- So, what happens next?
- Next, we take care of him.

763
00:51:14,647 --> 00:51:16,399
We kill Beecher?

764
00:51:16,967 --> 00:51:18,320
Yeah.

765
00:51:18,807 --> 00:51:21,480
But first, we make him suffer.

766
00:51:21,647 --> 00:51:24,161
Suffer long and hard.

767
00:51:27,727 --> 00:51:30,924
Maybe the greatest man
of the millennium was a woman.

768
00:51:31,087 --> 00:51:33,726
Princess Di, Mother Teresa,
Catherine the Great.

769
00:51:33,887 --> 00:51:36,845
Madame Curie, Marilyn Monroe.

770
00:51:37,007 --> 00:51:38,486
Say what you want about her, yo.

771
00:51:38,647 --> 00:51:40,205
She made her little slice
of the millennium

772
00:51:40,367 --> 00:51:42,562
a shitload more interesting.

773
00:51:44,847 --> 00:51:46,678
Shirley Bellinger,
who was convicted for the murder

774
00:51:46,847 --> 00:51:49,964
of her 4-year-old daughter,
was sentenced to death today.

775
00:51:50,127 --> 00:51:52,960
The first woman in this state
to be executed since 1 84 1.

776
00:51:54,607 --> 00:51:56,757
She will receive
a lethal injection next month

777
00:51:56,927 --> 00:51:58,679
at Oswald State Penitentiary.

778
00:51:58,847 --> 00:52:01,156
Bellinger's lawyer has already filed
an appeal in federal court

779
00:52:01,327 --> 00:52:03,716
and will hold a press conference
tomorrow.

780
00:52:03,887 --> 00:52:04,876
Speaking from the capital,

781
00:52:05,047 --> 00:52:07,242
Governor Devlin said
he supports the sentence

782
00:52:07,407 --> 00:52:11,161
and would not consider
a stay of execution if petitioned.

783
00:52:13,927 --> 00:52:15,883
How comfy.

784
00:52:21,847 --> 00:52:26,284
Yo, imagine being remembered
for a thousand years.

785
00:52:26,447 --> 00:52:27,766
The things you did
when you was alive

786
00:52:27,927 --> 00:52:32,523
reaching across time and touching
the lives of people not yet born.

787
00:52:32,807 --> 00:52:34,240
That's some dream.

788
00:52:34,407 --> 00:52:36,398
Yeah, that's why people write books,

789
00:52:36,567 --> 00:52:38,558
start religions, find cures,

790
00:52:38,727 --> 00:52:40,843
run for president. But me?

791
00:52:41,007 --> 00:52:42,406
l don't wanna be a great man.

792
00:52:42,567 --> 00:52:45,035
l don't care if l'm remembered
for the next thousand years.

793
00:52:45,207 --> 00:52:49,485
All l ask is if we pass on the street,

794
00:52:49,927 --> 00:52:51,599
notice me.

