1
00:01:45,087 --> 00:01:47,601
lt's called the butterfly effect.

2
00:01:47,807 --> 00:01:51,641
A butterfly starts flapping its wings
in China, and over the course of time,

3
00:01:51,807 --> 00:01:56,039
that little movement of air
becomes a hurricane in Texas.

4
00:01:56,207 --> 00:01:58,516
One day,
you got a butterfly dancing on a flower.

5
00:01:58,687 --> 00:02:02,521
The next,
you got pianos stuck in trees.

6
00:02:02,687 --> 00:02:04,598
The little butterfly,
he didn't know any better.

7
00:02:04,767 --> 00:02:10,125
He was just out looking for food,
for love, for some kind of satisfaction.

8
00:02:17,727 --> 00:02:19,638
Count.

9
00:02:24,087 --> 00:02:26,203
Oh, fuck.

10
00:02:38,687 --> 00:02:39,836
Let's go, Beecher.

11
00:02:41,527 --> 00:02:42,926
l'm not feeling well.

12
00:02:44,127 --> 00:02:46,357
This place smells like a gin mill.

13
00:02:46,527 --> 00:02:49,360
- So do you. You've been drinking?
- No.

14
00:02:53,567 --> 00:02:56,764
Yep, you've been drinking.

15
00:02:57,167 --> 00:02:58,600
Let's go.

16
00:03:05,127 --> 00:03:06,242
Where'd you get the moonshine?

17
00:03:07,487 --> 00:03:09,125
- l don't know, man.
- You don't know?

18
00:03:10,447 --> 00:03:12,881
lt just magically appeared
in your cell?

19
00:03:13,407 --> 00:03:15,284
- Yeah.
- Who brought it in, fairies?

20
00:03:16,127 --> 00:03:17,765
Or was it Keller?

21
00:03:17,927 --> 00:03:20,282
Because if it was Keller,
l'll leave him in the hole for a month.

22
00:03:20,447 --> 00:03:22,005
lt wasn't Keller. lt was me.

23
00:03:22,167 --> 00:03:24,044
Then who sold you the moonshine?

24
00:03:25,247 --> 00:03:26,919
- Some guy in Unit B.
- What's his name?

25
00:03:27,087 --> 00:03:29,157
- l don't know.
- Maybe you need time in the hole.

26
00:03:29,327 --> 00:03:32,125
Tim, l'd like to talk to him alone
for just a moment.

27
00:03:32,287 --> 00:03:34,198
Sure, you deal with him.

28
00:03:39,127 --> 00:03:43,405
l know, Sister, l know.
l was doing so well.

29
00:03:43,567 --> 00:03:46,001
You've also been
under a lot of pressure recently.

30
00:03:46,167 --> 00:03:49,159
Your wife dying, you falling in love.

31
00:03:51,487 --> 00:03:53,682
You told me, remember?

32
00:03:55,207 --> 00:03:56,196
Who is it? Keller?

33
00:03:57,927 --> 00:04:00,964
He's in the hole and you miss him.
Right?

34
00:04:02,007 --> 00:04:03,759
l'm gonna send you
to the hospital ward,

35
00:04:03,927 --> 00:04:05,838
get you some aspirin,

36
00:04:06,007 --> 00:04:09,682
let you sleep it off this one time.

37
00:04:11,207 --> 00:04:15,325
Listen, you drink again
and l will kick your ass.

38
00:04:23,487 --> 00:04:25,239
Mail call.

39
00:04:30,007 --> 00:04:31,759
Hey, Beech-ball.

40
00:04:32,487 --> 00:04:34,603
Yeah,
l heard you went on a little bender.

41
00:04:35,887 --> 00:04:38,959
You're upset
about your wife killing herself, huh?

42
00:04:40,407 --> 00:04:42,841
Would it make you feel any better
if l told you that

43
00:04:43,007 --> 00:04:45,680
she didn't commit suicide,
that l had her killed?

44
00:04:48,607 --> 00:04:49,926
You're lying.

45
00:04:50,767 --> 00:04:52,519
Maybe l am.

46
00:04:53,047 --> 00:04:54,844
Maybe l'm not.

47
00:04:55,007 --> 00:04:58,716
She wrote me a note
telling me her reasons.

48
00:04:58,887 --> 00:05:01,117
She would've written anything.

49
00:05:01,567 --> 00:05:04,764
She would've done anything
with that gun pointed to her head.

50
00:05:05,847 --> 00:05:07,280
Bullshit.

51
00:05:08,767 --> 00:05:11,327
l guess you'll never know for sure.

52
00:05:12,927 --> 00:05:14,280
Best part is,

53
00:05:15,327 --> 00:05:17,204
either way, it's your fucking fault.

54
00:05:18,007 --> 00:05:19,201
Hey!

55
00:05:19,367 --> 00:05:20,766
What's going on over there?

56
00:05:21,527 --> 00:05:22,926
Nothing.

57
00:05:25,887 --> 00:05:28,355
Later, fuckwad.

58
00:05:30,207 --> 00:05:32,004
Can l get some water?

59
00:05:33,247 --> 00:05:35,636
- Hey, O'Reily.
- Yeah?

60
00:05:35,807 --> 00:05:37,399
l heard
your brother came into Oz yesterday.

61
00:05:37,567 --> 00:05:38,966
- Yeah.
- You seen him yet?

62
00:05:39,127 --> 00:05:40,162
No.

63
00:05:40,327 --> 00:05:41,555
- You know what unit he's in?
- No.

64
00:05:41,727 --> 00:05:43,080
Want me to find out?

65
00:05:43,247 --> 00:05:46,000
Why are you suddenly so interested
in me and my family, Coushaine?

66
00:05:46,167 --> 00:05:48,601
l don't know. You're both brothers,
both inmates in the same prison.

67
00:05:48,767 --> 00:05:50,758
- lt's just kind of--
- What? You trying to convert us?

68
00:05:50,927 --> 00:05:54,363
Give Cyril and me a family discount?
Fuck you.

69
00:05:54,527 --> 00:05:56,757
- No, l'm just--
- Move away.

70
00:06:02,087 --> 00:06:03,202
Hey.

71
00:06:05,567 --> 00:06:07,444
You're Cyril O'Reily, right?

72
00:06:08,127 --> 00:06:10,197
Can l have my ball back?

73
00:06:11,007 --> 00:06:13,202
Hey, you look like your brother.

74
00:06:14,367 --> 00:06:16,039
Can l have my ball back?

75
00:06:19,287 --> 00:06:21,562
l know Ryan from Emerald City.

76
00:06:21,727 --> 00:06:24,799
Emerald City? What's that?

77
00:06:24,967 --> 00:06:28,084
You wanna see Em City?
You wanna see your brother?

78
00:06:30,847 --> 00:06:32,326
Come with me.

79
00:06:50,247 --> 00:06:52,044
Where's Ryan?

80
00:06:52,527 --> 00:06:57,237
Well, Cyril,
the way things work in Oz is this:

81
00:06:57,407 --> 00:06:59,477
Before l take you to your brother,

82
00:06:59,647 --> 00:07:02,081
you have to do something for me.

83
00:07:03,047 --> 00:07:04,924
Okay. What?

84
00:07:05,687 --> 00:07:08,440
First, take off your clothes.

85
00:07:08,607 --> 00:07:10,438
lt's okay.

86
00:07:14,647 --> 00:07:17,081
Come on. lt's all right.

87
00:07:20,327 --> 00:07:23,046
Supposedly,
cats can see in the dark.

88
00:07:23,447 --> 00:07:25,119
But how do we know for sure?

89
00:07:25,927 --> 00:07:30,318
And if you could be given cat's eyes,
even for one night,

90
00:07:30,487 --> 00:07:33,365
would you really wanna see
what's going on?

91
00:07:42,807 --> 00:07:44,286
Cyril.

92
00:07:44,447 --> 00:07:45,675
Cyril.

93
00:07:45,847 --> 00:07:46,836
Hey.

94
00:07:47,007 --> 00:07:48,918
- Hey.
- Hey.

95
00:07:49,407 --> 00:07:51,204
Hey, knock it off.

96
00:07:51,367 --> 00:07:52,925
He's my brother.

97
00:07:53,087 --> 00:07:55,282
Looks more like your sister.

98
00:07:55,447 --> 00:07:56,675
Knock it off.

99
00:07:59,207 --> 00:08:03,041
Hey. So where'd they put you, huh?
Which unit are you in?

100
00:08:03,847 --> 00:08:06,680
l don't know. With him.

101
00:08:08,807 --> 00:08:11,241
Don't worry.
l gave him the royal welcome.

102
00:08:13,247 --> 00:08:16,284
You better not fucking touch him.
You got that, motherfucker?

103
00:08:17,127 --> 00:08:18,765
Why, you gonna touch him?

104
00:08:18,927 --> 00:08:21,236
l want you to stay away
from that Nazi fuck.

105
00:08:21,407 --> 00:08:24,160
You understand me? Cyril?

106
00:08:24,487 --> 00:08:27,001
l think l did a bad thing.

107
00:08:27,927 --> 00:08:29,724
Oh, fuck.

108
00:08:32,007 --> 00:08:33,042
Listen to me.

109
00:08:33,207 --> 00:08:35,516
l'm gonna get you transferred
out of Unit B. Okay?

110
00:08:35,687 --> 00:08:38,406
Now, l don't know how long
it's gonna take me.

111
00:08:38,567 --> 00:08:39,841
So in the meantime,

112
00:08:40,007 --> 00:08:41,520
hit me.

113
00:08:41,687 --> 00:08:43,166
- What?
- Hit me.

114
00:08:44,007 --> 00:08:46,840
- Ryan--
- Just fucking hit me.

115
00:08:48,207 --> 00:08:49,845
Stop.

116
00:08:50,007 --> 00:08:51,645
Come on, hit me.

117
00:08:53,927 --> 00:08:56,885
- You just bought a ticket to the hole.
- Ryan.

118
00:08:57,407 --> 00:08:58,601
- Ryan?
- Go with him.

119
00:08:58,767 --> 00:09:01,406
Ryan. Ryan.

120
00:09:01,567 --> 00:09:03,523
Ryan!

121
00:09:03,687 --> 00:09:06,963
l wanna be with you, Ryan.

122
00:09:07,127 --> 00:09:08,242
You're dead.

123
00:09:16,287 --> 00:09:19,916
McManus, l want you
to transfer my brother to Em City.

124
00:09:20,087 --> 00:09:24,956
Your brother. The one who killed
Gloria Nathan's husband?

125
00:09:25,367 --> 00:09:28,643
The one who we just put in ad seg
for punching you?

126
00:09:29,207 --> 00:09:30,560
Give me a break.

127
00:09:30,727 --> 00:09:34,640
You leave Cyril where he is
and Schillinger will suck his bones dry.

128
00:09:34,807 --> 00:09:36,445
Well, Schillinger's
gonna suck anyway,

129
00:09:36,607 --> 00:09:38,802
so why should your brother
be the one that's spared?

130
00:09:38,967 --> 00:09:40,116
He's slow.

131
00:09:40,647 --> 00:09:43,957
Cyril had an accident last year
and he got slow.

132
00:09:44,127 --> 00:09:45,685
He doesn't understand
what's going on here.

133
00:09:45,847 --> 00:09:47,519
He can't protect himself.

134
00:09:47,687 --> 00:09:49,723
Sad, but too bad.

135
00:09:51,327 --> 00:09:55,525
Hey. l'll do anything you ask me to.
Anything.

136
00:09:55,687 --> 00:09:57,086
- A deal?
- Yes.

137
00:09:57,247 --> 00:09:58,885
Okay.
l want you to rat on somebody.

138
00:09:59,487 --> 00:10:01,159
- Who?
- Yourself.

139
00:10:01,327 --> 00:10:04,763
l want you to confess you told Cyril
to murder Preston Nathan.

140
00:10:04,927 --> 00:10:06,201
l didn't.

141
00:10:06,367 --> 00:10:08,005
Oh, you did.

142
00:10:08,167 --> 00:10:09,202
lf l say yes,

143
00:10:09,367 --> 00:10:12,200
l'm looking at another decade
added on to my sentence.

144
00:10:12,367 --> 00:10:14,597
- Probably.
- No way.

145
00:10:14,767 --> 00:10:20,444
Well, then your brother stays
in Vern Schillinger's ever-loving arms.

146
00:10:20,607 --> 00:10:22,325
McManus, don't you fucking
play with me.

147
00:10:22,487 --> 00:10:23,715
- Hey!
- Get out.

148
00:10:23,887 --> 00:10:25,718
You got something to say, say it.

149
00:10:25,887 --> 00:10:27,366
l'm a busy man.

150
00:10:29,647 --> 00:10:32,241
Fuck you, McManus,
you fucking cocksucker.

151
00:10:33,887 --> 00:10:36,196
A federal court
today upheld a new state law

152
00:10:36,367 --> 00:10:38,676
that requires sex offenders
released from prison

153
00:10:38,847 --> 00:10:40,917
to register with local police.

154
00:10:41,087 --> 00:10:43,806
Victims' rights groups
are calling the decision a total victory

155
00:10:43,967 --> 00:10:45,923
because the law permits neighbours
to be notified

156
00:10:46,087 --> 00:10:47,964
if a sex offender moves
into their community.

157
00:10:48,127 --> 00:10:50,004
They can't do that, it's Orwellian.

158
00:10:50,167 --> 00:10:51,156
Or-who-ian?

159
00:10:51,327 --> 00:10:54,125
lf a man pays his debt to society,
if he redeems himself,

160
00:10:54,287 --> 00:10:56,562
he deserves a chance at a normal life
when he gets out.

161
00:10:56,727 --> 00:10:58,126
Perverts aren't normal.

162
00:10:58,287 --> 00:11:00,517
l mean, if one moved next door to me,
l'd wanna know about it.

163
00:11:00,687 --> 00:11:01,915
- You?
- Yeah.

164
00:11:02,087 --> 00:11:04,157
You're a convicted murderer.

165
00:11:04,327 --> 00:11:05,396
- So?
- So?

166
00:11:05,567 --> 00:11:07,478
What if it's murderers next?
What if when you get out,

167
00:11:07,647 --> 00:11:09,126
you have to register
with your community,

168
00:11:09,287 --> 00:11:10,686
tell everybody
you did time for murder?

169
00:11:10,847 --> 00:11:13,156
Why stop there?
Register bigots, fat ladies.

170
00:11:13,447 --> 00:11:16,245
Fuck, people who talk
in movie theatres. l hate those people.

171
00:11:16,567 --> 00:11:18,285
You know what
they should tell you?

172
00:11:18,527 --> 00:11:21,963
They should register, like, some
sex-crazed nympho with real big titties

173
00:11:22,127 --> 00:11:23,480
when she moves onto your block.

174
00:11:23,647 --> 00:11:24,796
That's what they should tell you.

175
00:11:24,967 --> 00:11:26,764
They should give you
her phone number and address.

176
00:11:26,927 --> 00:11:28,201
- Word.
- Bet you wouldn't mind that.

177
00:11:28,447 --> 00:11:30,756
Thanks for the stimulating
conversation. You guys are like goats.

178
00:11:30,927 --> 00:11:32,804
You gotta bring everything
down to the level of a goat.

179
00:11:33,007 --> 00:11:35,043
Titties and humping.

180
00:11:35,967 --> 00:11:37,764
- Sex offender.
- Sex offender.

181
00:11:41,647 --> 00:11:44,445
Sippel, follow me.

182
00:11:47,007 --> 00:11:48,838
l am a priest.

183
00:11:49,727 --> 00:11:51,399
l am a pervert.

184
00:11:51,567 --> 00:11:54,525
l knew early on
that l had a vocation from God.

185
00:11:55,607 --> 00:11:58,201
l knew early on
that l had these other...

186
00:12:00,487 --> 00:12:02,557
These other tremblings.

187
00:12:02,887 --> 00:12:05,845
l acted on the first
but never on the second.

188
00:12:06,007 --> 00:12:07,360
Never.

189
00:12:09,167 --> 00:12:12,443
l'd done nothing
but good works my whole life.

190
00:12:13,447 --> 00:12:15,165
Yet l never...

191
00:12:17,367 --> 00:12:19,403
l never saw God

192
00:12:22,327 --> 00:12:26,115
until l saw that boy.

193
00:12:27,167 --> 00:12:31,683
Fourteen years old,
his body so perfect,

194
00:12:31,847 --> 00:12:34,759
so pure, so angelic.

195
00:12:37,407 --> 00:12:38,999
l had to touch it.

196
00:12:39,167 --> 00:12:43,160
Prisoner number 88S51 0,
Robert Sippel.

197
00:12:43,327 --> 00:12:47,605
Convicted March 1 0, '88,
sexual abuse in the second degree.

198
00:12:47,767 --> 00:12:53,080
Sentence? Fifteen years.
Up for parole in ten.

199
00:12:54,727 --> 00:12:59,005
l fondled him for a moment,
just a moment.

200
00:12:59,327 --> 00:13:02,046
He didn't yell. He didn't cry.

201
00:13:02,847 --> 00:13:04,917
He didn't tell a soul.

202
00:13:05,087 --> 00:13:06,122
l confessed.

203
00:13:09,327 --> 00:13:12,797
l want to be saved.
l want to do good.

204
00:13:15,687 --> 00:13:18,565
l want Jesus to forgive me.

205
00:13:20,167 --> 00:13:21,964
He has, Robert.

206
00:13:22,367 --> 00:13:25,006
But you need to forgive yourself.

207
00:13:25,167 --> 00:13:27,044
You've done your time.

208
00:13:27,207 --> 00:13:30,404
Tomorrow, you'll be out in the world,
able to start a new life.

209
00:13:30,567 --> 00:13:31,682
A new life?

210
00:13:32,967 --> 00:13:35,242
What kind of life would that be?

211
00:13:37,167 --> 00:13:39,806
And Sippel gets out tomorrow morning
without a job,

212
00:13:39,967 --> 00:13:43,118
without a place to live,
and no support.

213
00:13:43,287 --> 00:13:46,199
So l called a friend at the diocese to
see if a bed was available anywhere

214
00:13:46,367 --> 00:13:47,800
and he laughed.

215
00:13:47,967 --> 00:13:49,161
Well, can you blame him?

216
00:13:49,327 --> 00:13:52,683
The church paid off a million-dollar
lawsuit to Sippel's victim.

217
00:13:52,847 --> 00:13:54,644
Ray, l want you to call
your buddy, the cardinal

218
00:13:54,807 --> 00:13:55,876
and get him to help Sippel.

219
00:13:57,407 --> 00:13:58,476
No.

220
00:13:59,087 --> 00:14:00,236
Why not?

221
00:14:01,007 --> 00:14:03,077
Well, it's not a favour that l'll ask.

222
00:14:03,247 --> 00:14:04,566
Because...

223
00:14:04,727 --> 00:14:07,446
Look, my relationship
with His Eminence is stormy at best.

224
00:14:07,607 --> 00:14:11,566
l can't be calling him every ten minutes
asking him for a favour.

225
00:14:12,607 --> 00:14:13,801
And?

226
00:14:17,647 --> 00:14:20,002
And Sippel disgusts me.

227
00:14:20,167 --> 00:14:23,125
Ray, he made a mistake.
He's repentant.

228
00:14:23,287 --> 00:14:24,686
He deserves absolution.

229
00:14:24,847 --> 00:14:26,883
He robbed a boy of his innocence.

230
00:14:27,047 --> 00:14:29,322
- He's a child molester.
- He was.

231
00:14:29,487 --> 00:14:32,524
That child trusted his priest.
He's a threat.

232
00:14:32,687 --> 00:14:34,882
To what? To society?

233
00:14:35,047 --> 00:14:36,924
To the priesthood?

234
00:14:37,927 --> 00:14:38,962
To you?

235
00:14:50,247 --> 00:14:52,078
Hello, Father Mukada.

236
00:14:55,887 --> 00:14:57,400
You're still reading the breviary.

237
00:14:57,567 --> 00:14:58,761
Oh, yes. Every day.

238
00:14:59,407 --> 00:15:01,363
Just as l was taught to do
in the seminary.

239
00:15:02,087 --> 00:15:04,123
But you're not a priest anymore.

240
00:15:05,727 --> 00:15:09,606
When l was ordained,
l became a priest forever.

241
00:15:10,287 --> 00:15:12,005
Forever, just like you.

242
00:15:13,447 --> 00:15:16,359
But the church has stripped me
of my powers.

243
00:15:17,007 --> 00:15:21,637
l'm a priest forever,
but not allowed to be a priest.

244
00:15:23,487 --> 00:15:27,400
l'm a man forever,
but not allowed to be a man.

245
00:15:29,367 --> 00:15:31,039
l am...

246
00:15:32,967 --> 00:15:35,800
...yet l'm not, you see.

247
00:15:39,327 --> 00:15:40,601
Father, will you pray with me?

248
00:15:42,607 --> 00:15:44,165
l can't.

249
00:15:44,327 --> 00:15:46,795
l can't pray with you.

250
00:15:48,487 --> 00:15:51,160
But l will pray for you.

251
00:15:57,927 --> 00:16:01,363
No, sir. All l'm asking is
that you give him a second chance.

252
00:16:01,527 --> 00:16:03,119
He knows
that he can't work with kids again.

253
00:16:03,287 --> 00:16:06,438
But the church is still
a part of his life and--

254
00:16:07,567 --> 00:16:09,797
But if you abandon him...

255
00:16:11,407 --> 00:16:13,796
l am aware of the victim.

256
00:16:14,807 --> 00:16:16,445
Yes, sir.

257
00:16:18,407 --> 00:16:19,681
No.

258
00:16:22,487 --> 00:16:24,205
Thank you, cardinal.

259
00:16:25,847 --> 00:16:26,916
Channel 3 News has learned

260
00:16:27,087 --> 00:16:30,079
that Robert Sippel, a Catholic priest
convicted of sexually abusing

261
00:16:30,247 --> 00:16:32,283
a boy in his care,
will be released today

262
00:16:32,447 --> 00:16:34,915
from Oswald
Maximum Security Penitentiary.

263
00:16:35,087 --> 00:16:37,123
Sippel spent ten years in jail

264
00:16:37,287 --> 00:16:40,245
for the molestation
of a 1 4-year-old boy upstate.

265
00:16:40,407 --> 00:16:43,717
A state law requires Sippel must
register as a sex offender with police

266
00:16:43,887 --> 00:16:46,799
and is expected
to reside in the area.

267
00:16:47,207 --> 00:16:49,004
Anxious residents
have expressed their concern

268
00:16:49,167 --> 00:16:52,045
over Sippel's plan
to live in their neighbourhood.

269
00:17:00,207 --> 00:17:02,243
This is the cup of my blood.

270
00:17:02,407 --> 00:17:05,479
The blood
of the new and everlasting covenant.

271
00:17:05,647 --> 00:17:10,084
lt will be shed for you and for all
so that sins may be forgiven.

272
00:17:10,607 --> 00:17:12,359
Do this in memory of me.

273
00:17:22,767 --> 00:17:25,440
- Hey, Schillinger.
- What do you want?

274
00:17:25,607 --> 00:17:28,041
How much would it cost
to mail me out of here?

275
00:17:28,207 --> 00:17:29,845
Mail you?
What are you talking about?

276
00:17:30,007 --> 00:17:31,918
l've been trying to think of ways
to get out of here.

277
00:17:32,087 --> 00:17:33,918
- Escape from Oz?
- Yeah.

278
00:17:34,087 --> 00:17:36,078
And l figured, you know,
you could box me up in a crate

279
00:17:36,247 --> 00:17:38,442
and mail me to my wife
overnight express,

280
00:17:38,607 --> 00:17:40,802
Priority Mail, whatever.

281
00:17:40,967 --> 00:17:43,959
How much would that cost?
Postage, shipping, handling, et cetera?

282
00:17:44,127 --> 00:17:45,116
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.

283
00:17:45,287 --> 00:17:46,276
Then you're nuts.

284
00:17:46,447 --> 00:17:47,766
ls that a no?

285
00:17:48,367 --> 00:17:50,358
Yeah. No.

286
00:17:51,367 --> 00:17:54,279
No, yeah, it's a no. Get the fuck
out of here before l tip you over.

287
00:17:54,447 --> 00:17:56,119
All right, Vern, l ain't mad at you.

288
00:17:56,287 --> 00:17:59,120
You can't help it
if you're ugly and stupid.

289
00:18:16,087 --> 00:18:17,520
Ain't that a...

290
00:18:17,687 --> 00:18:20,155
Yo, what's up with him?

291
00:18:20,967 --> 00:18:23,561
- He's in love.
- Adebisi?

292
00:18:23,727 --> 00:18:26,002
Get the fuck out of here. With who?

293
00:18:26,167 --> 00:18:27,520
Shirley Bellinger.

294
00:18:27,687 --> 00:18:30,963
Say word.
That bitch over on death row?

295
00:18:31,127 --> 00:18:33,880
Word. They been exchanging notes.

296
00:18:34,047 --> 00:18:36,083
Every meal for about a week.

297
00:18:36,247 --> 00:18:37,475
How they know each other?

298
00:18:37,647 --> 00:18:41,799
That's what's funny about it.
They never even seen each other.

299
00:18:47,727 --> 00:18:48,955
Hey.

300
00:18:50,727 --> 00:18:52,558
Go away. You've got diseases.

301
00:18:52,727 --> 00:18:55,525
l'm cured, Adebisi.
Cancer's not contagious.

302
00:18:55,687 --> 00:18:57,279
That's what they say.

303
00:18:57,447 --> 00:18:59,403
- Look, l want back in the kitchen.
- No.

304
00:18:59,567 --> 00:19:01,205
Christ,
haven't l always been there for you?

305
00:19:01,767 --> 00:19:03,837
- No.
- Come on.

306
00:19:04,007 --> 00:19:05,963
l'm the only friend you got, pal.

307
00:19:07,087 --> 00:19:08,520
O'Reily, you can read, right?

308
00:19:08,687 --> 00:19:10,120
Yeah. So can you.

309
00:19:10,287 --> 00:19:12,084
Yeah, but not all the words.
Like this one.

310
00:19:12,247 --> 00:19:13,919
What does that say?

311
00:19:14,087 --> 00:19:15,725
Brawny.

312
00:19:16,207 --> 00:19:17,481
What does that mean, brawny?

313
00:19:17,647 --> 00:19:19,126
Lots of muscles.

314
00:19:20,847 --> 00:19:22,166
- l'm brawny.
- Yeah.

315
00:19:22,327 --> 00:19:24,318
Among other things.
Here, let me see.

316
00:19:24,487 --> 00:19:25,806
No.

317
00:19:26,527 --> 00:19:28,040
Let me see.

318
00:19:33,487 --> 00:19:36,047
Bellinger says
that tomorrow is her birthday.

319
00:19:37,127 --> 00:19:40,039
And it's her last birthday on Earth.

320
00:19:40,647 --> 00:19:43,320
And the only thing
that she really wants to do

321
00:19:43,487 --> 00:19:47,400
is to see your brawny body naked...

322
00:19:48,567 --> 00:19:50,159
And suck your cock.

323
00:19:51,687 --> 00:19:53,803
lt don't say that?
Where does it say that?

324
00:19:53,967 --> 00:19:55,480
Right there.

325
00:19:56,167 --> 00:19:57,759
Fellatio.

326
00:19:58,607 --> 00:19:59,881
Cunnilingus.

327
00:20:00,527 --> 00:20:01,801
Girlfriend can spell.

328
00:20:04,207 --> 00:20:06,118
l wanna see her.

329
00:20:06,447 --> 00:20:07,596
l wanna meet her.

330
00:20:07,767 --> 00:20:09,758
You want her to suck your cock.

331
00:20:11,287 --> 00:20:12,686
lf l can arrange it,

332
00:20:12,847 --> 00:20:14,803
will you let me back in the kitchen?

333
00:20:14,967 --> 00:20:18,960
O'Reily, if she sucks my cock,

334
00:20:21,007 --> 00:20:22,565
l'll suck yours.

335
00:20:22,727 --> 00:20:25,321
That's an appetizing thought. Pass.

336
00:20:25,487 --> 00:20:28,524
Hey, hey, hey. Can you do it?

337
00:20:28,687 --> 00:20:30,439
l can do it.

338
00:20:36,127 --> 00:20:37,162
All right, listen.

339
00:20:37,327 --> 00:20:39,557
Tomorrow,
Adebisi's doing your mop duty.

340
00:20:39,727 --> 00:20:41,479
- Why?
- So he can see Bellinger.

341
00:20:41,647 --> 00:20:43,638
Fuck that.
Every day she shows her pussy.

342
00:20:43,807 --> 00:20:46,924
Well, you're gonna have to go
without it for once. Here, take that.

343
00:20:56,647 --> 00:20:58,205
Here, Shirley.

344
00:20:58,967 --> 00:21:01,117
Thank you, dumpling.

345
00:21:07,167 --> 00:21:09,078
Well, l'll be.

346
00:21:11,407 --> 00:21:14,240
That Simon thinks of everything.

347
00:21:24,047 --> 00:21:25,036
Shirley?

348
00:21:25,767 --> 00:21:29,203
- You like your cake?
- Yes.

349
00:21:35,807 --> 00:21:37,559
Happy birthday, baby.

350
00:21:38,887 --> 00:21:40,764
You're Simon?

351
00:21:42,927 --> 00:21:44,440
Quickly.

352
00:21:45,727 --> 00:21:46,921
Before the hacks come.

353
00:21:47,087 --> 00:21:48,122
But...

354
00:21:48,287 --> 00:21:50,596
- What?
- You're a nigger.

355
00:21:57,487 --> 00:21:59,364
Suck my dick now.

356
00:21:59,527 --> 00:22:01,006
Hey, get the fuck away from her.

357
00:22:01,167 --> 00:22:02,725
What the fuck are you doing?

358
00:22:02,887 --> 00:22:04,286
Tony, Al.

359
00:22:04,807 --> 00:22:06,718
Adebisi, move. Get away.

360
00:22:06,887 --> 00:22:08,718
Suck my dick.

361
00:22:32,687 --> 00:22:35,281
Yo, Wangler. Check this out, man.

362
00:22:35,447 --> 00:22:37,597
This nigga's bugging.

363
00:22:39,127 --> 00:22:41,880
Yo, man.
What the fuck is up with you, man?

364
00:22:42,607 --> 00:22:44,438
- Go away.
- What the fuck?

365
00:22:44,607 --> 00:22:46,404
- You losing your mind or something?
- Go away!

366
00:22:59,607 --> 00:23:01,165
Stay down.

367
00:23:09,487 --> 00:23:12,604
Hey, Chucky.
How's your head?

368
00:23:12,767 --> 00:23:15,042
That can of peaches
knocked your brains loose?

369
00:23:17,927 --> 00:23:19,724
Fuck those guys, man.

370
00:23:20,447 --> 00:23:23,405
Don't worry about them.
l got good news.

371
00:23:23,567 --> 00:23:25,842
Antonio Nappa's coming to Oz.

372
00:23:26,807 --> 00:23:30,038
For those of you going to Emerald City,
we got rules.

373
00:23:30,207 --> 00:23:33,324
We got a lot more rules
than anywhere else in Oz.

374
00:23:33,487 --> 00:23:37,162
Your cell is your home.
You are to keep it clean.

375
00:23:37,327 --> 00:23:40,239
You are to exercise regularly,
attend classes,

376
00:23:40,407 --> 00:23:42,363
go to drug and alcohol counselling.

377
00:23:42,527 --> 00:23:44,597
Follow the rules.

378
00:23:44,767 --> 00:23:45,802
There is no yelling,

379
00:23:45,967 --> 00:23:48,959
no fighting, no fucking.

380
00:23:49,127 --> 00:23:50,924
Okay, those of you going to Em City

381
00:23:51,087 --> 00:23:52,122
will each be given a sponsor.

382
00:23:52,287 --> 00:23:54,005
You can pair up as follows.

383
00:23:54,167 --> 00:23:56,840
Nappa, Pancamo.

384
00:23:57,527 --> 00:23:59,040
Hoyt, Burns.

385
00:24:00,367 --> 00:24:03,086
Vincent, Adebisi.

386
00:24:03,887 --> 00:24:06,401
The rest of you
can follow Officer Tobin to Gen Pop.

387
00:24:12,247 --> 00:24:13,236
Goldfish.

388
00:24:13,407 --> 00:24:16,717
They live their whole lives
in 30-second intervals.

389
00:24:17,247 --> 00:24:19,317
Every half minute,
their little brain forgets

390
00:24:19,487 --> 00:24:22,240
what the last half minute
of their life was like.

391
00:24:22,407 --> 00:24:25,524
ln other words,
when this little goldfish is happy,

392
00:24:25,687 --> 00:24:27,245
he thinks he's been happy
his whole life

393
00:24:27,407 --> 00:24:30,444
since his whole life
was only 30 seconds ago.

394
00:24:30,607 --> 00:24:32,996
And when this little goldfish
is hungry,

395
00:24:33,167 --> 00:24:35,556
he thinks he's been hungry
his whole life.

396
00:24:36,207 --> 00:24:37,481
And when he's dying,

397
00:24:37,647 --> 00:24:41,640
this little goldfish thinks
he's been dying his whole life.

398
00:24:42,127 --> 00:24:43,879
lmagine that.

399
00:24:44,407 --> 00:24:49,879
Death being the only life
this little goldfish will ever know.

400
00:25:12,607 --> 00:25:16,998
Prisoner number 98N7 44,
Antonio Nappa.

401
00:25:17,167 --> 00:25:20,842
Convicted June 4, '98,
murder in the second degree.

402
00:25:21,007 --> 00:25:26,320
Sentence: 80 years.
Up for parole in 50.

403
00:25:27,247 --> 00:25:30,842
Needless to say, l was saddened
by Peter Schibetta's rape.

404
00:25:31,007 --> 00:25:32,963
His father, Nino, and l were paisans.

405
00:25:33,127 --> 00:25:34,765
l'm Peter's godfather.

406
00:25:37,087 --> 00:25:41,160
No, his actual godfather at baptism.

407
00:25:42,287 --> 00:25:44,084
We won't tolerate revenge.

408
00:25:44,247 --> 00:25:45,282
Nor should you.

409
00:25:45,447 --> 00:25:48,996
All l ask is that you punish
the man responsible.

410
00:25:49,167 --> 00:25:50,566
We will when we find him.

411
00:25:50,727 --> 00:25:52,365
You have no suspect?

412
00:25:52,527 --> 00:25:56,042
We have suspects.
Problem is, we have no witnesses.

413
00:25:56,207 --> 00:25:59,005
Pancamo was unconscious
and Schibetta--

414
00:25:59,167 --> 00:26:00,282
--ls unwilling to talk.

415
00:26:00,447 --> 00:26:01,482
That's right.

416
00:26:01,647 --> 00:26:02,966
May l see him?

417
00:26:05,447 --> 00:26:07,039
No.

418
00:26:09,807 --> 00:26:13,641
l tell you, Antonio, l think
that Peter's mind has snapped.

419
00:26:13,807 --> 00:26:17,163
He keeps talking to his father,
as if Nino was still alive.

420
00:26:17,327 --> 00:26:19,602
This Adebisi who raped Peter,

421
00:26:19,767 --> 00:26:22,327
we can't kill him, at least not yet.

422
00:26:22,487 --> 00:26:23,522
But l want him to suffer.

423
00:26:23,687 --> 00:26:27,202
l want to take away
whatever's most important to him.

424
00:26:27,367 --> 00:26:28,846
Well, well,

425
00:26:29,007 --> 00:26:31,885
that would be heroin. He's a fiend.

426
00:26:32,047 --> 00:26:34,163
- He's a user and a dealer?
- Yeah.

427
00:26:34,327 --> 00:26:36,045
Then his black ass is mine.

428
00:26:37,167 --> 00:26:39,397
l want you to suggest to Glynn

429
00:26:39,567 --> 00:26:43,242
that it's time to do
a little random drug testing.

430
00:26:43,407 --> 00:26:44,601
You got it.

431
00:26:49,567 --> 00:26:52,604
You, you,

432
00:26:52,767 --> 00:26:56,123
you and you.

433
00:26:56,967 --> 00:26:58,525
Come with me.

434
00:27:00,447 --> 00:27:01,960
Hill.

435
00:27:03,927 --> 00:27:05,679
Rebadow.

436
00:27:08,847 --> 00:27:10,485
Said.

437
00:27:14,087 --> 00:27:15,884
Adebisi.

438
00:27:34,127 --> 00:27:35,560
Hey.

439
00:27:35,727 --> 00:27:37,126
Hey.

440
00:27:38,567 --> 00:27:40,842
- Let's go.
- Let's go.

441
00:27:41,487 --> 00:27:43,717
Simon, after the riot,

442
00:27:43,887 --> 00:27:47,402
you went into
severe heroin withdrawal.

443
00:27:47,567 --> 00:27:49,637
l thought you kicked the habit.

444
00:27:49,807 --> 00:27:51,718
- l did.
- Oh, come on.

445
00:27:51,887 --> 00:27:54,276
These reports say
that you're still using.

446
00:27:54,447 --> 00:27:57,644
Now, l want you
to come to drug counselling.

447
00:27:57,807 --> 00:28:00,526
Rehab is bullshit. No offence.

448
00:28:01,327 --> 00:28:02,362
Fine.

449
00:28:02,527 --> 00:28:04,483
Then l'll have you tested
for drug use every week.

450
00:28:04,647 --> 00:28:07,559
And if you keep using,
l'll send you to the psych ward.

451
00:28:07,727 --> 00:28:10,605
Have you ever been
to the psych ward here, Simon?

452
00:28:10,767 --> 00:28:12,723
Peter Schibetta's there.

453
00:28:13,247 --> 00:28:16,398
Along with 20 other guys
who've lost all sense of reality.

454
00:28:16,567 --> 00:28:19,479
Reality? Oz?

455
00:28:21,047 --> 00:28:24,357
So tell me,
what world are you living in?

456
00:28:24,527 --> 00:28:29,965
Better yet,
which world are you trying to avoid?

457
00:28:30,287 --> 00:28:34,405
Because drugs
are all about avoidance, Simon,

458
00:28:35,047 --> 00:28:39,677
about not being able to accept
some secret in yourself.

459
00:28:42,207 --> 00:28:46,723
Sister,
don't send me to that loony bin.

460
00:28:46,887 --> 00:28:49,117
l will come to your meetings.

461
00:28:49,287 --> 00:28:51,721
l will stop taking drugs.

462
00:29:01,567 --> 00:29:03,762
What are you looking at, old man?

463
00:29:09,487 --> 00:29:14,925
Hey. Nappa, he engineered
the drug testing to slow you down.

464
00:29:15,407 --> 00:29:17,238
- Yeah?
- Yeah.

465
00:29:19,047 --> 00:29:21,356
Looks like l'm gonna
have to kill me some dagos.

466
00:29:21,527 --> 00:29:23,119
Thattaboy.

467
00:29:28,927 --> 00:29:31,157
Here's the plan:
We go out there, grab that bitch Nappa

468
00:29:31,327 --> 00:29:32,840
and his guinea friends,
cut their throats.

469
00:29:33,007 --> 00:29:34,360
- What, now?
- Yeah.

470
00:29:34,527 --> 00:29:36,677
lt's the middle of fucking lunchtime.
What are you, crazy?

471
00:29:36,847 --> 00:29:39,566
- ls there a better time?
- Yes, there's a fucking better time.

472
00:29:39,727 --> 00:29:41,763
There's hacks all over the place.
Everyone's gonna see.

473
00:29:41,927 --> 00:29:43,360
Let them see. l said, do it now.

474
00:29:43,527 --> 00:29:45,802
Please, go back.

475
00:29:45,967 --> 00:29:49,118
You disgrace us all
when you act like a fool.

476
00:29:49,887 --> 00:29:50,922
Out of my way.

477
00:29:51,087 --> 00:29:52,998
We're African brothers.
l know you see that.

478
00:29:53,167 --> 00:29:54,441
Look at all this black skin around.

479
00:29:54,607 --> 00:29:56,359
No, you and l are different.

480
00:29:56,527 --> 00:29:58,279
l'm no different.

481
00:29:58,727 --> 00:30:00,365
Yoruba.

482
00:30:02,607 --> 00:30:05,485
What have they turned you into?

483
00:30:06,327 --> 00:30:08,318
Who are you?

484
00:30:08,847 --> 00:30:10,724
Who are you?

485
00:30:11,927 --> 00:30:14,487
ls there a problem here, Adebisi?

486
00:30:18,127 --> 00:30:20,004
No problem, officer.

487
00:30:20,167 --> 00:30:22,237
Then get back to work.

488
00:31:06,367 --> 00:31:08,039
Hey, hey.

489
00:31:08,527 --> 00:31:10,597
What happened in the cafeteria
with that old man?

490
00:31:10,767 --> 00:31:12,405
Just some crazy fuck.

491
00:31:12,567 --> 00:31:14,523
You were gonna take care of Nappa.

492
00:31:14,687 --> 00:31:16,040
Another day.

493
00:31:16,207 --> 00:31:18,084
Are you planning
on doing anything soon?

494
00:31:18,247 --> 00:31:21,683
Yeah, planning on lying down.
Wangler.

495
00:31:23,847 --> 00:31:25,917
Where's the CD player?

496
00:31:26,687 --> 00:31:28,518
The batteries are low.

497
00:31:36,087 --> 00:31:37,520
Here.

498
00:31:41,967 --> 00:31:43,116
What's in here?

499
00:31:43,287 --> 00:31:45,801
Some hard shit my cousin sent me.

500
00:31:48,807 --> 00:31:51,082
What are we gonna do
about Nappa, man?

501
00:31:51,527 --> 00:31:53,040
Adebisi?

502
00:31:57,007 --> 00:31:59,157
You know what? Fuck it.

503
00:32:00,487 --> 00:32:01,556
You slipping.

504
00:32:01,727 --> 00:32:04,924
And if your balls end up in a cannoli,
don't say shit.

505
00:32:57,727 --> 00:32:59,126
What's up, man?

506
00:33:08,567 --> 00:33:12,162
- That's my motherfucking CD player.
- What is he doing?

507
00:33:16,087 --> 00:33:20,046
Do you believe in voodoo, Chucky?
The power of magic?

508
00:33:20,207 --> 00:33:22,323
- No.
- l do.

509
00:33:22,767 --> 00:33:24,837
There's an old wives' tale in Sicily

510
00:33:25,007 --> 00:33:27,680
that a new bride waits
until she menstruates,

511
00:33:27,847 --> 00:33:30,725
then she takes her blood
and puts it into the first tomato sauce

512
00:33:30,887 --> 00:33:32,684
she makes for her husband.

513
00:33:32,847 --> 00:33:33,882
What for?

514
00:33:34,047 --> 00:33:37,437
lf he eats her blood,
she can control him forever.

515
00:33:37,607 --> 00:33:41,919
Somebody's got Adebisi
under a spell.

516
00:33:42,447 --> 00:33:44,961
Too bad it's not us.

517
00:33:49,407 --> 00:33:53,923
Those National Geographic specials,
they're popular here at Oz.

518
00:33:54,087 --> 00:33:57,045
All those wild beasts
attacking each other,

519
00:33:57,207 --> 00:33:59,801
ferocious lions running down
to the watering hole,

520
00:33:59,967 --> 00:34:04,040
brutalizing antelopes and gazelles.

521
00:34:04,807 --> 00:34:07,844
How come there's never a programme
where the animals get along,

522
00:34:08,007 --> 00:34:09,963
where they help each other?

523
00:34:10,127 --> 00:34:12,846
ls it possible for, say,
a flat-billed platypus

524
00:34:13,007 --> 00:34:16,317
to help a green-eyed cockatoo
cross the street?

525
00:34:23,527 --> 00:34:24,642
Now what?

526
00:34:24,807 --> 00:34:25,922
The fun part.

527
00:34:26,087 --> 00:34:28,282
We read everybody's mail.

528
00:34:28,687 --> 00:34:30,325
Our nigger warden has a rule.

529
00:34:30,487 --> 00:34:32,205
Every piece of mail
that comes into Oz

530
00:34:32,367 --> 00:34:34,722
gets opened
and thoroughly examined.

531
00:34:34,887 --> 00:34:36,525
ln case somebody's pulling a scam
or something.

532
00:34:36,687 --> 00:34:38,086
Right.

533
00:34:38,247 --> 00:34:39,362
lf we find anything suspicious,

534
00:34:39,527 --> 00:34:41,518
we're supposed to pass it on
to the supervising hack.

535
00:34:41,687 --> 00:34:42,915
And do we?

536
00:34:44,287 --> 00:34:45,481
His spot check is pretty regular,

537
00:34:45,647 --> 00:34:48,639
so you gotta pick your shot
letting something slip through.

538
00:34:48,807 --> 00:34:51,605
ln the meantime,
we know every prisoner's business.

539
00:34:52,047 --> 00:34:53,366
Right.

540
00:34:53,527 --> 00:34:57,520
And like the great man said,
''Knowledge is power.''

541
00:34:57,687 --> 00:35:00,485
You can do some real damage
with this bad boy.

542
00:35:02,127 --> 00:35:05,005
Relax. You're suffering from PBS.

543
00:35:05,167 --> 00:35:06,202
PBS?

544
00:35:06,367 --> 00:35:09,837
Pre-Bunny Syndrome. lt happens
quite often in my line of work.

545
00:35:10,007 --> 00:35:11,235
You dig and dig and dig,

546
00:35:11,407 --> 00:35:13,238
and just before you
have to make like a little bunny

547
00:35:13,407 --> 00:35:14,760
and go through the hole, you panic.

548
00:35:14,927 --> 00:35:17,077
This is real? Pre-Bunny Syndrome?

549
00:35:17,247 --> 00:35:18,726
Oh, yeah.

550
00:35:19,287 --> 00:35:22,006
l mean,
l made the name up, but sure.

551
00:35:27,447 --> 00:35:28,846
Come on, man, what's the slow-up?

552
00:35:29,007 --> 00:35:30,679
Keep your fucking shirt on.

553
00:35:37,407 --> 00:35:38,442
What's the matter?

554
00:35:40,807 --> 00:35:42,957
lt's a letter from my mother.

555
00:35:43,127 --> 00:35:44,276
You have a mother?

556
00:35:45,567 --> 00:35:49,196
She's 90. She says
my grandson has leukaemia.

557
00:35:49,367 --> 00:35:50,880
You have a grandson?

558
00:35:52,247 --> 00:35:54,761
My fiancée was pregnant
at the time of my arrest.

559
00:35:54,927 --> 00:35:57,361
Rebadow, who'd have thought
about you doing the nasty?

560
00:35:59,367 --> 00:36:01,961
You got a kid, huh? Boy or girl?

561
00:36:02,127 --> 00:36:04,846
Boy. Man.

562
00:36:05,487 --> 00:36:07,876
Alex would be 34.

563
00:36:08,447 --> 00:36:10,119
And he has a boy.

564
00:36:10,287 --> 00:36:11,720
Who has leukaemia.

565
00:36:13,647 --> 00:36:15,922
l've never seen either one of them.

566
00:36:20,047 --> 00:36:21,878
Okay, any other new business?

567
00:36:22,047 --> 00:36:26,279
Yeah. This guy Rebadow,
his grandson's got leukaemia.

568
00:36:27,527 --> 00:36:29,165
That's too bad, dude.

569
00:36:29,327 --> 00:36:31,887
The kid's dying, and his dying wish
is to go to Disney World.

570
00:36:32,047 --> 00:36:33,958
- Mine too.
- Mickey Mouse sucks cock.

571
00:36:34,207 --> 00:36:35,196
How do you know all this?

572
00:36:35,367 --> 00:36:38,279
l work the mail, right?
l read the letter from his mama.

573
00:36:38,967 --> 00:36:41,322
Rebadow's family
doesn't have the $3000

574
00:36:41,487 --> 00:36:43,125
to send the kid to Disney World.

575
00:36:43,287 --> 00:36:45,801
So l'm thinking,
maybe we should send him.

576
00:36:45,967 --> 00:36:47,446
- Who, us?
- Come on. How?

577
00:36:47,967 --> 00:36:50,765
My bike club,
we raised $1 0,000 once

578
00:36:50,927 --> 00:36:53,316
doing a run across the state
for the Ronald McDonald House.

579
00:36:53,487 --> 00:36:56,047
You all earn money in here
working whatever job you got,

580
00:36:56,207 --> 00:36:57,242
same as me.

581
00:36:57,407 --> 00:36:59,523
So l'm thinking,
instead of spending the money on shit,

582
00:37:00,047 --> 00:37:01,446
we can make a donation.

583
00:37:01,607 --> 00:37:03,802
Look, what the fuck do we care
about Rebadow's grandson?

584
00:37:03,967 --> 00:37:06,435
Hey, Kenny, if you don't care,
then you don't care.

585
00:37:06,607 --> 00:37:09,246
But if you do, then help out.

586
00:37:09,407 --> 00:37:13,195
Whatever you guys raise,
the COs will match.

587
00:37:14,127 --> 00:37:15,196
Meeting's adjourned.

588
00:37:19,407 --> 00:37:24,037
Look, it's not a lot, but take it.

589
00:37:25,247 --> 00:37:27,681
Thank you, Augustus,
Tobias, Busmalis.

590
00:37:28,487 --> 00:37:30,125
How much do you have?

591
00:37:30,927 --> 00:37:36,445
With this and the money
in my account, $72.

592
00:37:37,327 --> 00:37:39,204
One hundred and seventy-two.

593
00:37:41,127 --> 00:37:42,606
From the brothers.

594
00:37:43,367 --> 00:37:44,720
Thank you. Thank you.

595
00:37:44,887 --> 00:37:47,845
l thought l was gonna die. You know?

596
00:37:48,807 --> 00:37:51,560
So maybe your grandson,
he won't die.

597
00:37:51,727 --> 00:37:52,842
Maybe.

598
00:37:53,007 --> 00:37:54,725
But just in case...

599
00:37:55,887 --> 00:37:57,286
Here.

600
00:38:19,727 --> 00:38:20,921
l got kids too.

601
00:38:21,087 --> 00:38:23,078
Mostly they're a pain in the ass,
but...

602
00:38:26,087 --> 00:38:28,157
So how much have you raised?

603
00:38:28,687 --> 00:38:30,996
Almost $2000.

604
00:38:31,167 --> 00:38:33,761
Then this
should put you over the top.

605
00:38:37,447 --> 00:38:40,041
First thing tomorrow,
l'll wire the money to my mother.

606
00:38:40,207 --> 00:38:41,196
l've told her it was coming

607
00:38:41,367 --> 00:38:44,484
and l told her
l want this gift to be anonymous.

608
00:38:44,647 --> 00:38:47,480
l don't want my grandson to know
where it came from.

609
00:38:47,647 --> 00:38:49,126
You're ashamed?

610
00:38:51,967 --> 00:38:53,320
Yes.

611
00:39:24,007 --> 00:39:27,158
That's fucking what l heard.
Rebadow collected like 3 G's.

612
00:39:27,807 --> 00:39:30,082
And that money's gone tomorrow.

613
00:39:31,607 --> 00:39:33,086
You know what?

614
00:39:33,647 --> 00:39:38,323
l'm thinking we go to Rebadow,
we take the dough,

615
00:39:38,487 --> 00:39:40,159
and then so these other fucks
don't get mad,

616
00:39:40,327 --> 00:39:42,443
we make Rebadow swear
that he sent it.

617
00:39:42,607 --> 00:39:44,120
No.

618
00:39:44,287 --> 00:39:45,800
What do you mean, no?
lt's $3000.

619
00:39:45,967 --> 00:39:47,685
l said, no.

620
00:39:48,167 --> 00:39:49,202
Why?

621
00:39:50,087 --> 00:39:53,124
Because sometimes
it's good to be human.

622
00:40:06,447 --> 00:40:11,441
Prisoner number 98H432,
Jaz Hoyt.

623
00:40:30,007 --> 00:40:32,840
Convicted August 1 2, '98,

624
00:40:33,007 --> 00:40:35,521
aggravated assault
in the first degree.

625
00:40:35,687 --> 00:40:40,363
Sentence: eight years.
Up for parole in four.

626
00:40:42,207 --> 00:40:44,038
- Yo, Alvarez.
- Man, no, leave me alone.

627
00:40:44,207 --> 00:40:46,038
Wait a second, man.
l gotta ask you a question, bro.

628
00:40:46,207 --> 00:40:47,242
What?

629
00:40:49,327 --> 00:40:53,764
Yo, working bedpans, you ever see
any opportunities at getting out?

630
00:40:53,927 --> 00:40:56,680
Getting out?
What, you mean like escape?

631
00:40:56,847 --> 00:40:58,519
Yeah, man.

632
00:41:00,447 --> 00:41:01,436
You trying to escape, Hill?

633
00:41:02,807 --> 00:41:04,877
l've been exploring the possibilities.

634
00:41:05,047 --> 00:41:06,082
Right.

635
00:41:06,247 --> 00:41:09,125
Okay, well, hospital ward, right?
That's a dead end.

636
00:41:09,287 --> 00:41:12,643
Because if there was a way out,
my ass would be like a vapour.

637
00:41:12,807 --> 00:41:14,035
But hey,

638
00:41:14,207 --> 00:41:17,324
you find a crack,
you let me know, all right?

639
00:41:17,487 --> 00:41:19,762
Because l'd be there
right behind you.

640
00:41:19,927 --> 00:41:20,996
- Okay?
- Yeah.

641
00:41:21,167 --> 00:41:22,486
Okay.

642
00:41:25,607 --> 00:41:29,077
Welcome to Oswald
Maximum Security Penitentiary.

643
00:41:29,247 --> 00:41:32,637
We are, of course, pleased that
the state budget increased its line item

644
00:41:32,807 --> 00:41:34,286
for more correctional officers.

645
00:41:34,447 --> 00:41:37,007
Your presence here
will help alleviate stress

646
00:41:37,167 --> 00:41:39,158
between the COs and the inmates

647
00:41:39,327 --> 00:41:42,205
as well as increase safety for all.

648
00:41:42,367 --> 00:41:45,359
Now, l myself stood where
you're standing some 30 years ago.

649
00:41:46,127 --> 00:41:47,446
The warden back then

650
00:41:47,607 --> 00:41:50,440
gave us a piece of advice
l'd like to pass on to you.

651
00:41:52,367 --> 00:41:55,677
Be aware and beware.

652
00:41:55,847 --> 00:41:57,678
My own little addendum

653
00:41:57,847 --> 00:41:59,599
is ''be fair.''

654
00:41:59,767 --> 00:42:02,440
Again, welcome.

655
00:42:12,367 --> 00:42:13,800
Man, l know that dude.

656
00:42:13,967 --> 00:42:14,956
The new hack?

657
00:42:15,127 --> 00:42:16,401
Yeah, man. He was in Los Diablos.

658
00:42:16,567 --> 00:42:18,956
Los Diablos?
You wiped the motherfuckers out.

659
00:42:19,127 --> 00:42:21,687
Rivera was always a pussy.

660
00:42:23,047 --> 00:42:25,959
- Yeah, speaking of pussies.
- You shut the fuck up.

661
00:42:26,127 --> 00:42:28,357
What do you want, Michael?

662
00:42:28,527 --> 00:42:31,724
l wanna have a sit-down,
just him and me.

663
00:42:32,567 --> 00:42:34,762
Yo, get out, man. You're busted.

664
00:42:35,727 --> 00:42:37,080
Can l?

665
00:42:45,327 --> 00:42:48,205
You know, my grandfather was
in Oz for 40 years.

666
00:42:48,367 --> 00:42:50,517
Spent the last half in solitary.

667
00:42:50,687 --> 00:42:51,881
Yeah, l know.

668
00:42:52,487 --> 00:42:54,762
My father was an inmate here.

669
00:42:55,727 --> 00:42:58,002
Got his tongue cut out.

670
00:42:58,167 --> 00:43:01,079
Yeah, l know, man. So what?

671
00:43:01,967 --> 00:43:04,561
Yo, man,
l used to run shit around here.

672
00:43:05,727 --> 00:43:08,195
You know? And l got no problem
with you taking over.

673
00:43:08,367 --> 00:43:11,723
l mean, you, El Cid,
you have cojones.

674
00:43:11,887 --> 00:43:14,765
But, yo, ever since you came in, man,
l've been low man.

675
00:43:14,927 --> 00:43:16,918
l get my face in the dirt every day.

676
00:43:20,127 --> 00:43:24,564
l just wanna know what l gotta do
to get in your good graces.

677
00:43:25,287 --> 00:43:27,482
Change your skin, man.
You're too white.

678
00:43:28,487 --> 00:43:30,762
Man, there ain't nothing
l can do about that.

679
00:43:30,927 --> 00:43:34,442
l'm not talking about your outside.
l'm talking about right here, man.

680
00:43:34,607 --> 00:43:35,722
Too white.

681
00:43:35,887 --> 00:43:37,206
l'm not.

682
00:43:38,687 --> 00:43:40,359
All right, l'll prove it.

683
00:43:40,967 --> 00:43:42,923
You tell me to do something.

684
00:43:45,327 --> 00:43:46,999
See that pato over there?

685
00:43:54,607 --> 00:43:56,359
Are you kidding me?

686
00:44:09,567 --> 00:44:10,966
Papa.

687
00:44:11,527 --> 00:44:13,802
Gonglewski's shit in his bed again?

688
00:44:13,967 --> 00:44:15,764
l'll give you a hand.

689
00:44:18,767 --> 00:44:24,717
Papa, l got a problem,
and l got nobody to talk to but you.

690
00:44:26,967 --> 00:44:29,322
El Cid is in Oz now.

691
00:44:29,487 --> 00:44:31,921
And the only way
he's gonna let me stay in the game...

692
00:44:33,287 --> 00:44:36,723
He wants me
to pluck out the eyes of a CO.

693
00:44:36,887 --> 00:44:38,923
Some new guy, Rivera.

694
00:44:39,087 --> 00:44:40,839
Now, the way l see it,

695
00:44:41,007 --> 00:44:43,965
if l do it, l'm dead.

696
00:44:44,287 --> 00:44:45,515
The hacks are gonna tear me apart.

697
00:44:45,687 --> 00:44:47,757
lf l don't, El Cid will.

698
00:44:48,887 --> 00:44:50,081
Papa, l don't know what to do.

699
00:44:52,647 --> 00:44:54,603
l mean, what do l do?

700
00:45:11,727 --> 00:45:13,479
Count.

701
00:45:14,727 --> 00:45:18,276
88P21 7. 86M51 0.

702
00:45:18,447 --> 00:45:21,200
93K51 8. 92H240.

703
00:45:21,367 --> 00:45:24,279
96J522.

704
00:45:24,447 --> 00:45:27,325
98H498.

705
00:45:27,487 --> 00:45:29,637
92M220.

706
00:45:29,807 --> 00:45:31,559
97 A41 3.

707
00:45:31,727 --> 00:45:32,876
Hey.

708
00:45:33,047 --> 00:45:34,116
What?

709
00:45:35,727 --> 00:45:37,319
What, Alvarez?

710
00:45:38,127 --> 00:45:41,597
They say the eyes
are the mirrors of the soul.

711
00:45:41,767 --> 00:45:44,201
What the fuck
are you talking about?

712
00:45:44,807 --> 00:45:46,763
Nice to see you.

713
00:45:51,847 --> 00:45:56,841
97P468. 98N7 44.

714
00:45:57,007 --> 00:46:02,843
91T81 8. 92L41 1 .

715
00:46:13,167 --> 00:46:15,044
Did Diane Wittlesey
shoot Scott Ross

716
00:46:15,207 --> 00:46:18,324
with the intention of ending his life?

717
00:46:18,487 --> 00:46:21,160
Did Wittlesey murder Ross?

718
00:46:24,767 --> 00:46:26,166
No.

719
00:46:26,767 --> 00:46:27,995
Hey, hey, there you are.

720
00:46:28,167 --> 00:46:30,442
Do you have time
to go over the statistical reports?

721
00:46:30,607 --> 00:46:32,802
Not right now,
l promised Coushaine that l would

722
00:46:32,967 --> 00:46:34,446
sit in on
his reading-and-writing class.

723
00:46:35,407 --> 00:46:36,396
Okay.

724
00:46:44,287 --> 00:46:46,755
Hey, Leo.

725
00:46:46,927 --> 00:46:48,883
- Hey.
- l've been meaning to ask you,

726
00:46:50,127 --> 00:46:51,845
how's your daughter?

727
00:46:52,407 --> 00:46:55,285
Well, she's out of the hospital,
on the road to recovery.

728
00:46:55,447 --> 00:46:58,166
That's great. l'm happy for you.
How about your brother?

729
00:46:58,847 --> 00:47:00,838
His trial starts in two weeks.

730
00:47:01,007 --> 00:47:02,406
God gives, God takes, huh?

731
00:47:04,207 --> 00:47:06,767
- Yeah.
- How about it?

732
00:47:06,927 --> 00:47:10,124
Come on, a little one-on-one.

733
00:47:10,287 --> 00:47:11,481
Nope.

734
00:47:13,367 --> 00:47:14,846
Hey, Leo.

735
00:47:17,487 --> 00:47:20,524
l know l can't tell the truth
about Ross' shooting,

736
00:47:20,687 --> 00:47:23,838
but l can't carry the lie around
anymore either.

737
00:47:24,247 --> 00:47:26,920
l try. l can't.

738
00:47:27,687 --> 00:47:30,565
Then find a way to lose the lie.

739
00:47:33,727 --> 00:47:36,287
Diane, l-- Sorry.

740
00:47:36,447 --> 00:47:39,405
lt's all right, Tim. lt's not like
you haven't seen me undressed.

741
00:47:39,567 --> 00:47:40,966
What's up?

742
00:47:42,607 --> 00:47:46,122
You're always telling me
that l get lost inside my own head,

743
00:47:46,287 --> 00:47:48,084
that l gotta be more blunt.

744
00:47:48,247 --> 00:47:49,362
So l'm going to be blunt.

745
00:47:50,687 --> 00:47:51,881
At Schillinger's hearing,

746
00:47:52,047 --> 00:47:56,120
l put my hand on the Bible
and l swore to God

747
00:47:56,287 --> 00:47:57,925
that l would tell the truth.

748
00:47:58,087 --> 00:48:00,043
And then l lied.

749
00:48:00,207 --> 00:48:02,163
l lied for you.

750
00:48:03,047 --> 00:48:05,242
And now, every time l see you,

751
00:48:05,407 --> 00:48:07,443
l'm reminded of my lie,

752
00:48:07,607 --> 00:48:10,599
of the vow to God that l broke.

753
00:48:10,767 --> 00:48:12,359
Of my sin.

754
00:48:13,487 --> 00:48:14,966
And?

755
00:48:15,127 --> 00:48:18,722
l want you to transfer
out of Em City to another unit.

756
00:48:24,207 --> 00:48:27,517
- Wittlesey's working on Unit B now.
- Find out why.

757
00:48:27,687 --> 00:48:29,166
Think she's been
selling cigarettes again?

758
00:48:29,327 --> 00:48:30,601
l heard she had
a nervous breakdown.

759
00:48:30,767 --> 00:48:32,120
lt's because of McManus.

760
00:48:32,287 --> 00:48:34,278
- God, l miss those tits of hers, man.
- Me too.

761
00:48:34,447 --> 00:48:36,756
- What do you think?
- Never liked the woman.

762
00:48:37,327 --> 00:48:39,966
l wonder who the new
head hack's gonna be.

763
00:48:40,127 --> 00:48:42,322
As long as it's not him.

764
00:48:49,927 --> 00:48:50,916
People are always wondering

765
00:48:51,087 --> 00:48:54,443
if their pets are gonna make it
to heaven.

766
00:48:54,607 --> 00:48:57,997
lf Jojo or Muffy are gonna pass
through those Pearly Gates.

767
00:48:58,167 --> 00:49:00,123
How much you wanna bet
the animals are wondering

768
00:49:00,287 --> 00:49:02,403
if their masters are gonna make it?

769
00:49:02,567 --> 00:49:04,478
Cats, dogs, parakeets,

770
00:49:04,647 --> 00:49:09,163
they don't spend their whole lives
drowning in sin, lies and suffering.

771
00:49:09,327 --> 00:49:10,840
They just wallow in the truth.

772
00:49:11,527 --> 00:49:13,006
lmagine that.

773
00:49:13,167 --> 00:49:15,601
lf all we humans knew
of life on Earth

774
00:49:15,767 --> 00:49:17,997
was the goddamn truth...

775
00:49:41,767 --> 00:49:43,166
Beecher.

776
00:49:44,927 --> 00:49:46,246
Don't do this.

777
00:49:47,127 --> 00:49:48,526
Do what?

778
00:49:49,927 --> 00:49:51,076
Drink.

779
00:49:53,327 --> 00:49:56,046
You love to dabble in people's lives,
don't you?

780
00:49:56,207 --> 00:49:58,516
You're so much better than us
because you've seen the light.

781
00:49:58,687 --> 00:50:00,996
You've seen the face of God.

782
00:50:01,167 --> 00:50:05,718
So you wave your dick around
in order to save us lowly mortals.

783
00:50:05,887 --> 00:50:09,243
Hill, Mershah, Groves.

784
00:50:09,847 --> 00:50:12,042
Jefferson Keane.

785
00:50:12,207 --> 00:50:15,199
Fuck, you helped Jefferson Keane
right into a lethal injection.

786
00:50:15,927 --> 00:50:18,725
- But in the end--
- No, no, no.

787
00:50:18,887 --> 00:50:20,843
When all is said and done,

788
00:50:21,007 --> 00:50:24,841
who have you really fucking helped,

789
00:50:25,287 --> 00:50:27,243
other than yourself?

790
00:50:28,407 --> 00:50:29,726
Poet.

791
00:50:30,567 --> 00:50:32,000
Poet?

792
00:50:32,167 --> 00:50:34,761
l just saw on the news,
he killed a man.

793
00:50:35,407 --> 00:50:37,557
He's coming back to Oz.

794
00:50:39,967 --> 00:50:43,926
Little Miss Tucket sat on a bucket
Eating some peaches and cream

795
00:50:44,087 --> 00:50:45,759
Then came a grasshopper
And tried to stop her

796
00:50:45,927 --> 00:50:48,680
But she said
''Go away or l'll scream!''

797
00:51:17,647 --> 00:51:23,597
Prisoner number 98J448,
Arnold Jackson, a.k.a. Poet.

798
00:51:23,767 --> 00:51:27,646
Convicted July 20, '98,
murder in the second degree.

799
00:51:28,087 --> 00:51:33,639
Sentence: 26 years.
Up for parole in 1 9.

800
00:52:12,127 --> 00:52:15,358
Can we get by, brother?
Come on, man.

801
00:52:23,567 --> 00:52:24,886
So, what is it that separates

802
00:52:25,047 --> 00:52:30,041
you and me from the goldfish,
the butterfly, the flat-billed platypus?

803
00:52:30,607 --> 00:52:32,677
Our minds, huh?

804
00:52:32,847 --> 00:52:35,122
Our souls, huh?

805
00:52:35,287 --> 00:52:37,517
The fact that we can get HBO?

806
00:52:37,687 --> 00:52:41,157
Well, maybe it's that humans
are the only species

807
00:52:41,327 --> 00:52:43,887
to put other animals in cages.

808
00:52:44,047 --> 00:52:47,596
Put its own kind in cages.

