1
00:01:41,167 --> 00:01:42,441
Family.

2
00:01:42,607 --> 00:01:46,077
Our families determine who we are,
determine what we're not.

3
00:01:46,247 --> 00:01:50,035
All of our relationships with everybody
we ever meet for the rest of our lives

4
00:01:50,207 --> 00:01:54,564
is based on the way we relate
to the members of our family.

5
00:01:54,727 --> 00:01:58,163
No wonder the world's so fucked up.

6
00:02:03,047 --> 00:02:04,526
Said.

7
00:02:06,407 --> 00:02:07,840
l read your book.

8
00:02:08,007 --> 00:02:09,759
l don't give refunds.

9
00:02:12,007 --> 00:02:13,599
l liked it.

10
00:02:14,207 --> 00:02:17,199
- Really, l did.
- Schillinger, what do you want?

11
00:02:17,967 --> 00:02:19,480
Same as you.

12
00:02:20,367 --> 00:02:23,359
l see in here a man who wants
to fuck the system.

13
00:02:23,527 --> 00:02:25,757
Use the law against itself.

14
00:02:25,927 --> 00:02:27,599
l do too.

15
00:02:28,047 --> 00:02:31,039
l've been charged with conspiracy
to commit murder.

16
00:02:31,447 --> 00:02:33,244
Trial's coming up.

17
00:02:34,087 --> 00:02:37,159
l fired my horseshit lawyer.
l want you to represent me.

18
00:02:41,047 --> 00:02:42,526
l'm serious.

19
00:02:43,287 --> 00:02:44,845
Think of it.

20
00:02:45,407 --> 00:02:49,685
lf Kareem Said believes l'm innocent,
the jury might too.

21
00:02:49,847 --> 00:02:54,523
And if you defend a white man
with my kind of beliefs,

22
00:02:54,687 --> 00:02:56,405
you'll stun Glynn and McManus.

23
00:02:56,567 --> 00:02:59,240
You will rock the outside world.

24
00:02:59,927 --> 00:03:02,566
You will be known as a man who truly
strives for justice,

25
00:03:02,727 --> 00:03:06,436
blind to race,
unfettered by prejudice.

26
00:03:08,887 --> 00:03:10,002
What do you say?

27
00:03:19,927 --> 00:03:21,838
l'll think about it.

28
00:03:37,447 --> 00:03:39,039
Hey, yo,
what the fuck is you doing, man?

29
00:03:39,207 --> 00:03:42,722
ls that my poetry you fucking with?
What the fuck is you doing, man?

30
00:03:44,407 --> 00:03:46,477
What you think,
this is a fucking joke, B?

31
00:03:46,647 --> 00:03:48,478
l'll fucking break you up,
that's my word, B.

32
00:03:48,647 --> 00:03:50,126
- Don't fuck with my poetry.
- Come on.

33
00:03:50,287 --> 00:03:51,720
Girls, stop it, you're both pretty.

34
00:03:51,887 --> 00:03:53,366
Come on, come on. Come on.

35
00:03:53,527 --> 00:03:55,438
Get the other bum out of here.

36
00:03:55,607 --> 00:03:57,245
Come on, do-rag.

37
00:04:04,887 --> 00:04:07,526
This is your third incident
in as many weeks.

38
00:04:07,687 --> 00:04:10,724
Clearly l am not getting
through to you.

39
00:04:11,167 --> 00:04:14,204
So as of today, our deal is off.

40
00:04:15,047 --> 00:04:18,278
You're back in the kitchen
mopping floors.

41
00:04:18,607 --> 00:04:20,563
Big fucking deal.

42
00:04:23,727 --> 00:04:25,445
l'm not gonna let you graduate.

43
00:04:25,607 --> 00:04:27,916
You can still go to class,
get your diploma,

44
00:04:28,087 --> 00:04:30,237
but l'm not gonna let you go
to the graduation ceremony.

45
00:04:30,407 --> 00:04:31,886
My girl's coming
and my mom's coming.

46
00:04:32,047 --> 00:04:33,799
Too bad. Call them and cancel.

47
00:04:40,247 --> 00:04:42,238
You have got to stay out of trouble.

48
00:04:42,407 --> 00:04:43,886
Fucker ripped up my poems, man.

49
00:04:44,047 --> 00:04:47,801
Even so, you're being published,

50
00:04:47,967 --> 00:04:50,037
and so a lot of
very important people,

51
00:04:50,207 --> 00:04:54,405
very famous writers, have taken up
your cause to get your case reviewed.

52
00:04:54,567 --> 00:04:56,603
We're about to go before
the parole commission.

53
00:04:56,767 --> 00:04:59,679
Something like this could
screw things up completely.

54
00:05:00,447 --> 00:05:01,800
Now...

55
00:05:03,047 --> 00:05:07,279
...Sister Peter Marie says that you
haven't been to drug counselling lately.

56
00:05:07,527 --> 00:05:09,199
l'm gonna let that slide too.

57
00:05:09,367 --> 00:05:10,925
You know why?

58
00:05:11,847 --> 00:05:14,407
Because you give this place
a good name.

59
00:05:14,967 --> 00:05:18,039
You do anything to give it a bad name
from here on out,

60
00:05:18,207 --> 00:05:20,357
you don't get a second chance.

61
00:05:22,247 --> 00:05:23,236
Okay.

62
00:05:23,407 --> 00:05:28,800
Prisoner number 96J332,
Arnold Jackson.

63
00:05:29,207 --> 00:05:31,801
Mr. Jackson,
l will ask you questions

64
00:05:31,967 --> 00:05:36,836
based upon your pre-parole summary
and your institutional profile.

65
00:05:37,167 --> 00:05:39,397
After this hearing, l will make
a written recommendation

66
00:05:39,567 --> 00:05:41,125
to the parole commissioner.

67
00:05:41,287 --> 00:05:42,800
Our conversation is being recorded

68
00:05:42,967 --> 00:05:47,040
should you choose to appeal
whatever decision is reached.

69
00:05:47,327 --> 00:05:48,760
Any questions?

70
00:05:50,407 --> 00:05:51,760
No.

71
00:05:53,847 --> 00:05:55,246
Everybody.

72
00:05:55,407 --> 00:05:57,284
Everybody, l've got some good news
for you.

73
00:05:57,447 --> 00:05:59,517
You two are engaged?

74
00:06:00,967 --> 00:06:03,322
The Poet has been granted parole.

75
00:06:04,567 --> 00:06:06,159
- Holy shit.
- Fuck that.

76
00:06:07,407 --> 00:06:08,806
So, what do l do? When?

77
00:06:08,967 --> 00:06:12,642
Well, it's an immediate release,
so that means right after graduation.

78
00:06:13,327 --> 00:06:15,682
This is perfect timing since McManus
and l have chosen

79
00:06:15,847 --> 00:06:18,042
Poet to be the class valedictorian.

80
00:06:18,207 --> 00:06:19,435
Yo, valedic-what?

81
00:06:19,607 --> 00:06:20,881
Congratulations, Poet.

82
00:06:21,927 --> 00:06:26,717
We wanted to share this with you here
in order to encourage you all.

83
00:06:27,967 --> 00:06:31,039
Poet's being rewarded now,
but everybody can be.

84
00:06:31,207 --> 00:06:34,244
So work hard.

85
00:06:35,967 --> 00:06:37,958
All right, guys,
let's get started, huh?.

86
00:06:38,127 --> 00:06:39,845
Who knows what
valedictorian means?

87
00:06:40,367 --> 00:06:42,562
lt'll be good for McManus.

88
00:06:42,727 --> 00:06:47,755
He needs a little education himself.
ln reality.

89
00:06:48,767 --> 00:06:50,644
Hello, Tim.

90
00:06:51,047 --> 00:06:52,036
Governor.

91
00:06:52,567 --> 00:06:54,956
What's this, Leo? Sneak attack?

92
00:06:55,847 --> 00:06:57,439
- Have a seat.
- No, thanks.

93
00:06:58,247 --> 00:07:00,363
What brings you down
from Mount Olympus?

94
00:07:00,967 --> 00:07:04,801
l'll give you three clues: G-E-D.

95
00:07:04,967 --> 00:07:08,004
The state has decided to eliminate the
high school equivalency programme

96
00:07:08,167 --> 00:07:09,566
from the next year's prison budget.

97
00:07:09,727 --> 00:07:11,319
What? You can't do that.

98
00:07:11,487 --> 00:07:13,398
This programme is working.
With time--

99
00:07:13,567 --> 00:07:14,795
Well, we don't have time.

100
00:07:15,887 --> 00:07:19,766
Plain and simple, we need more COs
and the budget can't handle both.

101
00:07:19,927 --> 00:07:21,121
We would need less COs

102
00:07:21,287 --> 00:07:24,006
if there were fewer prisoners,
which is exactly what's happening with

103
00:07:24,167 --> 00:07:25,919
education programmes like ours,
governor.

104
00:07:26,087 --> 00:07:28,647
l'm holding a press conference
on the 1 5th to announce the budget.

105
00:07:28,807 --> 00:07:31,640
Until then, this information
is not to leave the room.

106
00:07:32,487 --> 00:07:36,480
The 1 5th. That's three days
after the students graduate.

107
00:07:36,647 --> 00:07:40,276
l planned it that way,
so the ceremony wouldn't be affected.

108
00:07:40,447 --> 00:07:43,041
Oh, so you're coming
to the graduation ceremony?

109
00:07:43,207 --> 00:07:45,926
Unfortunately, yes.

110
00:07:46,087 --> 00:07:48,157
The wages of spin.

111
00:07:52,367 --> 00:07:54,642
l don't want a big production
or anything.

112
00:07:54,807 --> 00:07:56,479
lt's just gonna distract the inmates.

113
00:07:56,647 --> 00:07:59,764
Well, it's just the cameraman
and myself. That's all.

114
00:07:59,927 --> 00:08:02,600
Local news ain't Hollywood,
at least not yet.

115
00:08:02,767 --> 00:08:04,485
Now, how long will this story
be on the air?

116
00:08:04,647 --> 00:08:06,399
Depends on whatever else
is happening.

117
00:08:06,567 --> 00:08:08,046
Forty-five seconds, three minutes.

118
00:08:08,207 --> 00:08:09,481
l want three minutes.

119
00:08:09,647 --> 00:08:12,207
These men have worked hard,
they deserve the recognition.

120
00:08:12,367 --> 00:08:15,200
l want your viewers to know that
something good's coming out of Oz.

121
00:08:15,367 --> 00:08:18,359
- All right, see you on the 1 2th.
- Okay.

122
00:08:26,087 --> 00:08:28,999
Governor Devlin, Warden Glynn,

123
00:08:29,167 --> 00:08:32,318
graduates, families, friends.

124
00:08:33,007 --> 00:08:36,238
lt is with great pride
that l stand before you now

125
00:08:36,647 --> 00:08:39,480
to mark not only
the academic achievement

126
00:08:39,647 --> 00:08:41,877
of the individuals
we are here to honour,

127
00:08:42,047 --> 00:08:44,117
but also the communal victory

128
00:08:44,287 --> 00:08:47,996
to which every person in this room
has contributed.

129
00:08:48,447 --> 00:08:51,519
These students have taught me
that the GED diploma

130
00:08:51,687 --> 00:08:54,076
is only part of a much larger goal.

131
00:08:54,767 --> 00:08:58,442
To change one's life
and never look back.

132
00:09:01,287 --> 00:09:05,599
So it is with great sorrow
that l tell you,

133
00:09:05,767 --> 00:09:08,327
this could be the last year
of education at Oswald.

134
00:09:09,967 --> 00:09:13,198
ln the new budget that will soon
be considered by our legislature,

135
00:09:13,367 --> 00:09:16,439
the equivalency programme
will be terminated.

136
00:09:16,607 --> 00:09:21,123
This tragic decision won't affect
today's graduates,

137
00:09:21,287 --> 00:09:23,960
but their dedication and hard work
have left a legacy

138
00:09:24,127 --> 00:09:26,880
which inevitably will disappear.

139
00:09:27,567 --> 00:09:31,719
ln the immortal words of Chuck D.:

140
00:09:32,487 --> 00:09:34,796
''Don't believe the hype.''

141
00:09:38,807 --> 00:09:41,799
l'd like to introduce
our class valedictorian,

142
00:09:41,967 --> 00:09:44,959
Arnold ''Poet'' Jackson.

143
00:09:52,567 --> 00:09:55,843
Too many prisons
And not enough schools

144
00:09:56,287 --> 00:09:59,359
Too many weapons
And not enough tools

145
00:09:59,527 --> 00:10:02,837
Not enough teachers
Too many fools

146
00:10:03,327 --> 00:10:07,764
But me
l'm from where fights is born

147
00:10:07,927 --> 00:10:10,157
l'm from where nights is dawned

148
00:10:10,327 --> 00:10:13,319
l'm from the ingredients
Spit from the sun

149
00:10:13,487 --> 00:10:16,684
l formed an allegiance
With the number one

150
00:10:16,847 --> 00:10:19,805
The letter A
The beginning of the day

151
00:10:19,967 --> 00:10:22,037
The way, the wisdom
The wish, the will

152
00:10:22,207 --> 00:10:24,801
The river, the tree, the try, the trek

153
00:10:24,967 --> 00:10:27,003
The rub of the neck

154
00:10:28,247 --> 00:10:31,603
The ball of the foot
The back of the thigh

155
00:10:32,047 --> 00:10:35,801
The glimmer of their eye
Appeared at what it's intrigued by

156
00:10:35,967 --> 00:10:38,720
Tried by what it's believed by

157
00:10:39,127 --> 00:10:41,436
l have taken on the likeness of love

158
00:10:41,607 --> 00:10:44,804
The harbour of hate
The hell of here

159
00:10:44,967 --> 00:10:49,438
And the wonder of the where after
l've discerned the disaster

160
00:10:49,607 --> 00:10:52,883
And drank Dom Pérignon
And Armageddon

161
00:10:53,047 --> 00:10:55,163
l have drank the sacred ambrosia

162
00:10:55,327 --> 00:10:59,206
Housed in the chalice
Of the rebellious cherubim

163
00:10:59,367 --> 00:11:01,722
Disguised as quarter juices

164
00:11:02,167 --> 00:11:08,356
l have died toothless
And been reborn 1 44,000 times

165
00:11:08,527 --> 00:11:11,519
l've got 1 44,000 rhymes

166
00:11:11,687 --> 00:11:14,155
For every brain cell

167
00:11:14,807 --> 00:11:17,275
But l waste away in a cell

168
00:11:17,607 --> 00:11:19,279
Thank you.

169
00:11:28,287 --> 00:11:30,005
Ladies and gentlemen,
l present to you

170
00:11:30,167 --> 00:11:32,476
the graduating class of 1 998.

171
00:11:38,167 --> 00:11:40,203
Luis Battista.

172
00:11:43,327 --> 00:11:45,921
Arnold ''Poet'' Jackson.

173
00:11:47,927 --> 00:11:49,724
Timmy Kirk.

174
00:12:02,047 --> 00:12:03,924
Nice ceremony, huh, governor?

175
00:12:04,087 --> 00:12:06,237
How come you didn't hang around
for the cake and coffee?

176
00:12:06,407 --> 00:12:11,322
McManus, McManus, McManus,
you think you're so goddamn clever.

177
00:12:11,567 --> 00:12:15,196
Bring me here,
embarrass me publicly.

178
00:12:15,367 --> 00:12:18,006
That was pretty much the idea,
yeah.

179
00:12:18,167 --> 00:12:21,000
Oh, you think l'm vulnerable, right?

180
00:12:21,607 --> 00:12:24,917
What with my wife walking out,

181
00:12:25,167 --> 00:12:26,600
all the corruption charges,

182
00:12:26,767 --> 00:12:28,405
not to mention the drop
l took in the polls

183
00:12:28,567 --> 00:12:31,206
after sending in the SWAT team
during the riots.

184
00:12:31,367 --> 00:12:34,439
Saving your ass in the process,
l might add.

185
00:12:35,567 --> 00:12:38,604
You figure l can't take
anymore heat, right?

186
00:12:39,567 --> 00:12:42,001
l'm a simple man with a simple plan.

187
00:12:42,167 --> 00:12:45,364
Yes, but l'm not.

188
00:12:46,167 --> 00:12:50,206
A year ago, my enemies thought
by now l'd be impeached

189
00:12:50,367 --> 00:12:54,804
because, like you,
they underestimate me

190
00:12:55,087 --> 00:12:56,645
and the voters.

191
00:12:56,807 --> 00:13:00,322
See, the voters and l
have a love-hate relationship.

192
00:13:00,487 --> 00:13:03,240
They know l'm a bully,
they suspect l'm dishonest,

193
00:13:03,407 --> 00:13:06,399
they even assume
l cheated on my wife.

194
00:13:06,567 --> 00:13:09,365
But crime is down,

195
00:13:09,927 --> 00:13:11,201
taxes are down.

196
00:13:11,367 --> 00:13:15,155
Employment, however, is up.

197
00:13:15,327 --> 00:13:17,397
Median income is up, up, up.

198
00:13:17,567 --> 00:13:19,364
The Knights made it
into the playoffs.

199
00:13:19,527 --> 00:13:22,758
Even the ballet is thriving,
and as for education,

200
00:13:22,927 --> 00:13:25,805
we now have the second highest
literacy rate in the U.S. of A.

201
00:13:25,967 --> 00:13:29,846
So do you seriously think
that John and Jane Q. Public

202
00:13:30,007 --> 00:13:34,762
give a shit that some drugged-out
homeboy is gonna get a diploma,

203
00:13:34,927 --> 00:13:37,805
knowing that their own little darlings
are going to Yale?

204
00:13:42,847 --> 00:13:45,441
Enjoy that coffee and cake.

205
00:13:49,847 --> 00:13:52,156
You see what l'm saying?
People move the way that they do

206
00:13:52,327 --> 00:13:54,761
because they're still working out
some shit with their fathers.

207
00:13:54,927 --> 00:13:59,205
They're still pissed at their mothers
for not potty-training them properly.

208
00:13:59,367 --> 00:14:00,356
Shit like that.

209
00:14:00,527 --> 00:14:04,315
People wanna get back at their
parents for making them be born.

210
00:14:04,487 --> 00:14:06,239
Bad baby.

211
00:14:11,727 --> 00:14:13,126
Yo, what's up?

212
00:14:13,727 --> 00:14:15,445
What you want, Wangler?

213
00:14:16,487 --> 00:14:17,886
You're leaving today.

214
00:14:18,047 --> 00:14:20,242
Yeah, l'm leaving today.

215
00:14:23,767 --> 00:14:25,405
You want something or not? What?

216
00:14:27,247 --> 00:14:30,080
Yo, man, l heard your poem
at the graduation, man.

217
00:14:30,247 --> 00:14:31,600
l like what you said.

218
00:14:32,327 --> 00:14:33,919
Yeah, yeah.

219
00:14:34,607 --> 00:14:37,440
Yo, Poet, man, l know l been
giving you a lot of shit lately.

220
00:14:37,607 --> 00:14:41,122
You know, calling you a faggot, talking
about your poetry and everything else.

221
00:14:41,287 --> 00:14:42,606
Yeah.

222
00:14:43,527 --> 00:14:45,882
But, yo, you good, man,
you real good.

223
00:14:46,287 --> 00:14:47,959
Thanks, man.

224
00:14:49,127 --> 00:14:51,687
You know, it's kind of--
lt's kind of fucked up, you know,

225
00:14:51,847 --> 00:14:53,803
you not being able to graduate
and all.

226
00:14:53,967 --> 00:14:56,162
Yeah, man, l know.
Fucking McManus.

227
00:14:56,327 --> 00:14:58,045
l had to call my girl and explain.

228
00:14:58,207 --> 00:14:59,481
- Yeah.
- Yeah.

229
00:14:59,647 --> 00:15:01,922
l didn't even have the heart
to call my mom, man.

230
00:15:02,087 --> 00:15:03,679
You know,
she been so proud of me lately,

231
00:15:03,847 --> 00:15:05,724
learning to read and school
and all that shit.

232
00:15:05,887 --> 00:15:07,002
Yeah.

233
00:15:07,167 --> 00:15:10,079
And l broke her heart
so many fucking times.

234
00:15:10,367 --> 00:15:11,959
Yeah.

235
00:15:12,447 --> 00:15:15,484
That's why, yo, l was wondering
if before you jet,

236
00:15:15,647 --> 00:15:18,036
you could write me a letter to her.

237
00:15:18,207 --> 00:15:21,756
You know,
telling her l'm sorry for all this.

238
00:15:21,927 --> 00:15:23,360
Kenny,
you know how to write a letter.

239
00:15:23,527 --> 00:15:24,846
No, no, l mean...

240
00:15:25,007 --> 00:15:26,838
See, you got the words.

241
00:15:27,007 --> 00:15:29,202
l don't-- l don't have the words.

242
00:15:29,367 --> 00:15:31,642
The vocabulary.

243
00:15:32,127 --> 00:15:36,484
Plus, it's a trade.

244
00:15:37,607 --> 00:15:39,165
Yeah.

245
00:15:39,887 --> 00:15:41,445
All right.

246
00:15:57,767 --> 00:15:59,246
You're packed?

247
00:15:59,407 --> 00:16:01,159
No, you know,
l decided l didn't wanna

248
00:16:01,327 --> 00:16:03,477
take anything out of this place,
you know?

249
00:16:03,967 --> 00:16:06,037
So no last meal?

250
00:16:06,847 --> 00:16:11,443
No goodbyes to anybody.
Just, ''See you, have a nice life.''

251
00:16:12,647 --> 00:16:15,207
You know,
it's kind of fucked up, leaving.

252
00:16:15,367 --> 00:16:16,561
A little.

253
00:16:16,767 --> 00:16:19,042
Everybody else is staying.

254
00:16:19,207 --> 00:16:21,641
You know,
it's like waking up from a dream.

255
00:16:22,327 --> 00:16:24,397
Hope is a waking dream.

256
00:16:24,567 --> 00:16:26,159
Who that, Muhammad?

257
00:16:26,327 --> 00:16:27,396
Aristotle.

258
00:16:27,847 --> 00:16:30,520
Well, that fuck ain't never
served no time in Oz.

259
00:16:32,167 --> 00:16:34,886
Poet, your mother's here.

260
00:16:40,447 --> 00:16:42,119
l wanna thank you.

261
00:16:42,967 --> 00:16:44,036
Both.

262
00:16:47,527 --> 00:16:49,882
Salaam Alaikum, brother.

263
00:17:04,807 --> 00:17:06,286
Hey, Shirley.

264
00:17:06,447 --> 00:17:09,280
You know, you're the prettiest girl
on death row.

265
00:17:17,167 --> 00:17:18,395
Hello, Shirley.

266
00:17:18,567 --> 00:17:20,444
Thank you for coming.

267
00:17:20,607 --> 00:17:22,996
lf you hadn't asked,
l would have anyway.

268
00:17:25,847 --> 00:17:29,078
l never was much
for any kind of religion.

269
00:17:29,287 --> 00:17:32,757
l was baptized Lutheran,
went to Quaker school.

270
00:17:32,927 --> 00:17:37,557
My first husband was a Jew,
my second was a whatchadingy.

271
00:17:38,087 --> 00:17:39,076
Whatchadingy?

272
00:17:39,247 --> 00:17:41,522
You know,
when you don't believe in anything?

273
00:17:41,687 --> 00:17:44,326
- An atheist.
- Yeah.

274
00:17:44,487 --> 00:17:45,920
Are you an atheist?

275
00:17:46,087 --> 00:17:48,078
l'm not sure.

276
00:17:48,727 --> 00:17:52,959
Ever since the accident, l've been
full up with all sorts of feelings.

277
00:17:53,407 --> 00:17:54,999
The accident?

278
00:17:56,447 --> 00:17:58,677
When my daughter died.

279
00:18:01,767 --> 00:18:03,678
Save me.

280
00:18:04,967 --> 00:18:08,482
- Do you wanna be saved?
- l want you to save me.

281
00:18:08,647 --> 00:18:10,877
From what? From hell?

282
00:18:11,047 --> 00:18:13,163
From lethal injection?

283
00:18:14,047 --> 00:18:15,446
That collar looks so stiff.

284
00:18:15,607 --> 00:18:17,438
Why don't you take it off?

285
00:18:22,967 --> 00:18:24,241
Stop it.

286
00:18:24,407 --> 00:18:25,760
Officer.

287
00:18:27,127 --> 00:18:28,355
Look at me.

288
00:18:29,407 --> 00:18:32,285
l'm so fucked up.

289
00:18:35,127 --> 00:18:36,765
l'm sorry.

290
00:18:49,687 --> 00:18:53,566
ln Oz, you don't get to see much
of your real family,

291
00:18:53,727 --> 00:18:55,718
your blood relatives.

292
00:18:56,167 --> 00:19:00,001
Sometimes the things you do inside,
you do for them.

293
00:19:00,167 --> 00:19:03,284
To keep them alive,
to keep them around you,

294
00:19:03,447 --> 00:19:05,836
even if only in your head.

295
00:19:15,087 --> 00:19:17,396
Well, look who's here.

296
00:19:17,567 --> 00:19:19,717
What brings you down
to the low-rent district?

297
00:19:19,887 --> 00:19:21,400
Just because you're not
in Em City anymore,

298
00:19:21,567 --> 00:19:23,478
doesn't mean l don't care
what's going on with you.

299
00:19:25,607 --> 00:19:27,757
Bull-fucking-shit.

300
00:19:28,207 --> 00:19:30,198
McManus, l had to listen
to your sanctimonious crap

301
00:19:30,367 --> 00:19:32,244
when l lived in Em City,

302
00:19:32,887 --> 00:19:34,957
but l don't have to now.

303
00:19:35,327 --> 00:19:36,840
Bye.

304
00:19:37,807 --> 00:19:39,604
All right,
l don't care how you're doing.

305
00:19:40,607 --> 00:19:42,757
Hey, boys, honesty.

306
00:19:43,687 --> 00:19:45,803
l wanna talk to you

307
00:19:45,967 --> 00:19:48,117
about your accusation
that Officer Wittlesey

308
00:19:48,287 --> 00:19:50,755
shot Scott Ross during the riot.

309
00:19:51,647 --> 00:19:53,558
Accusation?

310
00:19:54,487 --> 00:19:57,285
l saw Wittlesey kill Ross.

311
00:20:00,367 --> 00:20:01,766
Well,

312
00:20:03,447 --> 00:20:04,800
l want you to tell me everything.

313
00:20:04,967 --> 00:20:06,480
- All the details.
- Why?

314
00:20:07,447 --> 00:20:09,881
You hacks just protect each other.

315
00:20:10,647 --> 00:20:13,320
All you're gonna do is bury the truth.

316
00:20:16,087 --> 00:20:17,520
Not this time.

317
00:20:30,007 --> 00:20:32,123
Tim. Hey.

318
00:20:32,287 --> 00:20:33,879
My daughter's in town.

319
00:20:34,047 --> 00:20:35,958
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.

320
00:20:36,127 --> 00:20:38,846
My mom's in the hospital, so she
hasn't been able to take care of her.

321
00:20:39,007 --> 00:20:40,918
l have this friend Janice who also
has a daughter

322
00:20:41,087 --> 00:20:42,645
and she lives a couple blocks
from here,

323
00:20:42,807 --> 00:20:45,526
so she's been helping me out a couple
days a week watching Deedee.

324
00:20:45,687 --> 00:20:47,166
That's good.

325
00:20:47,967 --> 00:20:49,923
You had said that you wanted
to meet her

326
00:20:50,087 --> 00:20:52,840
and l told her so much about you,

327
00:20:53,007 --> 00:20:55,237
l was wondering if you wanted
to get dinner tonight.

328
00:20:56,007 --> 00:20:58,646
Just the three of us, my treat.

329
00:21:01,607 --> 00:21:02,722
Okay.

330
00:21:04,087 --> 00:21:05,520
Okay.

331
00:21:11,527 --> 00:21:15,918
This goddamn motherfucking
piece of shit.

332
00:21:16,087 --> 00:21:18,123
ls there anything
in this fucking come stain

333
00:21:18,287 --> 00:21:19,561
of a building that works?

334
00:21:19,727 --> 00:21:22,764
Rick, relax.
lt's a soda machine there, pal.

335
00:21:22,927 --> 00:21:24,679
lt-- lt ate my dollar.

336
00:21:24,847 --> 00:21:27,680
Well, there's a number
on the side there you could call.

337
00:21:27,847 --> 00:21:30,315
Well, fuck that.

338
00:21:31,487 --> 00:21:32,602
You feel better?

339
00:21:34,407 --> 00:21:36,079
Yes, much.

340
00:21:36,247 --> 00:21:37,965
Much better.

341
00:21:38,527 --> 00:21:40,438
l can't come to poker tonight.

342
00:21:40,607 --> 00:21:42,006
Fuck. Why?

343
00:21:42,167 --> 00:21:44,601
l promised Diane l would go
have dinner with her and her kid.

344
00:21:45,527 --> 00:21:48,439
Man, you and she.
On again, off again.

345
00:21:49,327 --> 00:21:50,760
We're definitely off again.

346
00:21:50,927 --> 00:21:52,645
How come?

347
00:21:54,647 --> 00:21:56,046
Timmy boy, you have got to be

348
00:21:56,207 --> 00:21:58,767
the most transparent man
on God's green earth.

349
00:21:58,927 --> 00:21:59,962
What?

350
00:22:00,127 --> 00:22:02,322
You started shying away
from her ever since the riot.

351
00:22:02,807 --> 00:22:04,877
Ever since that bitch Case
and his commission

352
00:22:05,047 --> 00:22:06,241
started sniffing around.

353
00:22:06,407 --> 00:22:07,999
No, she came to see me
in the hospital.

354
00:22:08,167 --> 00:22:09,919
She was actually very helpful.

355
00:22:10,087 --> 00:22:12,521
So, what happened?

356
00:22:14,287 --> 00:22:16,403
- Forget it.
- Hey.

357
00:22:16,567 --> 00:22:19,445
Tim, how-- How long we known
each other, huh?

358
00:22:19,607 --> 00:22:21,325
You don't trust me?

359
00:22:26,007 --> 00:22:27,440
All right.

360
00:22:28,207 --> 00:22:32,564
Rick, l read the commission's report
about a hundred times.

361
00:22:32,727 --> 00:22:34,080
l may be nuts,

362
00:22:34,247 --> 00:22:37,205
but l don't think Scott Ross
died the way it says he did.

363
00:22:37,887 --> 00:22:39,161
l think--

364
00:22:40,087 --> 00:22:41,520
l think he was murdered.

365
00:22:41,687 --> 00:22:43,757
- No shit.
- By Diane.

366
00:22:43,927 --> 00:22:45,519
- Tim, come on.
- l know.

367
00:22:45,687 --> 00:22:47,279
- You got proof?
- No.

368
00:22:47,447 --> 00:22:49,677
Only Schillinger's word.
He says he saw her do it.

369
00:22:49,847 --> 00:22:51,565
Fuck Schillinger.

370
00:22:51,727 --> 00:22:53,285
Yeah, well...

371
00:22:54,167 --> 00:22:56,635
When l asked Diane about it,
she lied to me.

372
00:22:56,807 --> 00:22:59,605
- How do you know?
- You sleep with someone, you know.

373
00:23:01,967 --> 00:23:03,525
Gotta go.

374
00:23:12,407 --> 00:23:15,285
Yeah, hey, Joey, is Diane there?

375
00:23:22,487 --> 00:23:24,762
- Diane?
- Yeah.

376
00:23:25,327 --> 00:23:27,716
- Are you ready?
- Just about.

377
00:23:38,167 --> 00:23:39,441
Tim, l gotta be blunt.

378
00:23:40,127 --> 00:23:42,800
l know you have doubts about
what really happened to Scott Ross.

379
00:23:44,327 --> 00:23:47,239
Do you remember the look in his eyes
when he fired that gun at you?

380
00:23:48,727 --> 00:23:50,046
Yeah.

381
00:23:50,207 --> 00:23:52,198
Do you remember anything
of what happened next?

382
00:23:52,367 --> 00:23:53,516
l've tried to. l can't.

383
00:23:53,687 --> 00:23:57,157
l don't remember much myself.
lt all happened so fast.

384
00:24:01,727 --> 00:24:04,685
l do know that l did what l did
because he shot you.

385
00:24:04,847 --> 00:24:06,075
He wanted you dead.

386
00:24:06,247 --> 00:24:08,477
- And that justifies it?
- Yes.

387
00:24:08,647 --> 00:24:10,160
lf l agree with you,

388
00:24:10,327 --> 00:24:14,366
it goes against everything l believe in,
every principle l stand for.

389
00:24:14,527 --> 00:24:16,245
l'm not asking you
to compromise yourself.

390
00:24:16,407 --> 00:24:19,399
l'm just saying we don't all live
in the same world as you.

391
00:24:19,887 --> 00:24:22,162
For most of us,
what has to be done

392
00:24:22,327 --> 00:24:24,079
matters more than
what should be done.

393
00:24:24,247 --> 00:24:25,680
There's your mommy.

394
00:24:25,847 --> 00:24:27,758
Hey, sweetie.

395
00:24:29,967 --> 00:24:31,798
This is Deedee.

396
00:24:34,287 --> 00:24:35,925
You still wanna get dinner?

397
00:24:40,487 --> 00:24:41,966
No.

398
00:24:55,767 --> 00:24:57,758
Hello, Augustus.

399
00:24:58,167 --> 00:25:00,362
Yo, yo, yo-yos.

400
00:25:04,527 --> 00:25:06,119
Now that's what l call dirty.

401
00:25:06,287 --> 00:25:07,561
Clean it up.

402
00:25:09,847 --> 00:25:11,405
Confess, fellas.

403
00:25:13,367 --> 00:25:15,119
- Can you keep a secret?
- Of course he can.

404
00:25:15,287 --> 00:25:16,686
The question is do l want to?

405
00:25:16,847 --> 00:25:18,166
What would you like in return?

406
00:25:18,327 --> 00:25:20,204
- Wash my clothes for a month.
- A week.

407
00:25:20,367 --> 00:25:21,356
- Three.
- Two.

408
00:25:21,527 --> 00:25:22,960
- And a half.
- Done.

409
00:25:24,167 --> 00:25:27,637
- Busmalis and l are digging a tunnel.
- An escape tunnel.

410
00:25:28,887 --> 00:25:31,196
- Sorry.
- When we first got back to Em City,

411
00:25:31,367 --> 00:25:33,927
you said you was gonna dig out.
l thought you was bullshitting.

412
00:25:34,087 --> 00:25:35,725
- l know it sounds crazy.
- No, no.

413
00:25:35,887 --> 00:25:37,400
But it can be done.

414
00:25:37,567 --> 00:25:38,966
We take turns at night.

415
00:25:39,327 --> 00:25:40,999
During the day,
we put the floor tiles back.

416
00:25:41,447 --> 00:25:44,962
And then you get rid of the dirt
by washing the clothes, right?

417
00:25:45,127 --> 00:25:46,879
Yeah, that was Rebadow's idea.

418
00:25:47,047 --> 00:25:48,799
All right.

419
00:25:48,967 --> 00:25:50,320
Would you like to join us?

420
00:25:50,487 --> 00:25:53,604
Me? This hole gonna have
handicap access?

421
00:25:54,247 --> 00:25:57,125
Just-- Your secret's safe with me.

422
00:25:57,287 --> 00:25:59,039
Bottom, middle,
make sure you fold my clothes

423
00:25:59,207 --> 00:26:01,038
when you take them out of the dryer.

424
00:26:12,007 --> 00:26:14,805
Rumour has it
you're planning to kill Adebisi.

425
00:26:15,447 --> 00:26:17,836
- You shouldn't listen to rumours.
- Don't play games with me.

426
00:26:18,007 --> 00:26:21,397
l'm warning you, if anything happens
to Adebisi, l'm coming after you.

427
00:26:21,567 --> 00:26:22,886
Who's playing games?

428
00:26:23,047 --> 00:26:24,844
What, l gotta keep reminding you?
You owe me.

429
00:26:25,047 --> 00:26:26,321
You owe me large.

430
00:26:26,487 --> 00:26:28,398
You think you can hold that
over my head forever?

431
00:26:28,927 --> 00:26:32,476
Forever or for as long
as we're in this fucking zoo together.

432
00:26:33,127 --> 00:26:35,197
You know what l appreciate
about you?

433
00:26:35,367 --> 00:26:37,164
You're a family man.

434
00:26:38,207 --> 00:26:41,597
You like your job,
but you love your family.

435
00:26:42,647 --> 00:26:44,956
Looks like we got nothing
to talk about.

436
00:26:47,527 --> 00:26:49,199
Officer.

437
00:27:12,527 --> 00:27:17,760
Older brothers. Older brothers
get to fuck up first, break in the folks.

438
00:27:20,967 --> 00:27:23,640
What's going on, little brother?

439
00:27:24,087 --> 00:27:25,679
Hey, Mark.

440
00:27:27,087 --> 00:27:28,600
Come.

441
00:27:29,807 --> 00:27:31,240
Sit down.

442
00:27:33,207 --> 00:27:34,276
What?

443
00:27:34,447 --> 00:27:36,915
You got your deep baritone going.

444
00:27:37,087 --> 00:27:40,682
That means some kind of shit
has hit some sort of fan.

445
00:27:49,127 --> 00:27:50,116
lt's Schibetta.

446
00:27:51,847 --> 00:27:53,519
l can't keep protecting you.

447
00:27:53,687 --> 00:27:55,120
What did he say?

448
00:27:55,807 --> 00:27:57,206
Nothing new.

449
00:27:57,367 --> 00:27:59,437
Either he gets what he wants
or you go to jail.

450
00:27:59,607 --> 00:28:02,201
Fucking guinea motherfucker.

451
00:28:02,967 --> 00:28:04,719
He's not to blame.

452
00:28:04,887 --> 00:28:05,876
You are.

453
00:28:06,047 --> 00:28:08,880
- Here we go. The lecture.
- This is not--

454
00:28:09,047 --> 00:28:11,277
l told you, man.
l didn't mean to kill nobody.

455
00:28:11,447 --> 00:28:14,086
l was just trying to make some
fucking money for rent.

456
00:28:23,087 --> 00:28:24,486
What are you doing?

457
00:28:24,647 --> 00:28:26,000
Please, no.

458
00:28:27,007 --> 00:28:28,599
Gisante said shoot, so l shoot.

459
00:28:28,767 --> 00:28:31,520
Look, you fired the gun, period.

460
00:28:32,087 --> 00:28:34,317
Now, Schibetta's boys
are holding on to it for leverage.

461
00:28:38,047 --> 00:28:39,924
- You gotta turn yourself in.
- What?

462
00:28:40,487 --> 00:28:43,604
- You fucking kidding me?
- Look, you have to, Mark.

463
00:28:43,767 --> 00:28:45,359
You killed a man.

464
00:28:45,527 --> 00:28:49,361
You gonna let your own brother burn,
so you can run your prison?

465
00:28:49,527 --> 00:28:51,802
Are you gonna make
your brother pay for your crime?

466
00:28:51,967 --> 00:28:54,003
Now, l am living a lie.

467
00:28:54,487 --> 00:28:56,762
l could get the death penalty.

468
00:28:58,887 --> 00:29:00,445
l keep protecting you,

469
00:29:00,927 --> 00:29:03,361
who knows how far Schibetta
could take this.

470
00:29:03,527 --> 00:29:05,836
How many more people will die?

471
00:29:06,007 --> 00:29:07,360
l'm sorry, Leo.

472
00:29:08,007 --> 00:29:09,725
He said shoot.

473
00:29:09,887 --> 00:29:12,276
Please. Don't do this to me.

474
00:29:13,007 --> 00:29:15,316
You did it to yourself, Mark.

475
00:29:17,527 --> 00:29:19,802
Now, you have to turn yourself in.

476
00:29:20,327 --> 00:29:22,318
l'll go with you if you want.

477
00:29:23,887 --> 00:29:26,242
But you gotta turn yourself in.

478
00:29:33,607 --> 00:29:37,156
Hey. So l spread this rat poison
all over the place.

479
00:29:37,327 --> 00:29:38,646
You should have used the traps.

480
00:29:38,807 --> 00:29:40,957
Now the rats crawl
into the fucking walls to die.

481
00:29:41,127 --> 00:29:42,879
We'll smell the stench
for a fucking week.

482
00:29:43,047 --> 00:29:45,607
Not that you notice
anything smells bad, Adebisi.

483
00:29:46,567 --> 00:29:50,162
Little Nino,
when you say things like that,

484
00:29:50,327 --> 00:29:51,760
it hurts.

485
00:29:51,927 --> 00:29:54,157
l just wanna be friends.

486
00:29:54,327 --> 00:29:55,442
Friends, huh?

487
00:29:55,607 --> 00:29:59,805
Okay, pal of mine, how's about
you go get me a chocolate bar?

488
00:30:00,527 --> 00:30:02,404
My pleasure.

489
00:30:03,527 --> 00:30:05,119
No problem.

490
00:30:05,927 --> 00:30:07,440
Bitch.

491
00:30:10,807 --> 00:30:14,959
Yo, l been thinking about your offer,
about taking out Schibetta.

492
00:30:15,127 --> 00:30:16,719
- So you'll do it?
- No.

493
00:30:16,887 --> 00:30:19,162
But that don't mean
me and you still can't do business.

494
00:30:19,327 --> 00:30:22,478
Listen, l got a little slice of news
for you that might be helpful.

495
00:30:22,647 --> 00:30:24,080
Schibetta has something
on the warden.

496
00:30:24,247 --> 00:30:25,885
l don't know what it is, all right?

497
00:30:26,047 --> 00:30:30,086
But l got a funny feeling the warden
would not mind if the wop took a hit.

498
00:30:30,807 --> 00:30:32,445
l kill him,
they still have to investigate.

499
00:30:32,607 --> 00:30:35,485
No, no, no. What you gotta do
is you gotta slow down Schibetta.

500
00:30:35,647 --> 00:30:38,719
Let Glynn sweep the dirt
underneath the fucking rug.

501
00:30:41,767 --> 00:30:43,598
Hey, Papi.

502
00:30:44,647 --> 00:30:46,285
You and me.

503
00:30:48,927 --> 00:30:50,883
We could tango.

504
00:30:54,207 --> 00:30:56,516
You know,
l been taking dance lessons,

505
00:30:56,687 --> 00:30:58,325
just in case you asked me.

506
00:30:59,727 --> 00:31:00,876
Here, baby.

507
00:31:06,007 --> 00:31:07,440
There you go.

508
00:31:08,127 --> 00:31:10,243
Little more, little more.

509
00:31:12,647 --> 00:31:13,636
What happened?

510
00:31:14,127 --> 00:31:16,721
Schibetta was brought in,
vomiting and pissing blood.

511
00:31:16,887 --> 00:31:18,764
My guess is he was poisoned.

512
00:31:18,927 --> 00:31:20,565
Christ.

513
00:31:25,967 --> 00:31:27,878
l want Adebisi.

514
00:31:28,287 --> 00:31:30,039
l want you to deliver Adebisi to me.

515
00:31:30,207 --> 00:31:32,243
- No.
- No?

516
00:31:32,407 --> 00:31:36,116
No. lf Adebisi did this,
l'll punish him, not you.

517
00:31:36,287 --> 00:31:39,597
- Leo--
- Don't call me Leo.

518
00:31:40,567 --> 00:31:42,717
ls that a threat or a joke?

519
00:31:43,567 --> 00:31:45,478
My brother is turning himself in.

520
00:31:45,647 --> 00:31:49,845
You and l are done, capisce?

521
00:31:53,007 --> 00:31:54,918
Hey, warden,
what brings you to the kitchen?

522
00:31:55,087 --> 00:31:57,920
Schibetta's gone. You guys are out.

523
00:31:58,087 --> 00:31:59,998
With or without Schibetta,
we run the kitchen.

524
00:32:00,167 --> 00:32:03,045
Wrong.
You boys have been reassigned.

525
00:32:03,207 --> 00:32:04,242
The dress factory.

526
00:32:04,407 --> 00:32:07,558
Dress factory, that's bullshit.
We're no dress--

527
00:32:08,887 --> 00:32:10,320
l'll see you real soon.

528
00:32:10,487 --> 00:32:12,876
Make me a dress, bitch.

529
00:32:21,007 --> 00:32:24,079
See? A little poison

530
00:32:24,247 --> 00:32:28,286
and all the rats are gone.

531
00:32:28,727 --> 00:32:32,481
lf l can prove you hurt Schibetta,
you're gone too.

532
00:32:37,167 --> 00:32:38,964
The Jackson Five.

533
00:32:39,127 --> 00:32:40,924
The Kennedy brothers.

534
00:32:41,087 --> 00:32:43,078
The Marx Brothers.

535
00:32:43,247 --> 00:32:46,478
When brothers work together,
amazing shit happens.

536
00:32:49,487 --> 00:32:51,318
When they don't...

537
00:32:52,567 --> 00:32:55,286
...life sucks.

538
00:33:01,407 --> 00:33:03,921
lt's gonna cost you 1 0 bucks
to get in there.

539
00:33:04,367 --> 00:33:05,561
Oh, yeah?

540
00:33:05,967 --> 00:33:07,286
Yeah.

541
00:33:08,687 --> 00:33:11,247
You broke my fucking nose.

542
00:33:14,127 --> 00:33:17,642
All right, you just wait over there.
The doctor will be with you soon.

543
00:33:21,327 --> 00:33:22,476
What are you doing here?

544
00:33:22,647 --> 00:33:24,524
l'm checking my broken nose.

545
00:33:24,687 --> 00:33:26,325
Motherfucker.

546
00:33:26,487 --> 00:33:29,047
- Sorry about that.
- Yeah, right.

547
00:33:29,487 --> 00:33:32,001
Well, l'm getting this baby off.
My arm's finally healed.

548
00:33:32,167 --> 00:33:33,600
What makes you think
l give two shits?

549
00:33:33,767 --> 00:33:35,758
Hey, l said l was sorry
about breaking your nose,

550
00:33:35,927 --> 00:33:37,201
but fighting you had to look real

551
00:33:37,367 --> 00:33:39,835
or Beecher would have guessed
we were in cahoots.

552
00:33:41,327 --> 00:33:42,806
l owe you.

553
00:33:42,967 --> 00:33:46,482
Yeah, well, Schillinger
says we have to work together.

554
00:33:46,647 --> 00:33:49,002
Let me tell you,
after Beecher's dead,

555
00:33:49,167 --> 00:33:50,964
you and me,
we got a score to settle.

556
00:33:51,127 --> 00:33:53,038
Anytime you want,
day or night, baby.

557
00:33:53,207 --> 00:33:55,277
Okay, Keller.

558
00:33:56,127 --> 00:33:58,687
- He's all yours.
- Give me your arm.

559
00:34:05,167 --> 00:34:06,646
So you never wrestled before?

560
00:34:07,087 --> 00:34:09,237
Like, once in high school.

561
00:34:09,407 --> 00:34:12,399
When Arthur Weiner
got his leg broken by Tad Lefkofsky.

562
00:34:12,567 --> 00:34:14,205
l heard that snap, l got up, l got out.

563
00:34:14,567 --> 00:34:15,682
l'll make sure nothing snaps.

564
00:34:15,847 --> 00:34:17,599
Square yourself up,
put your strong leg back.

565
00:34:17,767 --> 00:34:19,962
- Which is my strong leg?
- l don't know, we'll figure out.

566
00:34:20,127 --> 00:34:21,560
Key is to grab
the other guy's waist,

567
00:34:21,727 --> 00:34:25,037
pull him on top of you, then spin him
around so you can pin him, all right?

568
00:34:25,207 --> 00:34:26,435
Let's go.

569
00:34:27,367 --> 00:34:28,595
Let's go.

570
00:34:33,887 --> 00:34:35,115
You grabbed my neck.

571
00:34:35,287 --> 00:34:37,642
Oh, yeah. l forgot to tell you
about that one.

572
00:34:38,167 --> 00:34:41,204
Let's try it again. Slowly.

573
00:34:50,967 --> 00:34:53,037
Hey, that was good.

574
00:34:53,207 --> 00:34:55,277
- You're letting me win.
- No, l'm not.

575
00:34:55,447 --> 00:34:57,244
Yeah, you are. You fucking are.

576
00:34:57,407 --> 00:35:01,286
Well, l'll tell you what.
Next time, l won't.

577
00:35:10,247 --> 00:35:11,999
Come on, let's go again.

578
00:36:00,367 --> 00:36:01,959
You know
this is a stupid-ass game.

579
00:36:02,127 --> 00:36:05,403
Will you just give it a chance?

580
00:36:06,647 --> 00:36:08,558
- You can't do that.
- This is what l'm talking--

581
00:36:08,727 --> 00:36:11,161
- There's too many fucking rules.
- There's no castle in check.

582
00:36:11,327 --> 00:36:12,999
And like wrestling
doesn't have too many?

583
00:36:15,767 --> 00:36:18,440
- That's my move.
- Beecher, l need to talk to you.

584
00:36:19,607 --> 00:36:22,360
- What did you do wrong?
- Nothing.

585
00:36:22,967 --> 00:36:26,164
lf you do something wrong,
you're summoned to McManus' office.

586
00:36:26,607 --> 00:36:30,486
He comes to deliver bad news.
What's up?

587
00:36:30,647 --> 00:36:32,558
You sure you want me
to do this in front of him?

588
00:36:35,527 --> 00:36:36,721
Yeah.

589
00:36:37,327 --> 00:36:40,399
Your wife, she died.

590
00:36:42,047 --> 00:36:43,446
What?

591
00:36:47,647 --> 00:36:50,320
She killed herself.

592
00:36:52,767 --> 00:36:55,076
God almighty.

593
00:36:57,487 --> 00:36:58,806
How?

594
00:36:59,207 --> 00:37:00,606
Asphyxiation. She--

595
00:37:00,767 --> 00:37:06,125
She locked herself in the garage,
she left the car running.

596
00:37:07,167 --> 00:37:08,316
And the kids?

597
00:37:08,487 --> 00:37:10,045
They're fine.

598
00:37:12,407 --> 00:37:13,601
Where are my kids?

599
00:37:13,767 --> 00:37:16,156
- They're with your family.
- l wanna see my kids.

600
00:37:17,047 --> 00:37:19,117
l arranged for a visit tomorrow.

601
00:37:20,647 --> 00:37:22,080
Okay.

602
00:37:22,967 --> 00:37:26,642
Beecher, l'm sorry.

603
00:37:26,807 --> 00:37:28,399
lf there's anything l can do...

604
00:37:30,167 --> 00:37:31,998
Did Genevieve leave a note?

605
00:37:32,167 --> 00:37:33,361
l don't know.

606
00:37:33,527 --> 00:37:36,963
Yeah, well, l bet she left a note.

607
00:37:38,007 --> 00:37:40,077
l'll try to find out.

608
00:37:52,687 --> 00:37:53,722
Wanna play some more chess?

609
00:37:56,567 --> 00:37:58,239
Wanna go wrestle?

610
00:37:59,847 --> 00:38:02,042
Want me to leave you
the fuck alone?

611
00:38:09,007 --> 00:38:11,601
- Oh, man.
- l'm sorry.

612
00:38:12,727 --> 00:38:14,445
l'm sorry.

613
00:38:15,087 --> 00:38:16,566
Look, you wanna cry,
you go ahead, man.

614
00:38:16,727 --> 00:38:18,285
No one's watching.

615
00:38:25,247 --> 00:38:26,236
lt's cool.

616
00:38:34,047 --> 00:38:36,083
Mail call.

617
00:38:42,367 --> 00:38:46,804
Tobias, got something here for you.

618
00:38:48,567 --> 00:38:51,206
Stationary from Cartier.

619
00:38:56,487 --> 00:38:58,842
l heard your wife offed herself.

620
00:39:15,927 --> 00:39:17,963
- What's the matter?
- Sweet Jesus.

621
00:39:19,327 --> 00:39:21,204
lt's from Genevieve.

622
00:39:24,407 --> 00:39:26,398
She says that l did it.

623
00:39:26,887 --> 00:39:29,924
That l killed her
just like that little girl.

624
00:39:35,847 --> 00:39:37,405
Toby.

625
00:39:38,887 --> 00:39:40,400
Where are they?

626
00:39:41,687 --> 00:39:43,723
ln the playroom.

627
00:39:43,967 --> 00:39:46,276
Toby. Toby, wait.

628
00:39:46,447 --> 00:39:48,085
Wait.

629
00:39:49,607 --> 00:39:51,598
What, Grandmother?

630
00:39:55,007 --> 00:39:57,202
They're the ones that found her.

631
00:40:00,687 --> 00:40:02,962
So go slowly.

632
00:40:03,607 --> 00:40:05,563
They haven't seen you
in more than a year,

633
00:40:05,727 --> 00:40:08,036
and then this place...

634
00:40:08,447 --> 00:40:10,961
l'm just not sure
we should have come this soon.

635
00:40:11,647 --> 00:40:13,922
They're still in shock.

636
00:40:16,527 --> 00:40:18,324
You don't want me to see them?

637
00:40:18,487 --> 00:40:21,684
lt's not that. lt's-- No.
Just not this way, not yet.

638
00:40:21,847 --> 00:40:23,519
Not now.

639
00:40:36,727 --> 00:40:38,558
l understand.

640
00:40:40,287 --> 00:40:42,403
Take them home, Grandmother.

641
00:40:44,487 --> 00:40:47,763
- Oh, Toby--
- Get them the fuck out of here.

642
00:41:10,647 --> 00:41:12,444
Beecher, what's the matter?

643
00:41:17,127 --> 00:41:19,687
l-- l fucked up my life.

644
00:41:19,847 --> 00:41:24,159
l have completely fucked up my life.

645
00:41:25,207 --> 00:41:26,799
- l'm all alone.
- No, you're not.

646
00:41:26,967 --> 00:41:29,481
- l'm all alone.
- No, no, you're not.

647
00:41:29,647 --> 00:41:31,205
No, you're not.

648
00:41:31,807 --> 00:41:33,479
lt's all right.

649
00:41:35,367 --> 00:41:37,005
lt's all right.

650
00:41:40,207 --> 00:41:42,675
Don't fucking touch me.

651
00:41:51,767 --> 00:41:55,555
Husbands and wives, man.

652
00:41:56,247 --> 00:41:59,444
We come into this world looking for
unconditional love from our parents.

653
00:41:59,607 --> 00:42:02,804
And when we don't get it,
we find someone,

654
00:42:02,967 --> 00:42:05,879
anyone, and we marry them.

655
00:42:06,087 --> 00:42:07,725
And we spend the rest
of our lives together

656
00:42:07,887 --> 00:42:09,240
beating the shit out of each other,

657
00:42:09,407 --> 00:42:13,844
trying to prove that we didn't deserve
unconditional love in the first place.

658
00:42:14,007 --> 00:42:17,920
ln a marriage, you pay for crimes
you never committed.

659
00:42:18,847 --> 00:42:21,281
- Beyotch.
- What? Motherfucker.

660
00:42:23,727 --> 00:42:25,160
My car just hissed at me.

661
00:42:25,327 --> 00:42:26,806
There's steam coming out
of the engine.

662
00:42:26,967 --> 00:42:29,162
Can you give me a ride
to the rectory?

663
00:42:31,247 --> 00:42:32,805
Pete?

664
00:42:32,967 --> 00:42:35,162
Oh, hi. Hi, Ray.

665
00:42:35,327 --> 00:42:36,476
Oh, you're working. l'm sorry.

666
00:42:36,647 --> 00:42:38,000
No, no, no, come on in.
Come on in.

667
00:42:38,167 --> 00:42:39,759
Maybe you can...

668
00:42:40,127 --> 00:42:43,802
Look, these are the words that
William Giles has been saying to me

669
00:42:43,967 --> 00:42:45,844
over and over and over again.

670
00:42:47,167 --> 00:42:49,044
- What do they mean?
- l don't have a clue.

671
00:42:49,207 --> 00:42:51,118
l've tried everything l can to--

672
00:42:51,287 --> 00:42:53,437
To get him to open up, but...

673
00:42:53,607 --> 00:42:58,158
So l thought
that if l just write them out,

674
00:42:58,327 --> 00:43:01,399
maybe l can see a connection.

675
00:43:01,767 --> 00:43:03,120
- Amore means love.
- Yeah.

676
00:43:03,287 --> 00:43:06,006
- Sick love?
- No, l tried that.

677
00:43:07,087 --> 00:43:11,046
Sick amore. Sick amore.

678
00:43:11,247 --> 00:43:12,919
Sycamore?

679
00:43:15,287 --> 00:43:16,879
Street.

680
00:43:23,847 --> 00:43:26,042
Sycamore Street.

681
00:43:32,087 --> 00:43:34,203
Broome Street.

682
00:43:34,367 --> 00:43:37,359
Sycamore Street. Broome Street.

683
00:43:37,527 --> 00:43:39,597
Sycamore and Broome.

684
00:43:40,247 --> 00:43:42,477
What the hell happened
on Sycamore and Broome?

685
00:43:42,927 --> 00:43:45,487
That's the corner where
my husband was killed.

686
00:43:49,007 --> 00:43:50,122
Open Giles' cell.

687
00:43:50,287 --> 00:43:52,005
- Sister, l can't do that.
- Open it.

688
00:43:52,167 --> 00:43:54,362
Warden Glynn gave me instructions
not to let you in

689
00:43:54,527 --> 00:43:56,916
- unless Giles is manacled--
- l don't have time to wait.

690
00:43:57,087 --> 00:44:00,557
- Sister, l--
- Listen to the sound of my voice.

691
00:44:00,727 --> 00:44:02,638
Let me in.

692
00:44:13,967 --> 00:44:15,923
Did-- Did you murder my husband?

693
00:44:16,087 --> 00:44:18,601
ls that what you've been
trying to tell me?

694
00:44:19,567 --> 00:44:22,877
- ls this confession by Morse code?
- No.

695
00:44:23,407 --> 00:44:24,601
No.

696
00:44:24,767 --> 00:44:26,280
Then, what?

697
00:44:26,807 --> 00:44:28,126
What?

698
00:44:28,287 --> 00:44:29,845
Peter. Peter Marie--

699
00:44:30,007 --> 00:44:32,521
Oh, no, please. Please don't start
that stuff with me again.

700
00:44:32,687 --> 00:44:34,405
Just-- Look.

701
00:44:34,567 --> 00:44:38,355
My husband died on the corner
of Sycamore and Broome, right?

702
00:44:38,967 --> 00:44:42,164
Somebody pushed him off
the back of a truck.

703
00:44:43,927 --> 00:44:45,519
Did you do it?

704
00:44:46,807 --> 00:44:48,240
No.

705
00:44:51,927 --> 00:44:54,885
- Eyes.
- Eyes.

706
00:44:56,407 --> 00:44:58,682
You saw Leonard get pushed.

707
00:45:01,487 --> 00:45:04,240
Right. So-- So--
So, what happened?

708
00:45:05,367 --> 00:45:08,086
Pop. Crackle.

709
00:45:09,567 --> 00:45:10,966
Snap.

710
00:45:11,527 --> 00:45:14,121
Yeah. Yes, his neck was broken.

711
00:45:14,287 --> 00:45:16,676
But what happened before that?

712
00:45:16,847 --> 00:45:17,882
Who pushed him?

713
00:45:19,167 --> 00:45:21,920
Please, please, please.

714
00:45:22,087 --> 00:45:24,681
William, who pushed him?

715
00:45:24,847 --> 00:45:26,200
Aim.

716
00:45:26,367 --> 00:45:28,005
- Aim. What do you mean by aim?
- Aim.

717
00:45:28,167 --> 00:45:29,361
- What is aim?
- Aim.

718
00:45:29,527 --> 00:45:31,916
- Tell me.
- Aim! Aim, aim!

719
00:45:32,087 --> 00:45:34,237
Aim! Aim!

720
00:45:34,407 --> 00:45:36,079
Aim!

721
00:45:36,247 --> 00:45:39,319
Aim! Aim!

722
00:45:40,407 --> 00:45:42,762
Because we share
the same blood with our family,

723
00:45:42,927 --> 00:45:44,918
we can ask them to do anything.

724
00:45:45,087 --> 00:45:48,397
Anything. Lie, cheat, take a bullet.

725
00:45:48,567 --> 00:45:50,285
Only, don't ask to borrow
the new Lexus

726
00:45:50,447 --> 00:45:53,007
because then, my man,
you are crossing the line.

727
00:45:58,607 --> 00:46:00,120
O'Reily.

728
00:46:00,927 --> 00:46:02,280
Did you get it?

729
00:46:02,447 --> 00:46:04,005
Nice.

730
00:46:04,767 --> 00:46:06,758
Let me see the benny first.

731
00:46:07,927 --> 00:46:09,326
Here.

732
00:46:11,287 --> 00:46:15,485
You know, l can understand paying
this type of money for tits, but for that?

733
00:46:15,647 --> 00:46:18,605
Hey, what the fuck kind of scam
you up to?

734
00:46:18,767 --> 00:46:21,839
- No scam.
- So why you have me steal it?

735
00:46:22,007 --> 00:46:23,520
Because it's hers.

736
00:46:23,687 --> 00:46:26,645
- Yeah, it's Nathan's, right?
- Yeah.

737
00:46:27,767 --> 00:46:29,200
- Okay.
- What?

738
00:46:29,687 --> 00:46:33,726
lf l didn't know better,
l'd say you're in love.

739
00:46:34,647 --> 00:46:36,638
What, is that so hard
to believe, huh?

740
00:46:36,807 --> 00:46:38,559
Me in love?

741
00:46:38,727 --> 00:46:41,525
You, me, anybody.

742
00:46:41,687 --> 00:46:43,757
Not in Oz, man.

743
00:46:45,527 --> 00:46:47,199
You're wrong.

744
00:46:51,567 --> 00:46:54,764
- Dr. Nathan.
- Hi.

745
00:46:54,927 --> 00:46:56,565
What do you want?

746
00:46:57,727 --> 00:47:01,356
l was wondering why you weren't
there for my latest dose of chemo.

747
00:47:01,527 --> 00:47:05,202
No, l don't need to be there. The nurse
is qualified to do the procedure.

748
00:47:06,527 --> 00:47:07,642
Look, this--

749
00:47:07,807 --> 00:47:11,117
This chemo's making me pretty sick

750
00:47:11,287 --> 00:47:13,005
and l think l need a check-up.

751
00:47:13,167 --> 00:47:16,557
Fine. l'll arrange for Dr. Prestopnik
to see you this afternoon.

752
00:47:16,727 --> 00:47:18,046
No, but l--

753
00:47:18,207 --> 00:47:20,084
l want you to take care of me.

754
00:47:20,247 --> 00:47:22,283
- l'm busy.
- Doing what?

755
00:47:22,447 --> 00:47:24,244
That's not your business.
l'm hanging up.

756
00:47:24,407 --> 00:47:26,159
No, no, no. Don't get angry.

757
00:47:26,327 --> 00:47:29,364
l'm not. You--
You gotta stop calling me all the time.

758
00:47:29,527 --> 00:47:31,802
- Okay.
- l'm hanging up.

759
00:47:31,967 --> 00:47:33,958
Hold on a second.

760
00:47:37,567 --> 00:47:39,285
l love you.

761
00:47:40,447 --> 00:47:42,005
Hello?

762
00:47:42,167 --> 00:47:43,919
- Hello? Hello, hello, hello?
- Goodbye.

763
00:47:51,007 --> 00:47:53,202
What was that all about?

764
00:47:54,887 --> 00:47:56,206
Ryan O'Reily.

765
00:47:56,927 --> 00:47:59,600
He calls me 1 0 times a day.

766
00:48:00,887 --> 00:48:03,720
- He writes me letters.
- Love letters?

767
00:48:06,287 --> 00:48:07,959
He's starting to creep me out.

768
00:48:08,487 --> 00:48:10,000
Gloria, you haven't--

769
00:48:10,167 --> 00:48:12,078
You haven't been encouraging him,
have you?

770
00:48:12,247 --> 00:48:14,397
- No.
- Okay, okay.

771
00:48:14,567 --> 00:48:16,159
l'm just asking,
because a few weeks ago,

772
00:48:16,327 --> 00:48:18,795
you said that
you were attracted to him.

773
00:48:18,967 --> 00:48:21,845
l know, but l didn't do anything.

774
00:48:22,007 --> 00:48:24,885
l didn't say anything.
l was just being a good doctor.

775
00:48:26,327 --> 00:48:27,919
l swear.

776
00:48:30,007 --> 00:48:31,565
You want me
to have a chat with him?

777
00:48:32,407 --> 00:48:34,045
lf you think it'll help.

778
00:48:34,207 --> 00:48:35,799
Can't hurt.

779
00:48:37,447 --> 00:48:39,403
Mind if l read these?

780
00:48:44,727 --> 00:48:46,319
Hey, Ryan, come on in.
Sit down.

781
00:48:51,127 --> 00:48:53,322
So how are you feeling?

782
00:48:54,007 --> 00:48:55,963
Some days are better than others.

783
00:48:56,127 --> 00:48:58,004
Well, l'm not surprised.

784
00:48:58,167 --> 00:49:00,442
What you've been through
these last few weeks,

785
00:49:00,607 --> 00:49:02,598
breast cancer, surgery, chemo,

786
00:49:03,327 --> 00:49:05,443
these things are difficult to adjust to.

787
00:49:05,607 --> 00:49:07,120
l manage.

788
00:49:07,287 --> 00:49:09,357
What l mean is,

789
00:49:09,527 --> 00:49:13,122
your life was in danger
just a short time ago, and now,

790
00:49:13,287 --> 00:49:16,245
your chances for recovery
are excellent.

791
00:49:16,767 --> 00:49:19,918
So that all the fear
that you experienced

792
00:49:20,087 --> 00:49:22,726
has to be replaced
by something else.

793
00:49:22,887 --> 00:49:26,163
You know, other emotions.

794
00:49:26,567 --> 00:49:29,081
Like your feelings for Dr. Nathan.

795
00:49:30,207 --> 00:49:33,643
You seem to have been
focusing a lot on her lately.

796
00:49:33,807 --> 00:49:35,126
She saved my fucking life.

797
00:49:35,287 --> 00:49:36,845
Well, sure, of course,

798
00:49:37,007 --> 00:49:41,842
but it's very easy to mistake
appreciation for affection.

799
00:49:42,007 --> 00:49:43,645
You're saying what l'm feeling
isn't real?

800
00:49:43,807 --> 00:49:46,765
Oh, no, no, no. l'm sure it is for you.

801
00:49:46,927 --> 00:49:50,761
But for Dr. Nathan, it's--

802
00:49:50,927 --> 00:49:53,202
Well,
she has a different perspective.

803
00:49:54,127 --> 00:49:58,803
And if you care for her, Ryan,

804
00:49:59,327 --> 00:50:02,444
you have to respect that.

805
00:50:03,127 --> 00:50:07,120
You should stop writing, stop calling.

806
00:50:11,847 --> 00:50:16,079
Sometimes l just need
to hear her voice.

807
00:50:16,727 --> 00:50:19,799
Yeah, l understand.

808
00:50:20,327 --> 00:50:24,878
But she doesn't wanna hear yours.

809
00:50:27,007 --> 00:50:32,081
Ryan, love, true love, is reciprocal.

810
00:50:32,447 --> 00:50:35,166
Both people have to care
for each other equally,

811
00:50:35,327 --> 00:50:38,080
and when half that equation
is missing--

812
00:50:38,247 --> 00:50:41,876
Listen to me,
when half that equation is missing,

813
00:50:42,047 --> 00:50:43,639
it's no longer love.

814
00:50:43,807 --> 00:50:46,719
- lt's obsession.
- No, no, you're wrong.

815
00:50:48,407 --> 00:50:51,399
What l feel for her is--

816
00:50:51,567 --> 00:50:55,446
ls the truest, best thing

817
00:50:55,607 --> 00:50:59,919
l have ever had
in my whole fucking life.

818
00:51:02,167 --> 00:51:04,727
And you're not gonna
take it away from me.

819
00:51:04,887 --> 00:51:07,560
- That was not--
- What, is she too good for me?

820
00:51:07,727 --> 00:51:09,126
No, you know what?

821
00:51:10,567 --> 00:51:12,478
You tell her this.

822
00:51:13,047 --> 00:51:15,277
l love her.

823
00:51:15,727 --> 00:51:18,161
She can send me
to a thousand shrinks,

824
00:51:18,327 --> 00:51:21,205
she can drop me
into the hole for a million years

825
00:51:21,367 --> 00:51:24,996
and there's nothing she can do to
ever change the way l feel about her.

826
00:51:25,167 --> 00:51:26,600
Got it?

827
00:51:27,927 --> 00:51:29,565
Thanks.

828
00:51:30,767 --> 00:51:32,200
You dated her, didn't you?

829
00:51:32,367 --> 00:51:33,959
She's married, O'Reily. So are you.

830
00:51:34,127 --> 00:51:35,276
Did you fuck her, huh?

831
00:51:35,447 --> 00:51:37,039
Did you fuck her, McManus?
Was she good?

832
00:51:37,207 --> 00:51:39,437
- You have got to stop.
- l can't.

833
00:51:49,167 --> 00:51:51,601
You gotta do this for me, Cyril.

834
00:51:52,207 --> 00:51:53,845
But it's bad.

835
00:51:54,007 --> 00:51:58,558
And you told me
not to be bad anymore.

836
00:51:58,807 --> 00:52:00,365
Do this.

837
00:52:01,167 --> 00:52:02,486
One time.

838
00:52:02,647 --> 00:52:04,080
For me.

839
00:52:06,087 --> 00:52:08,806
- Okay.
- Okay.

840
00:52:10,927 --> 00:52:12,406
l love you, bro.

841
00:52:12,567 --> 00:52:14,319
l love you too.

842
00:52:19,767 --> 00:52:22,327
Hey. You wanted to see me?

843
00:52:22,487 --> 00:52:24,842
Yes. Have a seat.

844
00:52:28,887 --> 00:52:30,878
We just got word
from the state police.

845
00:52:31,047 --> 00:52:34,642
They found a body
and they think it's your husband's.

846
00:52:37,847 --> 00:52:39,439
My husband?

847
00:52:40,087 --> 00:52:41,759
He was murdered.

848
00:52:45,567 --> 00:52:47,603
Oh, my God.

849
00:52:48,487 --> 00:52:50,557
Oh, my God.

850
00:52:50,887 --> 00:52:52,878
Oh, my God.

851
00:52:55,007 --> 00:52:56,884
Oh, my God.

852
00:53:00,887 --> 00:53:03,003
Oh, my God.

853
00:53:03,607 --> 00:53:05,962
Oh, my God.

854
00:53:06,407 --> 00:53:08,363
Every once in a while,
l remember something l did

855
00:53:08,527 --> 00:53:10,324
when l was a child.

856
00:53:10,487 --> 00:53:12,557
Or something that was done to me,

857
00:53:12,727 --> 00:53:16,276
by my father or my brother
or a cousin.

858
00:53:16,447 --> 00:53:19,598
Some injury, some humiliation.

859
00:53:20,007 --> 00:53:21,679
And it seems like

860
00:53:21,847 --> 00:53:25,123
it happened to another person
a century or two ago.

861
00:53:25,287 --> 00:53:29,200
l'm not really sure if what l remember
really took place at all.

862
00:53:29,567 --> 00:53:34,800
You can't build your life relying
on the perception of a little boy,

863
00:53:34,967 --> 00:53:38,323
on the echoes of some memory. No.

864
00:53:38,647 --> 00:53:42,276
You got to let all that shit go.

865
00:53:42,527 --> 00:53:45,678
You got to start fresh.

866
00:53:50,007 --> 00:53:52,840
Every single day,

867
00:53:53,007 --> 00:53:57,364
you have got to start again.

