1
00:01:41,287 --> 00:01:45,075
''You made your bed, now lie in it.''

2
00:01:45,247 --> 00:01:47,317
Anybody tell me
what the fuck that means?

3
00:01:47,487 --> 00:01:49,762
You don't go to the trouble
of making your bed,

4
00:01:49,927 --> 00:01:52,316
smoothing out the sheets,
fluffing up the pillows,

5
00:01:52,487 --> 00:01:54,717
just to ruin it all by lying down.

6
00:01:54,887 --> 00:01:59,085
The phrase should be,
''You laid in your bed, now make it.''

7
00:01:59,247 --> 00:02:03,399
The point being, you got to be
responsible for your actions.

8
00:02:07,327 --> 00:02:09,602
Responsible.

9
00:02:33,767 --> 00:02:36,998
Kareem, you know
we never doubt your wisdom.

10
00:02:37,167 --> 00:02:38,395
You're the boss, Vern.

11
00:02:38,567 --> 00:02:39,841
Why are you talking to that Nazi?

12
00:02:40,007 --> 00:02:41,122
That nigger?

13
00:02:41,287 --> 00:02:44,723
Like it or not,
that man is a child of God.

14
00:02:45,407 --> 00:02:46,840
Now, l have made
a commitment to Allah

15
00:02:47,007 --> 00:02:50,158
to defend the rights
of all prisoners inside of Oz.

16
00:02:50,887 --> 00:02:52,923
Not just the ones of colour.

17
00:02:53,087 --> 00:02:54,839
Not just the ones
who believe what we believe

18
00:02:55,007 --> 00:02:56,520
or who pray as we pray.

19
00:02:57,967 --> 00:03:00,481
That nigger's
gonna get me out of here.

20
00:03:01,167 --> 00:03:04,239
Said is representing
Vern Schillinger?

21
00:03:04,807 --> 00:03:06,718
Didn't Nostradamus predict this?

22
00:03:06,887 --> 00:03:08,684
Doesn't this mean
we're two steps closer

23
00:03:08,847 --> 00:03:10,838
to the end of the fucking world, here?

24
00:03:11,647 --> 00:03:13,558
You faced Said in Hill's hearing,
didn't you, Pat?

25
00:03:13,727 --> 00:03:16,685
Yeah, and l won.
But this is gonna be a jury trial.

26
00:03:16,847 --> 00:03:20,886
Said's a powerful speaker.
He could move those jurors.

27
00:03:21,047 --> 00:03:22,196
So, what happens next?

28
00:03:22,367 --> 00:03:24,437
You and Tim
have to give another deposition.

29
00:03:24,607 --> 00:03:26,199
- Great.
- All right, he'll wanna know

30
00:03:26,367 --> 00:03:28,676
how you set up
and trapped Schillinger,

31
00:03:28,847 --> 00:03:30,997
and Hill's also gonna bring up
Scott Ross.

32
00:03:31,167 --> 00:03:33,442
So be ready.

33
00:03:38,007 --> 00:03:38,962
That doesn't worry you?

34
00:03:39,127 --> 00:03:40,640
That we're gonna be questioned
about Ross?

35
00:03:40,807 --> 00:03:41,876
No, why should it?

36
00:03:42,047 --> 00:03:45,756
Diane, the last time l was asked
if l knew anything about the shooting,

37
00:03:45,927 --> 00:03:47,997
- l said no.
- Yeah?

38
00:03:48,167 --> 00:03:50,158
- Well, this time l can't.
- Why not?

39
00:03:50,327 --> 00:03:52,887
- Because now l know the truth.
- So?

40
00:03:53,047 --> 00:03:55,880
- l'll be under oath.
- So?

41
00:03:56,047 --> 00:03:57,480
You want me to perjure myself?

42
00:03:57,647 --> 00:04:00,115
Tim, what l want and what you do
are usually not even close.

43
00:04:00,287 --> 00:04:03,324
- l just--
- Look, wait, can we just cut the shit?

44
00:04:03,487 --> 00:04:05,842
You are gonna say
you have a conscience, right?

45
00:04:06,007 --> 00:04:07,645
A moral code.

46
00:04:07,807 --> 00:04:11,880
Seepage in your cerebral cortex.
And l am gonna say lie.

47
00:04:13,007 --> 00:04:18,286
lf you love me,
if you ever loved me, then lie.

48
00:04:21,047 --> 00:04:24,244
Schillinger approached me
outside the library.

49
00:04:24,407 --> 00:04:27,479
He told me he would pay me
to kill Beecher.

50
00:04:27,647 --> 00:04:31,083
- And you agreed?
- Yes.

51
00:04:31,247 --> 00:04:33,238
ln order to stop him.

52
00:04:35,807 --> 00:04:38,799
We have a tape recording
of you and Vern Schillinger.

53
00:04:40,287 --> 00:04:42,243
So last night...

54
00:04:43,967 --> 00:04:46,800
- You wanted Beecher dead, right?
- Yeah, l wanted him dead.

55
00:04:46,967 --> 00:04:47,956
You're paying me, right?

56
00:04:48,127 --> 00:04:49,765
- Two grand?
- Yeah.

57
00:04:51,007 --> 00:04:52,998
This was your second conversation
about Beecher.

58
00:04:53,887 --> 00:04:55,639
Yes.

59
00:04:56,967 --> 00:04:59,242
We don't have a recording
of the first one.

60
00:04:59,407 --> 00:05:02,126
lsn't it true that that time
you approached Schillinger?

61
00:05:03,087 --> 00:05:04,361
No.

62
00:05:04,527 --> 00:05:07,166
You never asked him how much
he'd pay you to kill Tobias Beecher?

63
00:05:07,607 --> 00:05:11,043
No, that would be entrapment,
and against the law.

64
00:05:11,767 --> 00:05:15,442
You say he offered to pay you money.
Did he offer you anything else?

65
00:05:17,647 --> 00:05:22,846
He implied that if l didn't help him,
he would tell people l killed Scott Ross.

66
00:05:23,287 --> 00:05:25,198
Did that factor into your decision
to trick him?

67
00:05:25,847 --> 00:05:28,759
No, because it's not true.

68
00:05:29,967 --> 00:05:31,958
No matter what Schillinger says

69
00:05:32,127 --> 00:05:36,439
or thinks he saw, l killed no one.

70
00:05:38,447 --> 00:05:42,326
So Officer Wittlesey is, in general,
a trustworthy person?

71
00:05:42,847 --> 00:05:44,121
Yes.

72
00:05:44,287 --> 00:05:45,879
She's never lied to you?

73
00:05:47,327 --> 00:05:50,603
- l didn't say that.
- So she has lied to you?

74
00:05:52,927 --> 00:05:54,599
Did she lie to you
regarding Vern Schillinger?

75
00:05:54,887 --> 00:05:56,957
You mean him
wanting to kill Beecher?

76
00:05:57,127 --> 00:05:59,641
- Yes.
- No.

77
00:05:59,807 --> 00:06:00,922
She told you the absolute truth

78
00:06:01,087 --> 00:06:02,566
about her reasons
for accepting his offer?

79
00:06:02,727 --> 00:06:05,036
- l assume so.
- You assume so?

80
00:06:05,207 --> 00:06:06,322
Yes.

81
00:06:06,487 --> 00:06:07,522
So was one of those reasons

82
00:06:07,687 --> 00:06:09,962
the fact that Schillinger knew
Wittlesey murdered Ross?

83
00:06:10,567 --> 00:06:14,116
You mean did she say to me
that was one of her reasons?

84
00:06:14,287 --> 00:06:16,801
- Yes.
- No.

85
00:06:19,287 --> 00:06:23,360
McManus,
did Wittlesey murder Ross?

86
00:06:24,287 --> 00:06:25,276
Murder?

87
00:06:25,447 --> 00:06:26,402
Yes.

88
00:06:26,567 --> 00:06:28,125
To the best of your knowledge,

89
00:06:28,287 --> 00:06:32,883
did Diane Wittlesey shoot Scott Ross
with the intention of ending his life?

90
00:06:38,367 --> 00:06:39,800
No.

91
00:06:53,447 --> 00:06:55,005
Well?

92
00:07:00,967 --> 00:07:02,082
You don't have a case.

93
00:07:02,247 --> 00:07:04,442
Will you turn that down?

94
00:07:04,607 --> 00:07:07,724
They have evidence, witnesses,
and the tape recording.

95
00:07:07,887 --> 00:07:10,959
There's gotta be some legal loophole,
some technicality.

96
00:07:11,127 --> 00:07:14,039
You will be convicted
of conspiracy to commit murder,

97
00:07:14,207 --> 00:07:16,323
and you will be sentenced
to 1 0 more years.

98
00:07:16,487 --> 00:07:20,765
Fuck, it might as well be life.
l'll never see my kids.

99
00:07:21,527 --> 00:07:22,926
Come on,
there's gotta be some way out.

100
00:07:23,087 --> 00:07:25,555
- What about Wittlesey killing Ross?
- Your word against theirs.

101
00:07:25,727 --> 00:07:27,319
And without proof,
your word is meaningless.

102
00:07:27,487 --> 00:07:28,602
They got you, baby.

103
00:07:28,767 --> 00:07:30,405
Will you mind
your own goddamn business?

104
00:07:30,567 --> 00:07:33,957
Schillinger, l'm withdrawing
from your case.

105
00:07:34,127 --> 00:07:35,082
No, you are not.

106
00:07:35,247 --> 00:07:37,681
You pull out,
that only compounds my guilt.

107
00:07:37,847 --> 00:07:40,520
l will not fight your lost battle.

108
00:07:42,167 --> 00:07:44,317
You did this on purpose.

109
00:07:44,487 --> 00:07:46,284
Didn't you? To set me up.

110
00:07:46,447 --> 00:07:49,439
You agreed to be my lawyer
knowing you were gonna pull out,

111
00:07:49,607 --> 00:07:53,122
- knowing that'd make things worse.
- Things couldn't be worse.

112
00:07:53,287 --> 00:07:55,847
l wasn't sure before,
but now l know.

113
00:07:56,287 --> 00:07:57,561
You are guilty.

114
00:07:58,127 --> 00:08:00,004
Truly guilty.

115
00:08:01,687 --> 00:08:04,759
- You used me.
- And you used me.

116
00:08:04,927 --> 00:08:08,397
- Life is balance.
- You fucking nigger.

117
00:08:11,847 --> 00:08:14,441
You just lost the balance, baby.

118
00:08:15,007 --> 00:08:17,282
Billy Shakespeare,
in his last will and testament,

119
00:08:17,447 --> 00:08:23,158
left his wife, Anne Hathaway,
his, quote, ''second-best bed.''

120
00:08:24,287 --> 00:08:27,643
Now, Shakespeare had abandoned
Anne and the kids years before,

121
00:08:27,807 --> 00:08:29,559
and had only come back
home to Stratford

122
00:08:29,727 --> 00:08:31,718
when his bones had started to creak.

123
00:08:32,447 --> 00:08:37,521
Was the second-best bed
a joke between a husband and wife?

124
00:08:37,687 --> 00:08:40,326
Or was it Shakespeare's
ultimate ''fuck you''?

125
00:08:45,767 --> 00:08:47,519
Hello.

126
00:08:48,447 --> 00:08:50,642
- Did you need something?
- No.

127
00:08:50,807 --> 00:08:52,604
Oh, l do.

128
00:08:52,767 --> 00:08:54,837
l need a friend.

129
00:08:55,167 --> 00:08:57,727
- That ain't gonna be me.
- Of course.

130
00:08:58,167 --> 00:09:01,159
l'm a convicted murderer. You're not.

131
00:09:02,927 --> 00:09:04,963
Let me ask you something.

132
00:09:06,247 --> 00:09:07,396
Do you sleep at night?

133
00:09:08,327 --> 00:09:11,319
- Yes.
- How is that possible,

134
00:09:11,487 --> 00:09:13,717
given what you did,
that you sleep through the night?

135
00:09:15,087 --> 00:09:17,965
When people ask me
about my daughter's death,

136
00:09:18,127 --> 00:09:20,163
l tell them it was an accident.

137
00:09:20,767 --> 00:09:24,885
But it wasn't an accident.
lt was what had to happen.

138
00:09:25,047 --> 00:09:27,845
lt was what had to be.

139
00:09:28,007 --> 00:09:29,156
And so l sleep.

140
00:09:30,167 --> 00:09:31,486
l sleep good.

141
00:09:39,207 --> 00:09:41,118
Hey, Diane.

142
00:09:43,687 --> 00:09:44,961
Hey.

143
00:09:46,367 --> 00:09:48,085
Here, Shirley.

144
00:09:49,367 --> 00:09:51,517
Thanks, sweetie.

145
00:10:58,247 --> 00:11:00,477
Peter Schibetta
was definitely poisoned.

146
00:11:00,647 --> 00:11:03,161
He's getting out of the hospital ward
sometime today.

147
00:11:03,327 --> 00:11:05,238
- Test results come back from the lab?
- Yeah.

148
00:11:05,407 --> 00:11:07,523
Same poison used on the rats
in the cafeteria

149
00:11:07,687 --> 00:11:09,564
was found in his digestive system.

150
00:11:09,727 --> 00:11:11,001
What did he eat?

151
00:11:11,167 --> 00:11:15,126
He says immediately before he got sick
he was eating a chocolate bar

152
00:11:15,287 --> 00:11:16,686
that had been given to him
by Adebisi.

153
00:11:16,847 --> 00:11:18,519
l mean, it's pretty clear
that Adebisi did it.

154
00:11:19,007 --> 00:11:20,520
Why is it so clear?

155
00:11:20,687 --> 00:11:21,722
Anybody could have poisoned

156
00:11:21,887 --> 00:11:23,718
the bar before Adebisi
took it out of the box.

157
00:11:23,887 --> 00:11:27,641
Everybody knows that Adebisi
has a problem with Schibetta.

158
00:11:27,807 --> 00:11:29,399
A problem is circumstantial.

159
00:11:29,567 --> 00:11:32,081
A lot of people work in the kitchen,
a lot of people hate Schibetta.

160
00:11:32,247 --> 00:11:33,726
All right, all right.

161
00:11:33,887 --> 00:11:35,798
Lenny, keep investigating.

162
00:11:36,287 --> 00:11:39,723
You get any solid evidence that Adebisi
was involved, we'll deal with him.

163
00:11:39,887 --> 00:11:40,842
And if not?

164
00:11:41,007 --> 00:11:43,965
Then this one goes
in the unsolved-mysteries file.

165
00:11:51,487 --> 00:11:53,079
Hey.

166
00:11:55,167 --> 00:11:56,486
What do you want?

167
00:11:57,007 --> 00:11:59,316
To tell you that Glynn ain't doing dick
about what happened.

168
00:12:00,127 --> 00:12:01,719
That's fine. l'll take care of it myself.

169
00:12:01,887 --> 00:12:03,400
How?

170
00:12:04,407 --> 00:12:06,318
Wait and see.

171
00:12:06,487 --> 00:12:07,966
Peter...

172
00:12:12,847 --> 00:12:15,042
...the family is embarrassed.

173
00:12:16,447 --> 00:12:17,721
They got no reason
to be embarrassed.

174
00:12:17,887 --> 00:12:20,447
They're unhappy with the way
that you're running things in here.

175
00:12:21,167 --> 00:12:23,158
They blame me
for getting poisoned?

176
00:12:23,327 --> 00:12:26,319
Your father got fed ground glass
over the course of months.

177
00:12:26,487 --> 00:12:29,399
Now, whoever did that,
probably Adebisi,

178
00:12:29,567 --> 00:12:32,320
took the time because they knew
that Nino was watching.

179
00:12:32,487 --> 00:12:34,364
Nino was smart.

180
00:12:35,527 --> 00:12:38,360
And so because l got
one quick shot of poison

181
00:12:38,527 --> 00:12:41,041
instead of ground glass,
l'm not as good as Pop, right?

182
00:12:42,007 --> 00:12:44,965
This is what they say. The family.

183
00:12:46,207 --> 00:12:47,959
Christ.

184
00:12:48,127 --> 00:12:50,687
You tell them
l'm gonna handle Adebisi.

185
00:12:50,847 --> 00:12:52,724
l'm gonna get my honour back.
By the end of today,

186
00:12:52,887 --> 00:12:55,481
either that fucking moolie or me
is gonna be in a body bag.

187
00:13:03,207 --> 00:13:06,517
- Look at that, Poet on TV.
- ln a fucking tux.

188
00:13:06,687 --> 00:13:09,645
l tell you, some serious shit
is going down, yo.

189
00:13:11,567 --> 00:13:15,401
Hey, Schibetta,
today's lunch special is arsenic.

190
00:13:15,567 --> 00:13:17,319
Yo, you got agita, bro?

191
00:13:17,487 --> 00:13:18,840
Knock it off, guys.

192
00:13:38,207 --> 00:13:41,244
- A new day dawns.
- Yeah, man, whatever.

193
00:13:41,407 --> 00:13:43,796
What's on the breakfast menu?

194
00:13:43,967 --> 00:13:46,037
Ham and eggs.

195
00:13:46,607 --> 00:13:49,041
- Eggs again?
- Yep, again.

196
00:13:49,207 --> 00:13:50,560
Shit.

197
00:13:50,727 --> 00:13:53,924
You, come into the freezer.

198
00:14:00,807 --> 00:14:03,002
Fucking chocolates.

199
00:14:08,127 --> 00:14:11,836
Morning, Chucky.
You don't work here anymore, baby.

200
00:14:12,007 --> 00:14:14,999
Wrong. l got a job to do.

201
00:14:16,647 --> 00:14:18,558
lt's payday, pal.

202
00:14:46,167 --> 00:14:48,317
Stay down.

203
00:15:18,127 --> 00:15:19,924
Hey there, baby.

204
00:15:32,767 --> 00:15:35,361
Pancamo and Schibetta
were found unconscious,

205
00:15:35,527 --> 00:15:36,960
Schibetta's rectum bleeding.

206
00:15:37,127 --> 00:15:39,436
- Could have been raped.
- What do you mean, could have?

207
00:15:39,607 --> 00:15:40,926
He says he doesn't know
what happened.

208
00:15:41,087 --> 00:15:43,999
- He won't talk about it.
- He knows.

209
00:15:44,167 --> 00:15:46,965
He's too ashamed to admit
he took one up the ass.

210
00:15:47,127 --> 00:15:48,924
He won't talk, he'll just get even.

211
00:15:49,087 --> 00:15:51,965
l'm gonna fire the CO
that let this happen.

212
00:16:04,247 --> 00:16:05,680
Peter.

213
00:16:08,887 --> 00:16:10,400
Peter.

214
00:16:12,047 --> 00:16:14,720
l just talked to the family.

215
00:16:14,887 --> 00:16:16,605
You're out.

216
00:16:16,767 --> 00:16:20,601
Somebody else is gonna be taking over
operations here in Oz.

217
00:16:25,407 --> 00:16:26,726
Lenny...

218
00:16:29,287 --> 00:16:31,482
...don't tell my father, okay?

219
00:16:33,567 --> 00:16:35,637
Don't tell my father.

220
00:16:52,407 --> 00:16:56,605
Yo, you should have been there, man.
Pancamo, out for the count.

221
00:16:56,767 --> 00:16:59,406
Schibetta's eyes wide open.

222
00:16:59,567 --> 00:17:00,886
His mind is shit.

223
00:17:01,327 --> 00:17:03,158
He got raped?

224
00:17:03,727 --> 00:17:05,558
Off who?

225
00:17:07,167 --> 00:17:08,759
What's up, partner?

226
00:17:10,847 --> 00:17:12,121
- Partners, eh?
- Yeah.

227
00:17:12,287 --> 00:17:13,925
You and me?

228
00:17:15,327 --> 00:17:17,522
We ain't fucking partners.

229
00:17:19,047 --> 00:17:21,038
l said you could help me
kill the dago.

230
00:17:21,207 --> 00:17:23,163
You didn't do shit.
Come on.

231
00:17:26,047 --> 00:17:28,038
Yo, man, you always let him
dis you, man.

232
00:17:28,207 --> 00:17:31,085
- What, you afraid of him, ése?
- Yo, fuck you.

233
00:17:31,247 --> 00:17:33,363
l ain't afraid of nobody, all right?

234
00:17:53,407 --> 00:17:55,045
Break it up, ladies, come on.

235
00:17:55,607 --> 00:17:58,201
- Hold still, goddamn it.
- Move it.

236
00:18:01,927 --> 00:18:04,805
- l'm gonna kill that motherfucker.
- No, you're not.

237
00:18:04,967 --> 00:18:06,844
Miguel...

238
00:18:07,007 --> 00:18:09,441
When we kill,
we kill for a reason, all right?

239
00:18:09,607 --> 00:18:12,440
- l got a reason.
- Man, you got shit.

240
00:18:12,607 --> 00:18:14,325
lt's your fucking fault.

241
00:18:14,487 --> 00:18:17,240
l ain't going to war
over your fucking bullshit, man.

242
00:18:17,407 --> 00:18:20,479
Oh, yeah?
So when do we go to war?

243
00:18:21,327 --> 00:18:23,636
What's it take, huh, Miguel?

244
00:18:34,447 --> 00:18:36,358
No. No!

245
00:18:41,607 --> 00:18:44,485
Prisoner number 98H498,

246
00:18:44,647 --> 00:18:47,957
Raoul Hernandez, a.k.a. El Cid.

247
00:18:48,127 --> 00:18:52,439
Convicted July 1 0th, '98,
murder in the second degree.

248
00:18:53,167 --> 00:18:55,727
Sentence, 36 years.

249
00:18:56,447 --> 00:18:58,563
Up for parole in 20.

250
00:19:00,327 --> 00:19:03,046
Raoul Hernandez, Miguel Alvarez.

251
00:19:03,207 --> 00:19:06,438
El Cid, it's an honour, man.

252
00:19:06,847 --> 00:19:07,962
You Latino?

253
00:19:09,087 --> 00:19:11,965
They lied to you, man.
You're too fucking white to be Latino.

254
00:19:12,127 --> 00:19:14,197
Get the fuck out of my face.

255
00:19:16,367 --> 00:19:18,198
Motherfucker.

256
00:19:45,047 --> 00:19:46,321
Rumour mill says

257
00:19:46,447 --> 00:19:50,201
the president of the United States
gets people to donate cash

258
00:19:50,367 --> 00:19:54,076
in return for spending a night
in the Lincoln Bedroom.

259
00:19:54,727 --> 00:19:57,366
But Lincoln never slept
in the Lincoln Bedroom.

260
00:19:57,527 --> 00:20:00,917
Lincoln never even slept in the bed
that's in the Lincoln Bedroom.

261
00:20:01,087 --> 00:20:05,478
Now, how dumb do you got to be
to give hard or soft money

262
00:20:05,647 --> 00:20:08,480
for a decent place to crash,
and it's false advertising?

263
00:20:08,647 --> 00:20:09,875
Shit.

264
00:20:10,367 --> 00:20:12,756
Wanna pay to snooze in my room?

265
00:20:12,927 --> 00:20:16,124
Jeffrey Dahmer lived there.
Hey, Al Capone too.

266
00:20:16,287 --> 00:20:17,720
Fuck, for a couple of extra bucks,

267
00:20:17,887 --> 00:20:21,641
l'll get the ghost of Jesse
fucking James to float on by.

268
00:20:35,007 --> 00:20:36,201
What?

269
00:20:36,367 --> 00:20:39,643
Water pipe. l almost busted it open.

270
00:20:39,807 --> 00:20:42,446
lmagine a geyser of water
spouting up out of the floor.

271
00:20:42,607 --> 00:20:46,680
Busmalis, l'm beginning to have
second thoughts about this excavation.

272
00:20:46,847 --> 00:20:50,157
Second thoughts?
Well, have third thoughts.

273
00:20:50,327 --> 00:20:53,444
- lf we get caught--
- We're not gonna get caught.

274
00:20:53,607 --> 00:20:55,916
We have a hole the size
of the Holland Tunnel in our cell.

275
00:20:56,087 --> 00:20:58,681
- We're gonna get caught.
- She'll hear you.

276
00:20:58,847 --> 00:21:00,405
She? She who?

277
00:21:00,567 --> 00:21:04,003
The hole. l treat every hole
l dig like a lady.

278
00:21:04,167 --> 00:21:07,523
A very special lady.
l never married, you know.

279
00:21:07,687 --> 00:21:11,600
l could never find a real woman who
could satisfy me the way she does.

280
00:21:13,287 --> 00:21:18,520
Yeah, l'll bet there are a lot of women
who are brokenhearted losing you.

281
00:21:38,967 --> 00:21:42,926
Prisoner number 98W504,
Jiggy Walker.

282
00:21:43,087 --> 00:21:47,239
Convicted July 1 2th, '98,
murder in the second degree.

283
00:21:48,447 --> 00:21:51,166
Sentence, 28 years.

284
00:21:51,327 --> 00:21:53,397
Up for parole in 20.

285
00:21:55,047 --> 00:21:56,765
What are you in for?

286
00:21:56,927 --> 00:21:58,679
What's it matter?

287
00:21:58,847 --> 00:22:00,883
The charge is trumped.

288
00:22:01,047 --> 00:22:03,436
Truth is l'm here
because l know too much.

289
00:22:03,607 --> 00:22:05,518
Too much about what?

290
00:22:13,327 --> 00:22:17,718
Rebadow will show you the ropes.
Behave yourself, we'll get along fine.

291
00:22:18,887 --> 00:22:20,798
Too much about what?

292
00:22:21,887 --> 00:22:25,926
- Governor Devlin.
- What about Devlin?

293
00:22:26,207 --> 00:22:28,437
He's a major-league crack addict.

294
00:22:28,607 --> 00:22:31,041
- No, no.
- Yeah.

295
00:22:31,207 --> 00:22:33,721
- Oh, yeah.
- Crack addict?

296
00:22:34,567 --> 00:22:36,444
How would you know
that he's a crack addict?

297
00:22:36,607 --> 00:22:39,963
How you think, bitch?
l sold him the shit.

298
00:22:40,127 --> 00:22:42,038
l'm the governor's
drug dealer of choice.

299
00:22:48,327 --> 00:22:50,045
Everybody play it straight.
All right,

300
00:22:50,207 --> 00:22:51,925
dealer takes two.
What are we looking at?

301
00:22:52,087 --> 00:22:54,840
- What you got?
- Well, lookie, lookie.

302
00:22:55,007 --> 00:22:58,443
- Four beautiful aces.
- Fuck. Damn it.

303
00:22:58,607 --> 00:23:01,201
- Wait a minute, l got a fucking ace.
- You cocksucker.

304
00:23:01,367 --> 00:23:03,039
Hey, hey, hey, gentlemen,
don't get testy now.

305
00:23:03,207 --> 00:23:04,879
Mr. Walker.

306
00:23:07,167 --> 00:23:09,362
May we talk privately, please?

307
00:23:09,967 --> 00:23:11,446
l understand
you have some information

308
00:23:11,607 --> 00:23:13,882
regarding the governor,
James Devlin?

309
00:23:14,047 --> 00:23:18,040
- lnformation of a damaging nature.
- Damaging?

310
00:23:18,207 --> 00:23:20,243
Depends on how you view crack.

311
00:23:20,407 --> 00:23:22,125
Well, my guess is
the voters would frown

312
00:23:22,287 --> 00:23:25,165
upon their chief executive
doing street drugs.

313
00:23:26,687 --> 00:23:29,247
l want this information to go public.

314
00:23:30,847 --> 00:23:33,998
l don't know, Said.
What's in it for me?

315
00:23:34,167 --> 00:23:37,159
- What's in it for you?
- Yeah.

316
00:23:38,207 --> 00:23:40,038
lf we create a tidal wave

317
00:23:40,207 --> 00:23:42,801
and we sweep Governor Devlin
right out of office,

318
00:23:42,967 --> 00:23:45,481
you might find yourself released.

319
00:23:46,047 --> 00:23:47,196
How?

320
00:23:47,367 --> 00:23:49,927
l have connections within the media.

321
00:23:50,207 --> 00:23:51,845
This time tomorrow morning,

322
00:23:52,007 --> 00:23:55,317
you might find yourself
the most famous man in the state.

323
00:23:58,527 --> 00:24:02,645
- Me, a celebrity like Oprah?
- Oh, yes, my brother.

324
00:24:03,167 --> 00:24:06,796
But what l need from you is this:
dates, times.

325
00:24:06,967 --> 00:24:09,401
Places of your business transactions
with Governor Devlin.

326
00:24:09,567 --> 00:24:12,764
l can't be exact.
lt's not like we kept records and such.

327
00:24:12,927 --> 00:24:15,964
Are there any other witnesses
to corroborate your story?

328
00:24:16,927 --> 00:24:19,805
- Scat'll do that.
- Who's Scat?

329
00:24:20,287 --> 00:24:21,561
My cousin.

330
00:24:21,727 --> 00:24:24,480
Works post office,
priority mail division.

331
00:24:25,447 --> 00:24:26,926
Okay.

332
00:24:27,367 --> 00:24:29,244
l'll make some calls.

333
00:24:30,207 --> 00:24:32,118
Be prepared
to do a lot of interviews, my brother.

334
00:24:33,007 --> 00:24:34,486
Bring them on, baby.

335
00:24:34,647 --> 00:24:36,797
l got plenty to say
and plenty time to say it.

336
00:24:36,967 --> 00:24:39,527
Arif, may l see you, please?

337
00:24:39,687 --> 00:24:41,359
My nigga.

338
00:24:42,927 --> 00:24:44,440
What's up, nigga?

339
00:24:49,927 --> 00:24:51,838
You seen this?

340
00:24:53,007 --> 00:24:55,043
l just spoke to Ekdahl.

341
00:24:55,207 --> 00:24:58,677
The monitoring office says that Walker
did five phone interviews yesterday

342
00:24:58,847 --> 00:25:00,121
to press across the state.

343
00:25:00,287 --> 00:25:03,085
- l saw it on the news this morning.
- l heard it on the radio driving in.

344
00:25:03,247 --> 00:25:04,236
Devlin's finished.

345
00:25:04,407 --> 00:25:06,523
Assuming he actually bought
the crack, yeah.

346
00:25:06,687 --> 00:25:08,484
Come on, Diane.
You doubt he's guilty?

347
00:25:08,647 --> 00:25:10,399
He's innocent
till proven otherwise, right?

348
00:25:10,567 --> 00:25:14,037
ABC, NBC, CNN,
they all want on-camera interviews.

349
00:25:14,207 --> 00:25:18,598
Let them, let them all talk to Walker.
All day, every day till Devlin resigns.

350
00:25:18,767 --> 00:25:21,201
Come on, the governor's not gonna
give them that kind of access.

351
00:25:21,367 --> 00:25:23,164
On the contrary.
l just got off the phone with him.

352
00:25:23,327 --> 00:25:25,045
Devlin wants Walker
to talk to the press.

353
00:25:25,207 --> 00:25:28,995
- And he wants full disclosure.
- Well, l'll be fucked.

354
00:25:29,167 --> 00:25:32,443
--no truth to these allegations.
l do not know Jiggy Walker,

355
00:25:32,607 --> 00:25:36,600
l have never bought drugs
from him or anyone, not now or ever.

356
00:25:37,087 --> 00:25:40,841
This is another in a long series
of false, partizan accusations

357
00:25:41,007 --> 00:25:43,646
that have been perpetuated
by a scandal-hungry press.

358
00:25:43,807 --> 00:25:47,117
l intend to go to Oswald today
and confront Mr. Walker face to face.

359
00:25:47,287 --> 00:25:49,881
l invite the media to accompany me.

360
00:25:50,047 --> 00:25:54,245
The monitoring office says you placed
the calls to the newspapers for Walker.

361
00:25:54,407 --> 00:25:56,284
ls that a crime, McManus?

362
00:25:56,447 --> 00:25:58,802
l hate Devlin as much as you do.

363
00:25:58,967 --> 00:26:01,401
l only wish you would have told me.

364
00:26:03,807 --> 00:26:06,526
l have here the records
of the two physical examinations

365
00:26:06,687 --> 00:26:09,155
performed on me
since l came into office.

366
00:26:09,327 --> 00:26:12,603
lncluded in the report
is the drug testing that l instituted

367
00:26:12,767 --> 00:26:14,644
as mandatory
for all state employees.

368
00:26:14,807 --> 00:26:16,126
There is no indication

369
00:26:16,287 --> 00:26:21,520
of any illegal chemical substances
in my system.

370
00:26:21,687 --> 00:26:23,518
l say to you now,

371
00:26:24,767 --> 00:26:26,837
bring me Jiggy Walker.

372
00:26:27,727 --> 00:26:30,002
Bring me my accuser.

373
00:26:30,767 --> 00:26:32,758
Mr. Walker, do you have
any other names of people--?

374
00:26:32,927 --> 00:26:35,487
Mr. Walker, how long
have you been selling drugs?

375
00:26:35,647 --> 00:26:37,717
Mr. Walker, is there a deal
in the works?

376
00:26:37,887 --> 00:26:39,525
- You wanna get Jiggy, huh, man?
- Mr. Walker.

377
00:26:39,687 --> 00:26:41,405
Mr. Walker.

378
00:26:42,127 --> 00:26:45,437
You claim that you sold me
two grams of crack cocaine

379
00:26:45,607 --> 00:26:49,395
on May 3rd at an apartment house
on Spring and Vine

380
00:26:49,567 --> 00:26:51,444
in the state capital.

381
00:26:51,807 --> 00:26:53,240
That's right.

382
00:26:53,407 --> 00:26:57,480
l have here plane tickets
and a guest list

383
00:26:57,647 --> 00:27:01,276
proving that on May 3rd,
l was attending a reception

384
00:27:01,447 --> 00:27:04,439
for our nation's governors
in the Blue Room at the White House.

385
00:27:04,607 --> 00:27:09,681
Now, Mr. Walker, how could l be
in two places at the same time?

386
00:27:09,847 --> 00:27:12,759
Okay, so that night
l sold the shit to one of your aides.

387
00:27:12,927 --> 00:27:15,566
- Which one?
- Sam Burlinghall.

388
00:27:15,727 --> 00:27:19,003
Sam Burlinghall was with me in D.C.

389
00:27:21,327 --> 00:27:23,966
Cat said he was Sam Burlinghall.
How was l to know that he's lying?

390
00:27:24,127 --> 00:27:25,196
How indeed.

391
00:27:25,367 --> 00:27:27,642
You claim your cousin,
James Dyson Walker,

392
00:27:27,807 --> 00:27:28,956
will back up your story.

393
00:27:29,127 --> 00:27:32,085
l have here a sworn statement
from James Dyson Walker

394
00:27:32,247 --> 00:27:36,081
denying any participation
in any drug transactions

395
00:27:36,247 --> 00:27:37,885
between you and me.

396
00:27:38,607 --> 00:27:39,801
Okay, so you paid him off.

397
00:27:40,127 --> 00:27:43,005
No, Mr. Walker,
l asked him to tell me the truth

398
00:27:43,167 --> 00:27:44,646
and now l'm asking you.

399
00:27:44,807 --> 00:27:47,560
Admit you lied.
Show's over, Mr. Walker.

400
00:27:47,727 --> 00:27:52,801
For once in your life,
do the decent thing and admit it.

401
00:28:01,007 --> 00:28:02,520
Okay.

402
00:28:03,167 --> 00:28:04,441
l lied.

403
00:28:05,767 --> 00:28:08,565
So, motherfucker, so what?
You've been lying all your life.

404
00:28:08,727 --> 00:28:10,877
Shit, still Jiggy.

405
00:28:12,487 --> 00:28:14,284
Shit.

406
00:28:15,607 --> 00:28:17,598
l don't understand why you'd lie.

407
00:28:17,767 --> 00:28:20,600
Man, l been in and out of prison
all my life.

408
00:28:20,767 --> 00:28:23,361
The one thing l learned is that
when you come through them gates,

409
00:28:23,527 --> 00:28:24,755
you got to have props.

410
00:28:24,927 --> 00:28:26,565
You got to be somebody
to get respect

411
00:28:26,727 --> 00:28:30,003
so the brothers and the others
don't fuck with you.

412
00:28:31,007 --> 00:28:32,440
Okay, but why go public?

413
00:28:32,607 --> 00:28:34,518
That was his idea,
making all sorts of noise

414
00:28:34,687 --> 00:28:36,439
about me getting released.

415
00:28:36,607 --> 00:28:38,165
l figured it was worth a shot.

416
00:28:38,327 --> 00:28:40,397
That's stupid. You must've known
that you'd be exposed.

417
00:28:40,767 --> 00:28:44,442
- l knew it was a good chance.
- Then you tell me why, brother.

418
00:28:44,607 --> 00:28:47,121
Man, my first prison stay
was over at Lardner.

419
00:28:47,287 --> 00:28:49,721
Eighteen years, l was 1 7.

420
00:28:49,887 --> 00:28:51,605
My family came to visit me regular.

421
00:28:51,767 --> 00:28:53,644
And LaTanya, my fiancée
and my friends.

422
00:28:53,807 --> 00:28:55,320
They all came the first year.

423
00:28:55,487 --> 00:28:57,876
Then LaTanya married Beau,
so she stopped coming.

424
00:28:58,047 --> 00:29:00,402
Stopped showing up.
Then Rodney didn't come no more.

425
00:29:00,567 --> 00:29:03,639
My cousin Scat, my sister.
My dad, he died.

426
00:29:03,807 --> 00:29:06,446
Year five,
it was just me and my mama.

427
00:29:07,407 --> 00:29:09,762
Then they put her
in an old folks' home.

428
00:29:09,927 --> 00:29:12,760
Six years in, l had no visiting days.

429
00:29:12,927 --> 00:29:15,521
l had no one to come to see
if l was still breathing.

430
00:29:15,687 --> 00:29:17,325
So l said, ''Hey,

431
00:29:17,487 --> 00:29:21,719
get on TV, become a superstar,
maybe they'd come for longer.

432
00:29:21,887 --> 00:29:23,878
Maybe they wouldn't
forget about me.''

433
00:29:28,927 --> 00:29:31,316
Fight the power, baby.

434
00:29:35,287 --> 00:29:36,322
He's a little hostile.

435
00:29:36,887 --> 00:29:38,843
l'm transferring you to gen pop.

436
00:29:39,487 --> 00:29:41,205
l hear that.

437
00:29:41,527 --> 00:29:44,917
Yes, yes, l know.
lt's shocking what some people will do.

438
00:29:47,407 --> 00:29:49,443
Thank you, Mr. President.

439
00:29:53,247 --> 00:29:55,283
All in all,

440
00:29:56,207 --> 00:29:58,402
it was a good day.

441
00:30:00,767 --> 00:30:02,200
Governor.

442
00:30:04,687 --> 00:30:07,155
You didn't set all this up, did you?

443
00:30:07,327 --> 00:30:10,524
You didn't hire Walker to lie,
did you?

444
00:30:12,167 --> 00:30:13,395
No.

445
00:30:14,047 --> 00:30:18,199
No, l simply took advantage
of the situation.

446
00:30:19,407 --> 00:30:22,524
l've been accused of so many things
in the past year or so

447
00:30:22,687 --> 00:30:27,442
that when l realized l could actually
prove my innocence on this one...

448
00:30:29,367 --> 00:30:32,757
Well, it tinges all the other charges

449
00:30:32,927 --> 00:30:37,955
with a wonderful veneer of doubt.

450
00:30:43,247 --> 00:30:44,805
Do me a favour,

451
00:30:44,967 --> 00:30:49,085
give these to Jiggy Walker.
l owe him.

452
00:31:03,727 --> 00:31:05,763
Giles was on the corner
of Sycamore and Broome

453
00:31:05,927 --> 00:31:08,122
on the day my husband was killed.

454
00:31:08,287 --> 00:31:11,916
He saw whoever pushed Leonard
off the back of that truck.

455
00:31:12,247 --> 00:31:15,319
- But he won't say who it was.
- Aim.

456
00:31:15,487 --> 00:31:16,476
Aim?

457
00:31:16,647 --> 00:31:19,366
That's all he'll say now,
over and over again. Aim.

458
00:31:23,847 --> 00:31:26,407
So, what's next?

459
00:31:27,127 --> 00:31:28,879
l'm gonna talk to Augustus Hill.

460
00:31:29,047 --> 00:31:30,241
Before Em City opened,

461
00:31:30,407 --> 00:31:33,558
he was in unit B,
in the cell right next to Giles.

462
00:31:35,487 --> 00:31:37,523
Before he got sent into solitary,

463
00:31:37,687 --> 00:31:41,646
did Giles ever say anything
about his life on the outside?

464
00:31:41,807 --> 00:31:44,401
- l guess so.
- What do you mean, you guess so?

465
00:31:44,567 --> 00:31:46,558
l never really listened
to what he was saying, you know.

466
00:31:46,727 --> 00:31:48,604
He'd just go on and on.

467
00:31:50,087 --> 00:31:51,839
l finally just tuned him O-U-T.

468
00:31:52,007 --> 00:31:55,841
What about two years ago,
when he killed his roommate Ron Bibi?

469
00:31:56,007 --> 00:31:57,725
The day wasn't different
than any other day.

470
00:32:09,087 --> 00:32:13,399
Ron Bibi was killed because
he was trying to steal Giles' stuff?

471
00:32:13,567 --> 00:32:15,797
Well, the files show the opposite.

472
00:32:15,967 --> 00:32:17,161
l don't know about no files,

473
00:32:17,327 --> 00:32:20,763
but l remember William Giles was
very conscientious about his teeth.

474
00:32:20,927 --> 00:32:22,997
The guy brushed, like,
a thousand times a day.

475
00:32:23,167 --> 00:32:26,239
Seriously, he guarded his toothpaste
like it was gold.

476
00:32:26,407 --> 00:32:29,205
- His toothpaste?
- Yup.

477
00:32:29,767 --> 00:32:31,564
Augustus.

478
00:32:31,967 --> 00:32:34,845
- What brand did he use?
- Brand?

479
00:32:35,007 --> 00:32:36,998
Oh, same as mine. Aim.

480
00:32:43,647 --> 00:32:46,207
Ron Bibi killed my husband.

481
00:32:49,567 --> 00:32:52,286
Can you tell me about it?

482
00:32:53,327 --> 00:32:56,637
Gingivitis bad.

483
00:32:56,807 --> 00:32:58,365
Bibi worse.

484
00:32:58,527 --> 00:33:00,802
Eye, eyes.

485
00:33:00,967 --> 00:33:06,087
Bibi, Bibi, eyes, eye.

486
00:33:07,487 --> 00:33:12,197
He saw you see him

487
00:33:12,367 --> 00:33:13,880
push Leonard off the truck?

488
00:33:17,727 --> 00:33:21,083
Do you know why Ron Bibi
murdered my husband?

489
00:33:22,207 --> 00:33:23,799
Sorry.

490
00:33:23,967 --> 00:33:28,563
He never said to you why
he pushed my husband off that truck?

491
00:33:28,967 --> 00:33:30,559
Sorry.

492
00:33:32,127 --> 00:33:33,845
Sorry.

493
00:33:34,407 --> 00:33:36,125
Sorry.

494
00:33:37,847 --> 00:33:39,644
lt's okay.

495
00:33:39,807 --> 00:33:41,286
lt's all right.

496
00:33:41,447 --> 00:33:42,926
lt's okay.

497
00:33:43,287 --> 00:33:46,279
Giles murdered the man
who murdered your husband.

498
00:33:46,447 --> 00:33:50,326
- You want to let him out of solitary?
- Yes.

499
00:33:50,487 --> 00:33:53,684
You ever consider the idea
that maybe he's playing you?

500
00:33:53,847 --> 00:33:57,157
- Maybe he made it all up.
- l believe him, Leo.

501
00:33:57,327 --> 00:33:59,443
Even if he did what he said he did,

502
00:33:59,607 --> 00:34:01,643
he's still prone to violence.

503
00:34:03,927 --> 00:34:06,566
He'd be a menace
to the rest of the prison population.

504
00:34:06,727 --> 00:34:08,604
Well, still,

505
00:34:08,767 --> 00:34:12,555
l feel like l should
do something special for him.

506
00:34:23,167 --> 00:34:25,476
From Sister Peter Marie.

507
00:34:58,607 --> 00:35:00,677
Hey, Dr. Prestopnik,
how you doing?

508
00:35:00,847 --> 00:35:05,079
Oh, my back is killing me,
my house needs a new sewer system,

509
00:35:05,247 --> 00:35:08,159
my wife wants to spend
our 30th wedding anniversary

510
00:35:08,327 --> 00:35:09,999
in the Virgin lslands.

511
00:35:10,167 --> 00:35:12,078
Talk about living in the past.

512
00:35:12,247 --> 00:35:13,965
Other than that, l'm hunky-dory.

513
00:35:14,527 --> 00:35:15,960
You?

514
00:35:17,247 --> 00:35:18,441
You know, l saw on TV

515
00:35:18,607 --> 00:35:21,724
that pot helps beat
the aftereffects of chemo.

516
00:35:21,887 --> 00:35:23,843
- Yeah.
- So, what do you say, huh?

517
00:35:24,007 --> 00:35:25,406
Wanna hook me up?

518
00:35:26,287 --> 00:35:28,278
- You want me to give you marijuana?
- Yeah.

519
00:35:28,447 --> 00:35:30,836
For, what do you call it,
medicinal purposes.

520
00:35:31,327 --> 00:35:33,204
Nice try, kid.

521
00:35:35,167 --> 00:35:38,204
Looks like you got the cancer
on the run, your hair's coming back.

522
00:35:38,367 --> 00:35:40,403
This will probably
be your final treatment.

523
00:35:41,087 --> 00:35:43,237
Thank fucking Christ.

524
00:35:43,407 --> 00:35:44,920
Hey, how's Dr. Nathan doing?

525
00:35:45,087 --> 00:35:46,281
l haven't seen her around lately

526
00:35:46,447 --> 00:35:49,405
and l heard about her husband
getting murdered and all.

527
00:36:08,887 --> 00:36:10,957
The funeral was Thursday.

528
00:36:11,367 --> 00:36:13,722
She says she's coming back to work
as early as tomorrow.

529
00:36:14,367 --> 00:36:16,927
- That's an amazing woman.
- Yeah.

530
00:36:17,087 --> 00:36:19,760
You see her, you tell her
l'm sorry for her loss.

531
00:36:20,607 --> 00:36:23,167
l will, O'Reily, l will.

532
00:36:23,327 --> 00:36:24,555
Hey, babe.

533
00:36:25,487 --> 00:36:29,116
Dr. Prestopnik,
this is my wife, Shannon.

534
00:36:29,527 --> 00:36:31,518
Pleasure and a half.

535
00:36:41,207 --> 00:36:43,163
You haven't been to see me lately.

536
00:36:44,127 --> 00:36:46,436
Yeah, l know. l've been busy.

537
00:36:47,007 --> 00:36:49,965
- Doing what?
- Taking care of your brother.

538
00:36:50,127 --> 00:36:52,163
He's a little out of control
these days.

539
00:36:52,767 --> 00:36:54,325
Yeah, l called my cousin Matthew.

540
00:36:54,487 --> 00:36:56,205
He's gonna take Cyril in.

541
00:36:57,207 --> 00:36:59,721
You and l, Shannon, we're done.

542
00:36:59,927 --> 00:37:01,485
What?

543
00:37:01,647 --> 00:37:04,002
l don't wanna be married
to you anymore.

544
00:37:05,127 --> 00:37:07,800
- Why?
- l found someone else.

545
00:37:09,207 --> 00:37:10,481
Shannon.

546
00:37:18,127 --> 00:37:21,483
Gloria, what are you doing here?

547
00:37:21,647 --> 00:37:25,242
Gotta work, Tim.
l got nothing else right now.

548
00:37:26,207 --> 00:37:28,243
You should take a vacation.

549
00:37:30,607 --> 00:37:32,199
Where?

550
00:37:33,207 --> 00:37:35,641
How far do l need to go
to get away from what happened?

551
00:37:39,567 --> 00:37:40,920
You know,

552
00:37:42,607 --> 00:37:45,405
we didn't have the best marriage,
Preston and l.

553
00:37:45,567 --> 00:37:48,445
Too many games, too many tests,

554
00:37:49,007 --> 00:37:51,316
too much pride,

555
00:37:53,047 --> 00:37:55,197
but we really loved each other.

556
00:37:57,247 --> 00:37:58,202
We really did.

557
00:37:58,927 --> 00:38:00,758
He was a good man.

558
00:38:06,247 --> 00:38:08,556
God, why did he have to die?

559
00:38:28,367 --> 00:38:32,565
Prisoner number 98P284,
Cyril O'Reily.

560
00:38:32,727 --> 00:38:37,323
Convicted July 1 st, '98,
murder in the first degree.

561
00:38:38,247 --> 00:38:40,602
Sentence: life.

562
00:38:41,167 --> 00:38:43,635
Up for parole in 60 years.

563
00:38:53,247 --> 00:38:54,999
- No.
- No.

564
00:38:55,167 --> 00:38:57,761
Preston is dead because of me.

565
00:39:19,807 --> 00:39:23,117
- Hey, Gloria, you're back. Hi.
- Don't.

566
00:39:23,287 --> 00:39:25,005
What?

567
00:39:31,647 --> 00:39:34,559
l became a doctor to help people.

568
00:39:35,207 --> 00:39:38,040
Now, l know that that sounds
like a cliché,

569
00:39:38,207 --> 00:39:42,041
it sounds naive, but it's true.

570
00:39:42,487 --> 00:39:45,877
l could have
a fancy practise anywhere,

571
00:39:46,047 --> 00:39:48,720
but instead l chose to work at Oz.

572
00:39:49,927 --> 00:39:53,078
l saved your life, O'Reily.

573
00:39:55,487 --> 00:39:57,955
And in return, you destroyed mine.

574
00:40:11,767 --> 00:40:13,564
Your brother Cyril confessed.

575
00:40:13,727 --> 00:40:15,524
Shit.

576
00:40:15,687 --> 00:40:17,518
Cops wanna interrogate you,

577
00:40:17,687 --> 00:40:20,838
although he's refusing
to implicate you in the murder.

578
00:40:21,367 --> 00:40:23,403
He's gonna take the rap himself.

579
00:40:24,367 --> 00:40:25,880
McManus.

580
00:40:27,767 --> 00:40:29,359
You gotta see that l love her, man.

581
00:40:31,447 --> 00:40:33,836
Love? What the fuck
do you know about love?

582
00:40:34,207 --> 00:40:39,122
Whoa, what do you know, huh?
What do any of us?

583
00:40:39,287 --> 00:40:41,847
l know it's not a reason
to commit murder.

584
00:40:42,007 --> 00:40:44,805
Yeah, well, then, maybe
you've never really been in love.

585
00:40:56,927 --> 00:40:59,202
Life is no bed of roses.

586
00:40:59,367 --> 00:41:00,880
But then again,

587
00:41:01,047 --> 00:41:03,845
which of us really wants to sleep
on a bed of roses?

588
00:41:04,007 --> 00:41:05,156
You never get any rest.

589
00:41:05,567 --> 00:41:07,797
Every time you toss and turn,

590
00:41:07,967 --> 00:41:09,958
you hit another thorn.

591
00:41:21,407 --> 00:41:23,602
Hey, hey, hey.

592
00:41:23,767 --> 00:41:26,679
Hey, you all right?

593
00:41:30,367 --> 00:41:32,881
- Same nightmare, huh?
- Yeah.

594
00:41:33,807 --> 00:41:36,765
- l'm soaked.
- Yeah, let's get you out of those.

595
00:41:41,887 --> 00:41:43,320
Jesus.

596
00:41:50,167 --> 00:41:51,122
Thanks.

597
00:41:51,287 --> 00:41:53,084
We need to do something
about that tattoo.

598
00:41:53,687 --> 00:41:55,166
Oh, yeah?

599
00:41:55,647 --> 00:41:57,080
What are we gonna do?

600
00:42:00,527 --> 00:42:02,279
l don't know.
Let me think on it, huh?

601
00:42:08,287 --> 00:42:11,484
- You're all right.
- Yeah.

602
00:42:32,687 --> 00:42:35,485
- Good morning, Tobias.
- Good morning.

603
00:42:36,887 --> 00:42:39,765
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.

604
00:42:39,927 --> 00:42:42,999
Tobias, l see you
almost every single day.

605
00:42:43,167 --> 00:42:48,241
l know the difference
between nothing and nothing.

606
00:43:06,807 --> 00:43:09,275
Two men shouldn't love each other.

607
00:43:11,607 --> 00:43:13,916
They can't feel the same things

608
00:43:14,567 --> 00:43:16,797
a man and a woman feel.

609
00:43:19,967 --> 00:43:21,639
l mean,

610
00:43:21,807 --> 00:43:25,197
if a guy has a lot of bad shit
happen to him,

611
00:43:25,367 --> 00:43:28,439
and another guy comforts him,
l mean, that's all it is, right?

612
00:43:28,607 --> 00:43:31,565
l mean, that's not love, right?

613
00:43:32,447 --> 00:43:35,007
Well, some men in here
are homosexual and some need sex--

614
00:43:35,167 --> 00:43:38,318
l'm not talking about sex.
l'm talking about love.

615
00:43:38,487 --> 00:43:42,526
l had sex with Schillinger.
lt was brutal, unloving.

616
00:43:44,927 --> 00:43:48,044
This is different.

617
00:43:50,847 --> 00:43:52,326
Tobias,

618
00:43:52,487 --> 00:43:54,955
are you in love with another man?

619
00:43:59,167 --> 00:44:01,237
l think so, yeah.

620
00:44:02,367 --> 00:44:05,996
98D242, 65R81 4,

621
00:44:06,167 --> 00:44:10,001
97B41 2, 98K51 4.

622
00:44:10,167 --> 00:44:13,045
All right, everybody. lnto your cells.

623
00:44:16,447 --> 00:44:19,166
- Got a surprise for you.
- A surprise?

624
00:44:19,327 --> 00:44:22,160
l talked to a couple of guys
who know about tattoos.

625
00:44:22,327 --> 00:44:25,125
They said because yours
was burned on instead of inked,

626
00:44:25,287 --> 00:44:27,005
it can't be removed.

627
00:44:27,167 --> 00:44:28,759
l could have told you that.

628
00:44:28,927 --> 00:44:32,124
- You hate the swastika, right?
- Yeah.

629
00:44:33,007 --> 00:44:35,521
Okay, so then we fill it in like that.

630
00:44:36,367 --> 00:44:39,006
Oh, okay. What, you don't like that?

631
00:44:39,687 --> 00:44:42,759
We'll be PC. Just do that.

632
00:44:43,167 --> 00:44:45,158
- That's crazy.
- Why crazy?

633
00:44:45,727 --> 00:44:47,638
As much as l wanna get rid
of the fucking thing,

634
00:44:47,807 --> 00:44:50,321
l remember how painful it was
going on.

635
00:44:50,487 --> 00:44:53,479
Both of those?
That's a lot of burned flesh.

636
00:44:53,647 --> 00:44:58,562
Which leads to the second part
of my surprise.

637
00:44:59,727 --> 00:45:01,126
- What's that?
- Moonshine.

638
00:45:01,287 --> 00:45:03,596
One hundred and one percent
pure alcohol.

639
00:45:03,767 --> 00:45:05,678
lt's like the old West.

640
00:45:05,847 --> 00:45:07,565
Cowboy gets shot,
you gotta remove the bullet.

641
00:45:07,727 --> 00:45:10,719
You take a couple snorts of this shit,
you're not gonna feel anything.

642
00:45:12,127 --> 00:45:13,879
- There's only one problem with that.
- Yeah?

643
00:45:14,047 --> 00:45:17,517
- l've been sober for over a year now.
- So what?

644
00:45:20,447 --> 00:45:22,881
l'm an alcoholic.

645
00:45:23,047 --> 00:45:24,765
Every bad thing
that's ever happened to me

646
00:45:24,927 --> 00:45:27,805
has been as a result of booze.

647
00:45:29,407 --> 00:45:33,525
l'm just now feeling like
l'm beating my heroin addiction.

648
00:45:33,807 --> 00:45:35,559
To go back home to alcohol...

649
00:45:36,287 --> 00:45:37,800
Okay.

650
00:45:38,967 --> 00:45:40,605
- Don't be mad.
- l'm not mad.

651
00:45:40,767 --> 00:45:42,803
- Yeah, you are.
- No, it was a stupid idea.

652
00:45:42,967 --> 00:45:45,242
l just didn't think things through.

653
00:45:45,407 --> 00:45:46,556
lt's my problem.

654
00:45:46,727 --> 00:45:49,082
l don't think anything
all the fucking way through.

655
00:45:51,727 --> 00:45:54,195
l hate when you're self-deprecating.

656
00:45:54,767 --> 00:45:56,519
lt's so cute.

657
00:45:58,527 --> 00:46:00,597
Hey, where'd you get that stuff,
anyway?

658
00:46:00,767 --> 00:46:02,803
Friend of mine in unit B's
rigged up a still.

659
00:47:24,087 --> 00:47:26,237
- So he didn't drink the moonshine?
- Nope.

660
00:47:26,407 --> 00:47:29,558
- Fuck.
- But he was close.

661
00:47:29,727 --> 00:47:31,957
Close? Fuck close.

662
00:47:32,127 --> 00:47:34,925
The whole idea here,
the whole beauty of this plan,

663
00:47:35,087 --> 00:47:37,681
is that we keep digging up
all the guilt and shame,

664
00:47:37,847 --> 00:47:41,840
all the shit that Beecher's got inside
of him until he can't live with himself.

665
00:47:42,007 --> 00:47:45,397
Until Beecher destroys himself.
The alcohol's the key.

666
00:47:45,567 --> 00:47:47,797
No, Vern, l'm the key.

667
00:47:48,007 --> 00:47:50,077
Beecher loves me.

668
00:47:50,247 --> 00:47:54,160
He won't admit it yet, but he loves me.
l'll get him to drink.

669
00:47:54,327 --> 00:47:57,444
- l win.
- Fuck you, you fucking redneck.

670
00:47:57,607 --> 00:48:01,316
- Eat me, jizzball.
- You'd like that, wouldn't you?

671
00:48:03,087 --> 00:48:04,600
Fucking asshole.

672
00:48:04,767 --> 00:48:07,679
- What the fuck was that about?
- Who the fuck knows?

673
00:48:08,487 --> 00:48:11,160
l hate what that cocksucker
did to you.

674
00:48:13,607 --> 00:48:14,960
Come on.

675
00:48:19,007 --> 00:48:21,396
Cocksucker!

676
00:48:24,967 --> 00:48:26,685
l don't understand.

677
00:48:26,847 --> 00:48:29,919
Your parents decide whether or not
you get to see your own kids?

678
00:48:30,087 --> 00:48:33,796
No. They think,
all things considered,

679
00:48:33,967 --> 00:48:35,400
l shouldn't spend time with them yet.

680
00:48:35,567 --> 00:48:37,797
You know, seeing me like this
might do more harm than good.

681
00:48:37,967 --> 00:48:40,720
Seeing you like this,
what the fuck does that mean?

682
00:48:41,207 --> 00:48:42,845
You know.

683
00:48:43,687 --> 00:48:45,962
Beecher, you're their father.

684
00:48:47,447 --> 00:48:49,278
For chrissakes,
everything they've been through,

685
00:48:49,447 --> 00:48:53,201
finding your wife,
their mother, dead.

686
00:48:54,687 --> 00:48:57,804
They need you,
not their grandparents.

687
00:48:57,967 --> 00:48:59,798
- You.
- You think?

688
00:48:59,967 --> 00:49:01,878
Look, despite everything
that you've gone through,

689
00:49:02,047 --> 00:49:04,277
one thing hasn't changed.

690
00:49:04,447 --> 00:49:06,517
They are your blood.

691
00:49:13,807 --> 00:49:15,160
Hey.

692
00:49:15,687 --> 00:49:17,917
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!

693
00:49:21,287 --> 00:49:23,562
l miss you, Daddy.

694
00:49:28,207 --> 00:49:30,596
l love you, Daddy.

695
00:49:36,727 --> 00:49:39,480
- You're doing laundry?
- Yeah.

696
00:49:39,647 --> 00:49:42,207
- You hate doing laundry.
- Yeah.

697
00:49:42,367 --> 00:49:44,756
- Chris.
- l'm celebrating your reunion.

698
00:49:44,927 --> 00:49:46,280
Are you nuts?
They're gonna see you.

699
00:49:46,447 --> 00:49:47,960
l don't care.

700
00:49:48,127 --> 00:49:49,480
All right.

701
00:49:50,767 --> 00:49:52,564
You look good without a beard.

702
00:49:52,727 --> 00:49:54,206
What happened?

703
00:49:59,767 --> 00:50:01,962
What? What?

704
00:50:02,127 --> 00:50:04,595
Remember l told you
l got married three times?

705
00:50:04,767 --> 00:50:06,803
Four times, if you count...

706
00:50:08,287 --> 00:50:10,437
...Bonnie, who l married twice.

707
00:50:11,647 --> 00:50:14,241
Yeah, why did you get married
so often?

708
00:50:14,407 --> 00:50:17,717
Call me old-fashioned,
but before l fuck them, l marry them.

709
00:50:20,367 --> 00:50:22,323
Problem is...

710
00:50:24,607 --> 00:50:26,325
...the sex.

711
00:50:28,767 --> 00:50:30,678
lt's never as good
as it is in the beginning.

712
00:50:30,847 --> 00:50:32,678
And once the sex sucks,

713
00:50:32,847 --> 00:50:36,726
l realise l got nothing
in common with them.

714
00:50:39,007 --> 00:50:42,363
Genevieve and l had
everything in common, till...

715
00:50:49,087 --> 00:50:51,203
Bonnie just got married again.

716
00:50:53,927 --> 00:50:57,761
l shouldn't care, right?
l divorced her twice.

717
00:50:59,567 --> 00:51:01,876
l got no claim on her.

718
00:51:05,087 --> 00:51:06,759
Bitch.

719
00:51:08,847 --> 00:51:10,166
Come here.

720
00:51:14,607 --> 00:51:16,757
Get the fuck over here.

721
00:51:37,567 --> 00:51:39,239
l love you.

722
00:51:45,567 --> 00:51:47,637
l love you, Toby.

723
00:51:59,527 --> 00:52:02,405
- Fuck you! Fuck you!
- What the fuck?

724
00:52:02,607 --> 00:52:03,960
What?

725
00:52:16,487 --> 00:52:19,160
Fuckers. Motherfuckers.

726
00:53:37,087 --> 00:53:41,205
Hannah Bantry in the pantry
Gnawing on a mutton bone

727
00:53:41,367 --> 00:53:44,723
How she gnawed it
How she clawed it

728
00:53:44,887 --> 00:53:47,560
When she found herself alone

729
00:54:18,207 --> 00:54:22,678
At the end of the day,
a bed is the best friend you got.

730
00:54:22,847 --> 00:54:26,556
Sure, the mattress may be lumpy,
the springs may have sprung,

731
00:54:26,727 --> 00:54:31,847
the bed itself may be
in some seedy motel or in Oz.

732
00:54:32,607 --> 00:54:35,838
But the bed, it beckons you.

733
00:54:36,007 --> 00:54:39,317
lt comforts and cradles till you sleep.

734
00:54:39,487 --> 00:54:42,684
And if you're lucky enough to have
the right person lying next to you, shit.

735
00:54:43,327 --> 00:54:46,683
There ain't a reason you got to
get out of that bed come morning.

736
00:54:46,847 --> 00:54:48,326
Good night.

737
00:54:50,087 --> 00:54:54,365
Sleep tight,
don't let the bedbugs bite.

