1
00:00:00,050 --> 00:00:02,210
previously on...

2
00:00:02,390 --> 00:00:04,200
you're awfully brave buyinga place site unseen.

3
00:00:04,240 --> 00:00:05,470
We could tellfrom the advertisement it was just what

4
00:00:05,510 --> 00:00:07,850
we were looking for. Sometimes...

5
00:00:07,870 --> 00:00:09,870
who ever said you were the father?

6
00:00:09,910 --> 00:00:12,650
Didn't you thinkit was strange that you have the only lawn on wisteria lane

7
00:00:12,700 --> 00:00:14,540
that needed to be mowedthree times a week?

8
00:00:14,580 --> 00:00:16,720
I am going to kill you!

9
00:00:16,740 --> 00:00:18,350
The truth about our loved ones...

10
00:00:18,380 --> 00:00:20,360
you asked peterson's wife tomake sure he wouldn't promote me

11
00:00:20,410 --> 00:00:22,500
so I quit. I'm gonna bea stay-at-home dad.

12
00:00:22,540 --> 00:00:24,500
We should... talk about this.

13
00:00:24,530 --> 00:00:25,530
You're goin' back to work.

14
00:00:25,570 --> 00:00:28,150
Can lead you into harm's way.

15
00:00:28,180 --> 00:00:29,480
I think I'm havinga heart attack.

16
00:00:29,510 --> 00:00:32,630
You are gonna come throughthis operation just fine.

17
00:00:32,660 --> 00:00:33,630
Hello?

18
00:00:33,670 --> 00:00:36,510
rex passed awayabout ten minutes ago.

19
00:00:36,570 --> 00:00:38,460
I'm so sorry.

20
00:00:38,500 --> 00:00:40,440
Mr. Delfino took my dad awayto kill him.

21
00:00:40,480 --> 00:00:43,110
Now I'm gonna killmr. Delfino.

22
00:00:46,500 --> 00:00:50,200
It was an accepted fact among the residents of wisteria lane

23
00:00:50,230 --> 00:00:54,180
that ida greenberg liked her liquor.

24
00:00:54,230 --> 00:00:57,960
People had seen her drunk at sewing bees...

25
00:00:58,630 --> 00:01:01,720
the department of motor vehicles...

26
00:01:02,660 --> 00:01:05,770
and the first methodist church.

27
00:01:07,440 --> 00:01:10,440
Ida had tried to quit drinking many times,

28
00:01:10,480 --> 00:01:12,050
but she couldn'T.

29
00:01:12,080 --> 00:01:14,870
Then one night in a moment of despair,

30
00:01:14,900 --> 00:01:16,900
she challenged god

31
00:01:16,930 --> 00:01:20,620
to quench her never-ending thirst.

32
00:01:22,110 --> 00:01:26,390
Luckily for ida,god was listening.

33
00:01:53,060 --> 00:01:55,790
zach,listen to me.

34
00:01:56,780 --> 00:01:58,340
No!

35
00:02:07,440 --> 00:02:10,150
Not so tough now,are you?

36
00:02:12,010 --> 00:02:13,260
Uh! Ow! Oh! Bongo,no!

37
00:02:13,290 --> 00:02:16,240
Bongo!Bongo!

38
00:02:25,770 --> 00:02:29,390
It was at that moment it occurred to ida

39
00:02:29,430 --> 00:02:32,600
god may work in mysterious ways,

40
00:02:32,640 --> 00:02:36,100
but he isn't particularly subtle.

41
00:03:10,120 --> 00:03:15,120
Sync:YTET-fisherchen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-

42
00:03:15,120 --> 00:03:19,070
Desperate Housewives

43
00:03:22,730 --> 00:03:25,010
It had been a year since my death,

44
00:03:25,040 --> 00:03:28,730
and a lot had changed on wisteria lane.

45
00:03:30,630 --> 00:03:33,630
children had learned new games.

46
00:03:36,260 --> 00:03:39,440
New neighbors had moved in.

47
00:03:41,400 --> 00:03:43,390
Old houses had been rebuilt...

48
00:03:43,430 --> 00:03:44,620
I told you guys twice.

49
00:03:44,670 --> 00:03:46,050
Okay,craig,what's goin' on?

50
00:03:46,090 --> 00:03:49,070
And fresh tragedies had occurred.

51
00:03:49,090 --> 00:03:51,380
In one house,

52
00:03:51,450 --> 00:03:55,970
a widow was getting ready to tell her friends of her husband's passing.

53
00:03:56,010 --> 00:03:58,280
But until the time was right,

54
00:03:58,320 --> 00:04:00,380
she would wait.

55
00:04:00,420 --> 00:04:03,300
And life,as it tends to do,

56
00:04:03,340 --> 00:04:05,370
would go on.

57
00:04:05,420 --> 00:04:08,470
I look like hell. I need a hairbrush.

58
00:04:08,500 --> 00:04:11,710
Yeah,um,ahem,that's not gonna help.

59
00:04:13,180 --> 00:04:14,650
Susan,

60
00:04:14,700 --> 00:04:17,700
officer romslove is here for your statement.

61
00:04:17,730 --> 00:04:19,300
Zach young do that?

62
00:04:19,330 --> 00:04:22,680
No. She fell. Bit her lip.
It was an accident.

63
00:04:22,710 --> 00:04:23,930
Okay.

64
00:04:23,960 --> 00:04:26,260
So,uh,walk me through what happened.

65
00:04:26,300 --> 00:04:28,700
well,I went over to mike's to feed the dog.

66
00:04:28,740 --> 00:04:31,550
- I'm sorry?
- Feed the dog.

67
00:04:32,520 --> 00:04:33,960
and I turned around,

68
00:04:33,990 --> 00:04:35,350
and there was zach young--

69
00:04:35,390 --> 00:04:37,410
and that's zach with an "h"--

70
00:04:37,440 --> 00:04:40,170
- pointing a gun at me.
- The doctor said keep that in.

71
00:04:40,200 --> 00:04:42,430
You gotta understand,zach's had a tough time.

72
00:04:42,470 --> 00:04:45,310
- He's got emotional issues--
- 'cause he's crazy.

73
00:04:45,370 --> 00:04:47,410
Still,I don't think he meant to hurt anybody.

74
00:04:47,450 --> 00:04:51,260
Uh,hello! Uh,he was waiting there for you to come home

75
00:04:51,310 --> 00:04:52,700
so he could kill you.

76
00:04:52,740 --> 00:04:54,220
Is that what happened when you got home?

77
00:04:54,260 --> 00:04:55,430
The kid took a shot at you?

78
00:04:55,480 --> 00:04:56,940
Actually,susan fired the gun.

79
00:04:56,990 --> 00:05:00,170
That's because I was wrestling it away from zach

80
00:05:00,200 --> 00:05:02,770
so that he wouldn't shoot you.

81
00:05:03,530 --> 00:05:05,860
Oh,there's blood.

82
00:05:05,900 --> 00:05:08,860
Could we do this later?
She's kind of a mess right now.

83
00:05:08,880 --> 00:05:10,770
Yeah,I think I can fill in the rest for you.

84
00:05:10,810 --> 00:05:12,130
I'd appreciate it.

85
00:05:12,180 --> 00:05:14,830
- You feel better,mrs. Mayer.
- Thanks.

86
00:05:17,200 --> 00:05:19,530
Ow! That hurts.

87
00:05:19,580 --> 00:05:22,120
- I'm gonna get you more ice.
- Okay.

88
00:05:23,110 --> 00:05:23,960
No,I'm tellin' you.

89
00:05:24,010 --> 00:05:26,680
Susan really flew off the handle when she jumped the kid.

90
00:05:26,720 --> 00:05:28,940
So you're saying this was more of a domestic squabble?

91
00:05:28,990 --> 00:05:30,370
Definitely,yeah.

92
00:05:30,420 --> 00:05:32,510
Are we required to press charges?

93
00:05:32,570 --> 00:05:34,050
Well,you're not really required,

94
00:05:34,100 --> 00:05:38,960
but it's something you should really consider when a handgun is involved.

95
00:06:01,910 --> 00:06:03,010
John!

96
00:06:03,050 --> 00:06:06,600
- How did you get in here?
- I know where you keep the key.

97
00:06:07,850 --> 00:06:10,050
- Mimosa?
- No,I'm pregnant,you jackass.

98
00:06:10,100 --> 00:06:11,510
I made yours with seltzer.

99
00:06:11,560 --> 00:06:13,420
Do you have any idea what you've done?

100
00:06:13,470 --> 00:06:14,880
That little stunt you pulled yesterday in the courtroom

101
00:06:14,910 --> 00:06:18,310
could get carlos sent away for eight years.

102
00:06:18,370 --> 00:06:20,950
Yeah,I thought you might be a little mad about that.

103
00:06:20,970 --> 00:06:23,040
But once you calm down,

104
00:06:23,090 --> 00:06:25,380
you'll see that it's just the two of us.

105
00:06:25,410 --> 00:06:27,520
It's gonna be awesome.

106
00:06:29,290 --> 00:06:31,500
you brought luggage?

107
00:06:31,560 --> 00:06:34,140
He's gone. We don't have to sneak around anymore.

108
00:06:34,180 --> 00:06:36,520
We can have a real relationship.

109
00:06:36,810 --> 00:06:38,320
It's what's best for the three of us.

110
00:06:38,360 --> 00:06:42,130
The three of us? How exactly does that benefit carlos?

111
00:06:42,170 --> 00:06:44,730
- I'm talking about my baby.
- You don't know it's your baby.

112
00:06:44,780 --> 00:06:46,260
I don't even know it's your baby.

113
00:06:46,310 --> 00:06:48,710
And I don't wanna know 'cause it doesn't matter.

114
00:06:51,740 --> 00:06:53,980
so what,you don't love me?

115
00:06:54,020 --> 00:06:56,910
Well,up until the point that you told my husband we were having an affair,

116
00:06:56,940 --> 00:06:58,280
I was quite fond of you.

117
00:06:58,330 --> 00:07:00,140
Since then...

118
00:07:00,240 --> 00:07:01,820
not a fan!

119
00:07:08,510 --> 00:07:09,120
Hey.

120
00:07:09,180 --> 00:07:10,250
hey.

121
00:07:10,310 --> 00:07:14,920
Oh,why on earth would you let them finger paint before breakfast?

122
00:07:15,030 --> 00:07:19,890
It's my job to clean that up now,so it's my call,right?

123
00:07:21,580 --> 00:07:22,860
You're right. I'm sorry.

124
00:07:22,900 --> 00:07:24,340
Hey,I thought the meeting wasn't until 1.

125
00:07:24,380 --> 00:07:27,150
Oh,I have a thousand things to do before that--

126
00:07:27,180 --> 00:07:29,250
borrow a decent scarf from bree,

127
00:07:29,300 --> 00:07:31,000
buy a lipstick I don't hate--

128
00:07:31,040 --> 00:07:32,730
- mommy,mommy,look!
- Aah! No! No!

129
00:07:32,780 --> 00:07:34,340
No,nobody touches mommy,okay?

130
00:07:34,390 --> 00:07:36,340
I love you,I love your finger painting,

131
00:07:36,360 --> 00:07:37,970
but if you touch me with those messy hands,

132
00:07:38,010 --> 00:07:39,190
I will cut them off.

133
00:07:39,230 --> 00:07:41,360
Go on. Off. Good.

134
00:07:41,390 --> 00:07:42,830
It's okay.

135
00:07:43,960 --> 00:07:45,480
- A little nervous?
- Who,me?

136
00:07:45,510 --> 00:07:47,200
I've been out of work for seven years,

137
00:07:47,240 --> 00:07:51,070
I'm a woman of a certain age in a business that values youth above all else.

138
00:07:51,110 --> 00:07:54,660
- Why should I be nervous?
- You are experienced.

139
00:07:54,690 --> 00:07:55,940
You are brilliant.

140
00:07:55,990 --> 00:07:59,840
You are going to nail this job interview,okay?

141
00:07:59,890 --> 00:08:01,550
Thank you.Uh,no. I can'T...

142
00:08:01,590 --> 00:08:03,910
you're very... so...

143
00:08:03,960 --> 00:08:05,830
Thank you. Here.

144
00:08:08,070 --> 00:08:09,940
Oh,my cell phone.

145
00:08:29,650 --> 00:08:31,490
lynette,hi,it's bree.

146
00:08:31,550 --> 00:08:33,860
I do hope I'm not calling too early.

147
00:08:34,250 --> 00:08:35,430
Hmm?

148
00:08:35,740 --> 00:08:37,310
Oh,of course you can borrowthat scarf.

149
00:08:37,350 --> 00:08:39,100
I'll press it for you.

150
00:08:39,330 --> 00:08:41,410
Um,I have,uh,some news.

151
00:08:41,480 --> 00:08:43,540
Rex died.

152
00:08:45,530 --> 00:08:47,960
I thought they weregonna operate. What happened?

153
00:08:47,990 --> 00:08:51,680
Apparently rex's heartjust gave out.

154
00:08:51,710 --> 00:08:53,720
Oh,my god.

155
00:08:53,800 --> 00:08:55,230
So when can we see bree?

156
00:08:55,270 --> 00:08:56,620
She saidshe was gonna call.

157
00:08:56,670 --> 00:08:58,850
She's gota lot of things to do,

158
00:08:58,910 --> 00:09:02,020
planning for the funeral,that sort of thing.

159
00:09:02,070 --> 00:09:04,640
She doesn't lookthat busy to me.

160
00:09:09,740 --> 00:09:12,940
Hi,hi. What are youdoing out here?

161
00:09:13,120 --> 00:09:15,170
Oh,I'm just waitingfor,uh,rex's mother.

162
00:09:15,220 --> 00:09:16,820
She's gonna be hereany second.

163
00:09:16,860 --> 00:09:19,280
Honey,we are so sorry.

164
00:09:19,850 --> 00:09:22,260
Oh,do one of youdrink soy milk?

165
00:09:22,290 --> 00:09:23,690
I was cleaning outthe fridge this morning,

166
00:09:23,730 --> 00:09:26,480
and rex is the only onewho drinks it.

167
00:09:26,510 --> 00:09:30,200
I just bought it on friday.I'd hate to throw it away.

168
00:09:32,050 --> 00:09:34,360
What a waste.

169
00:09:35,700 --> 00:09:37,150
Oh,sweetie.

170
00:09:37,190 --> 00:09:38,940
Honey,you can let it out.

171
00:09:38,990 --> 00:09:41,280
No. No,I can't affordto fall apart right now.

172
00:09:41,320 --> 00:09:43,040
Why?

173
00:09:43,080 --> 00:09:45,210
You're about to find out.

174
00:09:46,710 --> 00:09:48,540
bree!

175
00:09:48,590 --> 00:09:50,910
Oh,stop here.This is the house.

176
00:09:50,950 --> 00:09:52,280
Is that...

177
00:09:52,320 --> 00:09:55,380
yes,that is rex's mother.

178
00:10:03,190 --> 00:10:04,760
I can't believe it.

179
00:10:04,790 --> 00:10:07,350
It's likesome hideous nightmare.

180
00:10:07,380 --> 00:10:09,420
My life is over!

181
00:10:09,480 --> 00:10:12,480
My life is over!

182
00:10:26,850 --> 00:10:31,300
it appears there's a 7-year gapsince your last position.

183
00:10:31,340 --> 00:10:33,290
What,did you takesome time off?

184
00:10:33,330 --> 00:10:35,350
I was a stay-at-home mom.

185
00:10:35,370 --> 00:10:37,640
I wish it had been time off.

186
00:10:37,730 --> 00:10:40,540
- Boy or girl?
- A girl...

187
00:10:40,660 --> 00:10:43,480
- and three boys.
- Four kids?

188
00:10:43,520 --> 00:10:45,390
Yeah,of course,they won'tget in the way of the job

189
00:10:45,420 --> 00:10:49,530
because my husband's stayinghome with them from now on.

190
00:10:51,310 --> 00:10:53,850
I knew I could never doboth jobs justice.

191
00:10:53,890 --> 00:10:57,160
That's why I chosenot to have a family.

192
00:10:57,250 --> 00:10:59,290
I didn't want to be oneof those kind of women--

193
00:10:59,330 --> 00:11:02,740
you know,sloughingthings off onto coworkers

194
00:11:02,770 --> 00:11:06,350
because ofa pediatrician appointment or a dance recital.

195
00:11:06,380 --> 00:11:10,720
I get really neuroticabout putting people out.

196
00:11:11,500 --> 00:11:14,470
With all due respect,nina,won't be an issue.

197
00:11:14,500 --> 00:11:15,980
I can leave home at home.

198
00:11:16,020 --> 00:11:19,500
And it's not gonna breakyour heart
to leave thosesad little faces behind?

199
00:11:19,560 --> 00:11:21,540
are you kidding?

200
00:11:21,570 --> 00:11:23,380
This office is paradise--

201
00:11:23,410 --> 00:11:26,100
grown-ups talking aboutgrown-up things.

202
00:11:26,120 --> 00:11:29,410
No screaming,no vomiting,no boogers under the table.

203
00:11:29,450 --> 00:11:32,380
You're gonna have todrag me outta here kicking and screaming--

204
00:11:32,420 --> 00:11:35,620
weekends,holidays,whenever.

205
00:11:37,120 --> 00:11:39,980
All right,ed wants to makethe final decision.

206
00:11:40,000 --> 00:11:44,370
So I willbring you back tomorrow at 3 for a follow-up.

207
00:11:44,410 --> 00:11:46,510
Well,that--that sounds great. Thank you--

208
00:11:46,540 --> 00:11:50,000
lynette,be early.Show me something.

209
00:11:50,640 --> 00:11:52,570
Okay.

210
00:11:53,570 --> 00:11:55,680
No way.Dad did not have a teddy bear.

211
00:11:55,710 --> 00:11:57,430
He most certainly did.

212
00:11:57,490 --> 00:11:59,630
Oh,that was doolittle.

213
00:11:59,680 --> 00:12:02,410
Your father never wentanywhere without him.

214
00:12:06,040 --> 00:12:08,200
Here's your tea,phyllis.

215
00:12:09,190 --> 00:12:11,030
Oh.

216
00:12:11,120 --> 00:12:12,130
Look,bree.

217
00:12:12,160 --> 00:12:16,530
This was the tiethat rex wore
when he graduatedfrom prep school.

218
00:12:17,160 --> 00:12:19,750
I think he should wear it.

219
00:12:19,780 --> 00:12:22,610
You know,for the funeral?

220
00:12:22,640 --> 00:12:25,140
Phyllis,that's an orange tie.

221
00:12:25,160 --> 00:12:27,510
Well,those werehis school colors--green and orange.

222
00:12:27,540 --> 00:12:31,700
Well,um,he's being buriedin a blue suit.

223
00:12:32,590 --> 00:12:36,370
maybe he could be buriedin a different suit.

224
00:12:36,420 --> 00:12:39,470
I don't think so,but thank you,though.

225
00:12:40,510 --> 00:12:43,290
You,uh,you keptdad's old comic books?

226
00:12:43,330 --> 00:12:45,550
Oh,yes,I kept everything.

227
00:12:45,640 --> 00:12:47,160
Look here.

228
00:12:48,250 --> 00:12:53,980
I even keptthe dirty magazine
that he hidunder his mattress.

229
00:12:54,300 --> 00:12:58,250
He didn't thinkI knew about it,but I did.

230
00:12:59,920 --> 00:13:01,970
well,looks like dadwas into big breasts.

231
00:13:02,010 --> 00:13:03,130
Oh,yes.

232
00:13:03,190 --> 00:13:06,800
That's why I was surprisedwhen he married your mother.

233
00:13:15,680 --> 00:13:18,490
So you're just not gonnatalk to me,is that it?

234
00:13:20,830 --> 00:13:22,390
Fine.

235
00:13:22,810 --> 00:13:25,620
I don't need to talk.

236
00:13:30,040 --> 00:13:32,360
Okay. Yes,I hada little affair.

237
00:13:32,390 --> 00:13:34,870
It wasn't the best thing to do,and I'm not proud of it.

238
00:13:34,900 --> 00:13:36,360
But it's not the worst thingthat could have happened.

239
00:13:36,400 --> 00:13:38,590
Nobody died.

240
00:13:39,560 --> 00:13:41,960
Oh,don't be such a martyr,carlos.

241
00:13:42,000 --> 00:13:44,390
Okay,it takes two people.

242
00:13:44,450 --> 00:13:46,520
How many times did you go offon your little business trips

243
00:13:46,570 --> 00:13:48,400
and leave me alone?

244
00:13:48,450 --> 00:13:50,740
See,so technically,you cheated,too.

245
00:13:50,790 --> 00:13:53,790
It's just your mistresswas your work.

246
00:13:53,820 --> 00:13:56,150
No,okay.That was a stretch.I'm sorry.

247
00:13:56,200 --> 00:14:00,220
Carlos,wait! Come back.Look,I wanna start over.

248
00:14:00,240 --> 00:14:02,100
We're gonna have a baby.

249
00:14:02,140 --> 00:14:04,960
Isn't thatwhat you always wanted?

250
00:14:05,440 --> 00:14:06,520
Carlos,wait!

251
00:14:06,550 --> 00:14:08,700
I said I was sorryand I love you!

252
00:14:08,740 --> 00:14:11,410
What more do you want?!

253
00:14:11,980 --> 00:14:15,250
I want a paternity test.

254
00:14:22,320 --> 00:14:23,700
Mrs. Applewhite,hi.

255
00:14:23,740 --> 00:14:25,550
I am bree van de kamp,

256
00:14:25,590 --> 00:14:27,970
and this ismy daughter danielle.

257
00:14:28,010 --> 00:14:29,340
- Hello.
- hi.

258
00:14:29,390 --> 00:14:31,460
Hey,I'm matthew.This is my son.

259
00:14:31,490 --> 00:14:34,870
Hi. I would have been oversooner to introduce myself,

260
00:14:34,910 --> 00:14:38,380
but I'm afraid there's beena death in my family.

261
00:14:38,420 --> 00:14:39,350
My dad.

262
00:14:39,390 --> 00:14:41,610
I'm so sorry.I lost my dad,too.

263
00:14:41,660 --> 00:14:43,910
I know what you must begoing through right now.

264
00:14:43,960 --> 00:14:44,770
Thank you.

265
00:14:44,800 --> 00:14:48,300
Anyway,I'm afraidthat my visit has an ulterior motive.

266
00:14:48,350 --> 00:14:50,710
The organist at our churchis on vacation,

267
00:14:50,760 --> 00:14:54,470
and edie britt mentioned that you used to bea concert pianist,and--

268
00:14:54,520 --> 00:14:56,480
I would be honoredto play for you.

269
00:14:56,510 --> 00:14:58,430
Why don't I bringsome sheet music over later

270
00:14:58,470 --> 00:15:00,100
and we can plansome selections?

271
00:15:00,140 --> 00:15:04,020
Thank you. That's just a hugeweight off my shoulders.

272
00:15:04,060 --> 00:15:08,050
Oh,these are for you.
- How sweet.

273
00:15:08,160 --> 00:15:12,410
Bree,we widowshave to stick together.

274
00:15:13,550 --> 00:15:15,350
Bye.

275
00:15:23,600 --> 00:15:25,670
Pretendingyour father's dead?

276
00:15:25,700 --> 00:15:27,270
Don't you find thata little morbid?

277
00:15:27,310 --> 00:15:29,070
Well,I just thought it couldhelp our cover story,okay?

278
00:15:29,100 --> 00:15:31,460
Just,you know,win 'em over.

279
00:15:31,730 --> 00:15:35,830
Oh,sweetie.I know you meant well.

280
00:15:36,040 --> 00:15:40,400
But in the future,you leavethe cleverness to me.

281
00:15:49,440 --> 00:15:51,610
Since when are we protectedby dorset security?

282
00:15:51,650 --> 00:15:54,700
Oh,we're not.It's a deterrentin case zach comes back.

283
00:15:54,740 --> 00:15:57,820
I told mikeI didn't sleep last night,so he got me this sign.

284
00:15:57,860 --> 00:15:59,230
That guy is so supportive.

285
00:15:59,260 --> 00:16:02,810
You know he's out right nowin a ride-along with the police searching for zach?

286
00:16:02,840 --> 00:16:04,260
- Really?
- Yeah.

287
00:16:04,300 --> 00:16:07,190
He's determined to seethat kid behind bars.

288
00:16:07,240 --> 00:16:09,150
So tomorrow at school I want you to leteverybody know

289
00:16:09,190 --> 00:16:11,360
that we got this new,expensive security system.

290
00:16:11,390 --> 00:16:13,300
- Mom,just--
- work itinto the conversation.

291
00:16:13,340 --> 00:16:15,100
- You know,put the word out there
- I've gotta tell you something.

292
00:16:15,140 --> 00:16:18,130
- Emphasize the motion detectors.
- Mom,stop,stop.Listen.

293
00:16:18,160 --> 00:16:19,980
What? What is it?

294
00:16:20,020 --> 00:16:22,540
Yesterday I overheardmike telling that cop

295
00:16:22,580 --> 00:16:25,540
that he didn't wannapress charges against zach.

296
00:16:25,720 --> 00:16:27,890
He made the whole thingsound like it was your fault.

297
00:16:27,920 --> 00:16:29,790
My fault?

298
00:16:38,800 --> 00:16:41,440
Hi. Uh,I needa paternity test.

299
00:16:41,480 --> 00:16:43,570
Well,we'll just schedule youfor an exam.

300
00:16:43,620 --> 00:16:46,890
Oh,no,no. I-I don't needto take a test.

301
00:16:47,640 --> 00:16:53,740
I am just tryingto reassure my husband of what I knowis true in my heart.

302
00:16:53,800 --> 00:16:56,960
So if you could just slip mesomeone else's test results,

303
00:16:56,990 --> 00:16:58,300
I could make my own.

304
00:16:58,350 --> 00:17:01,070
I got photoshopfor christmas.

305
00:17:02,940 --> 00:17:04,870
Oh,come on.

306
00:17:04,950 --> 00:17:07,680
You look likea fun-loving girl.

307
00:17:07,710 --> 00:17:11,910
I am sure you've been in a couple hairy situationsof your own.

308
00:17:13,330 --> 00:17:15,650
Just because I chooseto express myself

309
00:17:15,680 --> 00:17:18,280
doesn't mean thatI condone adultery.

310
00:17:18,310 --> 00:17:19,850
Sorry.

311
00:17:36,980 --> 00:17:39,720
Paternity test results?

312
00:17:39,870 --> 00:17:43,370
I know.I'm in the same situation.

313
00:17:43,400 --> 00:17:45,070
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.

314
00:17:45,100 --> 00:17:46,850
I just found outthe clinic screwed up

315
00:17:46,880 --> 00:17:50,300
and gave me an eggthat belonged to some lesbian.

316
00:17:50,490 --> 00:17:52,940
It was supposed to beimplanted in her lover,

317
00:17:52,970 --> 00:17:54,970
and nowmy husband's freaking out

318
00:17:55,000 --> 00:17:58,770
because he thinks thatour baby's gonna be gay!

319
00:17:59,630 --> 00:18:03,730
Okay. We're inslightly different situations.

320
00:18:03,750 --> 00:18:06,440
But do you wanna geta cup of coffee and talk about it?

321
00:18:06,470 --> 00:18:09,920
Yeah. That'd be nice.Thanks.

322
00:18:10,060 --> 00:18:12,150
Yeah. Us girlshave to stick together.

323
00:18:12,200 --> 00:18:16,130
We shouldn't letthat stupid piece of paper ruin our life.

324
00:18:16,170 --> 00:18:17,960
Yeah!

325
00:18:24,480 --> 00:18:26,810
Obviously,I've known rex for years,

326
00:18:26,860 --> 00:18:28,520
but when it comesto writing a eulogy,

327
00:18:28,550 --> 00:18:31,570
I like as much inputfrom the family as possible.

328
00:18:31,600 --> 00:18:34,360
Oh. Well,um,what kind of input?

329
00:18:34,390 --> 00:18:36,310
Oh,well,he means anecdotes,

330
00:18:36,350 --> 00:18:38,080
little stories.

331
00:18:38,120 --> 00:18:39,840
Isn't that what you mean,reverend?

332
00:18:39,880 --> 00:18:41,760
Well,yes,but,uh,also--

333
00:18:41,800 --> 00:18:43,680
I thought thatyou might need some help,

334
00:18:43,720 --> 00:18:46,660
so last nightI stayed up all night

335
00:18:46,700 --> 00:18:50,240
and tried to rememberfunny things

336
00:18:50,280 --> 00:18:54,730
and moments that said so muchabout rex as a person.

337
00:18:54,770 --> 00:18:58,040
My. How--how many pagesdo you have there?

338
00:18:58,080 --> 00:19:00,070
15.

339
00:19:06,520 --> 00:19:09,980
well,you're hardlygoing to have to write anything at all,reverend.

340
00:19:10,020 --> 00:19:13,010
Some of those anecdotesare just priceless.

341
00:19:13,050 --> 00:19:17,160
Phyllis,these are all thingsthat happened to rex before he went to college.

342
00:19:17,220 --> 00:19:18,010
So?

343
00:19:18,040 --> 00:19:20,190
Well,don't you think it'd benice if reverend devoted

344
00:19:20,210 --> 00:19:22,690
part of the eulogy to his lifeafter he was married?

345
00:19:22,720 --> 00:19:24,730
Oh,well,yes,of course.

346
00:19:24,750 --> 00:19:27,780
The reverend will mentionthat part of his life.

347
00:19:27,820 --> 00:19:29,100
He's going to do morethan mention it.

348
00:19:29,140 --> 00:19:30,370
That's the parthe'll focus on.

349
00:19:30,420 --> 00:19:34,430
In fact,I think three anecdotesfrom rex's childhood is more than enough.

350
00:19:34,450 --> 00:19:37,480
Um,that--that seems fair.

351
00:19:39,980 --> 00:19:42,720
Well,whatever you thinkis appropriate.

352
00:19:42,740 --> 00:19:43,340
Fine.

353
00:19:43,410 --> 00:19:46,800
I just thoughtif we were going to focus on a time in rex's life,

354
00:19:46,830 --> 00:19:51,010
that we might as well focuson the happiest time.

355
00:19:54,150 --> 00:19:55,570
let's talk flowers.

356
00:19:55,620 --> 00:19:57,760
Now I knowlilies are traditional,

357
00:19:57,800 --> 00:20:01,480
but I think I can get youa deal on some white roses.

358
00:20:01,520 --> 00:20:04,950
Reverend,if you don't call her on that incrediblyinsensitive comment,

359
00:20:05,000 --> 00:20:06,140
I'm gonna lose it.

360
00:20:06,170 --> 00:20:08,170
I'm sure she didn't mean itthe way it sounded.

361
00:20:08,200 --> 00:20:10,580
- I knew exactlywhat I was saying.
- Ladies--

362
00:20:10,610 --> 00:20:13,500
the happiest timein rex's life was not his childhood.

363
00:20:13,520 --> 00:20:15,930
He loved being a husband,and he loved being a father.

364
00:20:15,970 --> 00:20:18,700
Well,he may have lovedbeing a father,

365
00:20:18,720 --> 00:20:22,080
but your marriagewas a disaster.

366
00:20:22,130 --> 00:20:26,230
Phyllis,is there somethingyou'd like to say?

367
00:20:26,290 --> 00:20:30,050
You made the last yearsof rex's life miserable,

368
00:20:30,100 --> 00:20:32,340
and now he's dead,

369
00:20:32,360 --> 00:20:37,030
and he'll never haveanother chance at happiness.

370
00:20:38,530 --> 00:20:41,780
You are no longerinvited to the funeral.

371
00:20:41,810 --> 00:20:42,710
What?

372
00:20:42,750 --> 00:20:45,370
- You're not serious.
- Oh,yes,I am.

373
00:20:45,420 --> 00:20:47,300
I am going to hire security,

374
00:20:47,350 --> 00:20:49,120
and those security menare going to have sticks,

375
00:20:49,160 --> 00:20:51,470
and if you so much asset foot in that sanctuary,

376
00:20:51,510 --> 00:20:55,010
they will be instructedto beat you with those sticks.

377
00:20:55,040 --> 00:20:56,130
Bree,this is your grief talking--

378
00:20:56,160 --> 00:20:58,670
reverend,if you don'tback me up on this,so help me,

379
00:20:58,710 --> 00:21:00,740
I will pull the funeral out of your church.

380
00:21:00,760 --> 00:21:02,640
- Bree!
- I am not kidding.

381
00:21:02,680 --> 00:21:06,840
I will go nondenominationalso fast,it will make your head spin.

382
00:21:19,090 --> 00:21:22,950
Susan,I heardwhat happened with zach.

383
00:21:22,980 --> 00:21:24,070
How are you doing?

384
00:21:24,100 --> 00:21:26,560
- Fine. Is mike here?
- Inside.

385
00:21:26,600 --> 00:21:28,760
Jeez. You must have beenterrified.

386
00:21:28,780 --> 00:21:31,530
I mean,he put poor feliciain the hospital.

387
00:21:31,540 --> 00:21:33,720
- Did he pistol-whip you?
- No.

388
00:21:33,760 --> 00:21:36,200
Oh,come on.You can tell me.

389
00:21:36,230 --> 00:21:39,070
- Did he slap you around?
- No.

390
00:21:39,110 --> 00:21:41,510
Well,don't get me wrong.I'm thrilled that you're okay.

391
00:21:41,540 --> 00:21:43,980
It's just that when someoneholds someone else hostage,

392
00:21:44,030 --> 00:21:47,370
they usuallyrough 'em up a little.

393
00:21:48,090 --> 00:21:50,900
It wasn't like that.

394
00:21:52,900 --> 00:21:55,740
- Not even a little kicking?
- Edie...

395
00:21:57,500 --> 00:21:59,510
someone to see you.

396
00:21:59,710 --> 00:22:00,950
- Well,hey,how's it goin'?
- Good.

397
00:22:00,990 --> 00:22:02,070
So there'sa rumor going around

398
00:22:02,100 --> 00:22:04,740
that you don't wannapress charges against zach.

399
00:22:04,790 --> 00:22:06,790
Is that true?

400
00:22:07,050 --> 00:22:09,120
Yeah.

401
00:22:10,040 --> 00:22:14,930
Wow. Um... I find that...confusing.

402
00:22:14,970 --> 00:22:16,640
Look,if we makea big deal out of this,

403
00:22:16,670 --> 00:22:18,450
he could end upgoing to prison.

404
00:22:18,490 --> 00:22:22,100
He held a gun to my face,so I'm thinking,"good."

405
00:22:22,130 --> 00:22:24,880
I've been to prison.He couldn't handle it.

406
00:22:24,920 --> 00:22:27,210
- Who cares?
- I care.

407
00:22:27,260 --> 00:22:28,910
Well,you should caremore about me.

408
00:22:28,960 --> 00:22:31,210
I'm your girlfriend.We're moving in together.

409
00:22:31,240 --> 00:22:33,060
He's just a neighbor.You don't even know zach.

410
00:22:33,100 --> 00:22:35,220
I know enough about him to knowthat deep down,he's a good kid.

411
00:22:35,260 --> 00:22:37,540
Mike,he wanted to kill you.

412
00:22:37,580 --> 00:22:39,070
But he didn'T.

413
00:22:39,110 --> 00:22:41,290
You never asked me whyzach wanted to shoot you.

414
00:22:41,330 --> 00:22:43,990
Aren't you curious?Does it matter?

415
00:22:44,030 --> 00:22:47,530
Zach said you kidnappedhis father so you could kill him.

416
00:22:47,560 --> 00:22:49,090
I didn't kill paul young.

417
00:22:49,120 --> 00:22:54,060
I didn't think you did.Now tell me why zach does.

418
00:22:59,550 --> 00:23:04,700
I found some evidencethat suggested that paul murdered deirdre.

419
00:23:04,730 --> 00:23:06,940
16 years agodeirdre had a baby,

420
00:23:06,980 --> 00:23:09,340
and paul and mary alice youngkidnapped him

421
00:23:09,370 --> 00:23:10,810
and raised him as their own.

422
00:23:10,830 --> 00:23:14,540
Deirdre tracked him down hereto wisteria lane and demanded her baby back.

423
00:23:14,580 --> 00:23:17,010
So paul killed her?

424
00:23:17,090 --> 00:23:20,200
Actually,it was mary alice.

425
00:23:21,210 --> 00:23:23,270
Oh,my god.

426
00:23:23,380 --> 00:23:25,060
Mike?

427
00:23:25,130 --> 00:23:27,070
I answered your phone.

428
00:23:27,130 --> 00:23:29,240
It's the police.

429
00:23:29,590 --> 00:23:31,500
Yeah. Delfino.

430
00:23:32,420 --> 00:23:34,240
You did?

431
00:23:34,310 --> 00:23:37,290
Okay,I can be therein 20 minutes.

432
00:23:40,330 --> 00:23:42,560
Zach's dead.

433
00:23:44,020 --> 00:23:46,820
They want me to comeidentify the body.

434
00:24:00,760 --> 00:24:02,640
Thanks for coming down.

435
00:24:02,770 --> 00:24:05,210
Since the kid's fatheris missing,

436
00:24:05,270 --> 00:24:07,780
we didn't knowwho else to call.

437
00:24:08,590 --> 00:24:12,460
So... you folks ready?

438
00:24:27,220 --> 00:24:28,930
that's not zach.

439
00:24:28,960 --> 00:24:30,440
You're sure?

440
00:24:30,490 --> 00:24:32,010
He had a gun in my facefor six hours.

441
00:24:32,040 --> 00:24:34,420
I know what he looks like.

442
00:24:51,980 --> 00:24:55,030
- Can you give us a minute?
- Sure.

443
00:25:05,360 --> 00:25:09,890
- Zach is your son,isn't he?
- Yeah.

444
00:25:09,940 --> 00:25:12,570
I'm pretty sure.

445
00:25:12,910 --> 00:25:15,590
How long have you known?

446
00:25:15,910 --> 00:25:18,560
Paul young told me.

447
00:25:20,470 --> 00:25:22,340
Deirdre got pregnantbefore I went to jail

448
00:25:22,370 --> 00:25:27,180
and,um,told meshe had an abortion.

449
00:25:27,940 --> 00:25:29,870
Guess she lied.

450
00:25:29,900 --> 00:25:31,740
I see.

451
00:25:34,670 --> 00:25:37,710
When I took paulout to the desert,

452
00:25:37,840 --> 00:25:41,210
and I was so angry,I just wanted to hurt him...

453
00:25:42,200 --> 00:25:45,080
the way they hurt deirdre.

454
00:25:45,660 --> 00:25:46,890
But then when he told me

455
00:25:46,930 --> 00:25:50,660
that he and mary alice hadtaken care of deirdre's baby--

456
00:25:50,710 --> 00:25:53,510
my baby...

457
00:25:54,220 --> 00:25:57,420
that rage just went away.

458
00:26:00,680 --> 00:26:04,890
Kept me from doingsomething really stupid.

459
00:26:12,240 --> 00:26:15,350
I'm gonna take a cab home,okay?

460
00:26:23,290 --> 00:26:26,150
Mom,grandma's leaving,all right?You have to talk to her.

461
00:26:26,190 --> 00:26:28,470
No,I don'T. If you heardthe things that she said to me--

462
00:26:28,510 --> 00:26:31,040
look,I'm sure she wasa real bitch,okay?

463
00:26:31,080 --> 00:26:35,200
But she's family,so that makes her our bitch.

464
00:26:35,520 --> 00:26:37,450
Let her say good-byeto dad.

465
00:26:37,490 --> 00:26:40,200
She went out of her wayto be cruel to me.

466
00:26:40,240 --> 00:26:41,520
I don't want her at the funeral.

467
00:26:41,560 --> 00:26:45,270
Mom,if you don't let grandmacome,I will never forgive you.

468
00:26:45,310 --> 00:26:48,010
Did I ask for your help?

469
00:26:49,960 --> 00:26:52,990
You know dadwould want her there.

470
00:27:04,430 --> 00:27:07,550
It's true rex and I did nothave the perfect marriage,

471
00:27:07,590 --> 00:27:11,460
but for 18 yearsI tried my very best,

472
00:27:11,490 --> 00:27:14,870
and for that I am entitledto your respect.

473
00:27:16,710 --> 00:27:19,030
Of course you are.

474
00:27:19,270 --> 00:27:21,900
Of course I respect you.

475
00:27:21,930 --> 00:27:26,030
Well,then why did you saythose things to me?

476
00:27:26,080 --> 00:27:29,960
I guess I thought it would beeasier to be angry at you

477
00:27:30,000 --> 00:27:33,230
than to be angry with rex.

478
00:27:34,040 --> 00:27:36,870
I mean,what was he thinking,

479
00:27:36,910 --> 00:27:38,410
leaving me?

480
00:27:42,990 --> 00:27:46,410
I do want you to cometo the funeral.

481
00:27:47,900 --> 00:27:51,310
you don't know whatthat means to me,bree.

482
00:27:51,370 --> 00:27:53,360
Thank you.

483
00:27:57,220 --> 00:28:00,180
Someone should get my luggage.

484
00:28:03,970 --> 00:28:06,950
Okay,let's get outta here.Tom?

485
00:28:06,990 --> 00:28:08,940
- yeah?
- Mom.

486
00:28:10,550 --> 00:28:12,090
What's the matter?

487
00:28:12,140 --> 00:28:16,210
My back--I threw it out. I washolding parker upside down.

488
00:28:16,240 --> 00:28:20,270
Okay. Come on.Give me your feet.

489
00:28:21,460 --> 00:28:23,470
how's that?Is that better?

490
00:28:24,540 --> 00:28:26,640
honey,can you push the interview?

491
00:28:26,660 --> 00:28:27,820
Because I don't thinkI'm gonna be able

492
00:28:27,850 --> 00:28:29,290
to take care of penny like this.

493
00:28:29,320 --> 00:28:29,980
Don't do this to me.

494
00:28:30,010 --> 00:28:31,420
I don't have timeto make a phone call,

495
00:28:31,450 --> 00:28:33,610
and I promised that womanI would not let the kids

496
00:28:33,640 --> 00:28:35,290
interfere with this job.

497
00:28:35,330 --> 00:28:37,880
But that wasa stupid promise.

498
00:28:38,270 --> 00:28:41,350
Remember that time whenyou were away in tucson,and I had a 104 fever,

499
00:28:41,380 --> 00:28:44,430
but I still managed to take the kids trick-or-treating?

500
00:28:45,130 --> 00:28:46,250
honey...

501
00:28:46,290 --> 00:28:48,150
I don't think that's helping.

502
00:28:48,910 --> 00:28:51,980
Tom,being a mom is likebeing an E.R. Doctor.

503
00:28:52,020 --> 00:28:56,870
There are no days off,so get up! Get up!

504
00:28:57,170 --> 00:28:58,920
Okay.

505
00:29:00,560 --> 00:29:03,150
Jeez,are you crying?

506
00:29:03,190 --> 00:29:05,310
Just a little.

507
00:29:05,440 --> 00:29:08,360
I'll be fine. You just... go.Just go.

508
00:29:12,030 --> 00:29:14,670
oh,for god sakes.

509
00:29:16,950 --> 00:29:18,840
Give 'em hell,honey.

510
00:29:18,920 --> 00:29:21,110
You...

511
00:29:32,270 --> 00:29:35,100
hi,mrs. Scavo.You can wait inside.

512
00:29:35,140 --> 00:29:36,890
- They'll be right in.
- Great.

513
00:29:36,920 --> 00:29:38,610
Listen,uh...

514
00:29:38,640 --> 00:29:40,010
- stu.
- Stu.

515
00:29:40,050 --> 00:29:42,340
You look like a bright,uh,responsible young man,

516
00:29:42,370 --> 00:29:45,520
and I bet you just love kids.Am I right?

517
00:29:56,780 --> 00:29:58,900
Ed ferrara,lynette scavo.

518
00:29:58,940 --> 00:30:00,350
Thanks so muchfor having me in.

519
00:30:00,400 --> 00:30:01,780
Nice to meet you.Please,sit.

520
00:30:01,820 --> 00:30:03,600
Thank you.

521
00:30:04,870 --> 00:30:07,440
We're gonna have tomake this quick.

522
00:30:07,690 --> 00:30:10,260
I gotta leave in fiveto catch a plane.

523
00:30:10,290 --> 00:30:13,100
I got celtic ticketson the floor.

524
00:30:15,160 --> 00:30:17,320
This is a great r閟um?

525
00:30:17,440 --> 00:30:20,220
I see you workedwith the donahues.

526
00:30:20,330 --> 00:30:23,920
You know,I snakedthe oslo candy account from 'em last year.

527
00:30:24,830 --> 00:30:26,510
So you've donea lot of copy work?

528
00:30:26,540 --> 00:30:30,080
I have. But when I movedover to cenn and simmons,

529
00:30:30,110 --> 00:30:35,100
um,I got to doa broader range of campaigns.

530
00:30:37,760 --> 00:30:38,890
T...

531
00:30:38,970 --> 00:30:41,440
uh,V...

532
00:30:41,490 --> 00:30:44,090
and... uh...

533
00:30:44,130 --> 00:30:46,160
radio...

534
00:30:46,200 --> 00:30:49,240
uh,billboards.

535
00:30:50,930 --> 00:30:53,110
could you excuse mefor a minute?

536
00:30:53,170 --> 00:30:54,620
Please?

537
00:30:54,800 --> 00:30:56,470
What's going on?

538
00:30:56,510 --> 00:30:58,780
I have no idea.

539
00:30:58,830 --> 00:31:00,550
Stu,you are an idiot.

540
00:31:00,610 --> 00:31:03,620
You're an idiot,an absolute idiot.

541
00:31:04,200 --> 00:31:04,950
Hi.

542
00:31:05,000 --> 00:31:07,540
Ha! Guys,I'd like youto meet penny.

543
00:31:07,570 --> 00:31:09,290
She gives meall my best ideas.

544
00:31:09,320 --> 00:31:11,070
You brought your babyto the interview.

545
00:31:11,110 --> 00:31:13,600
- It won't be an ongoing thing.
- You bet it won'T.

546
00:31:13,640 --> 00:31:14,710
Nina,it's fine.

547
00:31:14,770 --> 00:31:16,700
Any chance we can getthat little lady to be quiet?

548
00:31:16,730 --> 00:31:18,220
Not until I change her diaper.

549
00:31:18,260 --> 00:31:20,150
Could you just give metwo minutes?

550
00:31:20,190 --> 00:31:23,580
Sorry. Plane.Well...

551
00:31:25,500 --> 00:31:27,980
then watch me multitask.

552
00:31:28,010 --> 00:31:29,290
Here's how I see it.

553
00:31:29,330 --> 00:31:31,240
You guys runa really good shop,

554
00:31:31,280 --> 00:31:33,730
but if you want your agencyto go to the next level,

555
00:31:33,750 --> 00:31:35,570
you have to focuson two things.

556
00:31:35,610 --> 00:31:37,950
First,you've gotta winsome awards.

557
00:31:37,990 --> 00:31:41,260
Do some P.S.A.S,pro bono stuff,whatever it takes,

558
00:31:41,300 --> 00:31:44,560
because whetherthey admit it or not,

559
00:31:44,600 --> 00:31:46,860
clients care aboutwhat's in your trophy case.

560
00:31:46,890 --> 00:31:48,730
Two--your web site.

561
00:31:48,770 --> 00:31:50,810
It's the first thinga client's gonna look at,

562
00:31:50,860 --> 00:31:53,770
and it's hard to navigate.There's no site map.

563
00:31:53,810 --> 00:31:57,140
It just wasn't builtfor people who grow up without computers.

564
00:31:57,180 --> 00:31:59,790
There. And third...

565
00:32:00,130 --> 00:32:01,590
I don't have a third.

566
00:32:01,640 --> 00:32:05,830
Yeah,so that'S... it.

567
00:32:06,640 --> 00:32:07,640
Okay.

568
00:32:07,680 --> 00:32:09,010
You're in.

569
00:32:09,060 --> 00:32:11,310
- Seriously?
- Yeah.

570
00:32:12,320 --> 00:32:14,830
Take the office across the hall.I gotta run.

571
00:32:17,520 --> 00:32:19,690
Well,all right!

572
00:32:24,800 --> 00:32:27,080
Okay,obviously,I'm gonna clean that up.

573
00:32:27,640 --> 00:32:31,750
Here it is in black and white.It's your kid.

574
00:32:38,540 --> 00:32:40,660
What?Why aren't you smiling?

575
00:32:40,690 --> 00:32:41,860
It's not enough.

576
00:32:41,900 --> 00:32:43,250
What do you want,a father's day card?

577
00:32:43,290 --> 00:32:46,000
You knew the one thingthat I demanded was fidelity,

578
00:32:46,030 --> 00:32:47,790
and you still went outand screwed around behind my back.

579
00:32:47,830 --> 00:32:49,970
You knew the one thingI didn't want was a child,

580
00:32:49,990 --> 00:32:51,690
and you still tricked me into getting pregnant.

581
00:32:51,720 --> 00:32:52,470
It's not the same thing.

582
00:32:52,510 --> 00:32:55,350
Damn straight.What you did was worse.

583
00:32:58,670 --> 00:33:00,630
We're not very nice people,are we?

584
00:33:00,670 --> 00:33:02,660
No,we're not.

585
00:33:02,980 --> 00:33:04,110
Oh,when we got married,

586
00:33:04,150 --> 00:33:06,910
I thought we were gonna beso happy.

587
00:33:06,940 --> 00:33:08,940
Me too.

588
00:33:12,470 --> 00:33:15,890
Look on the bright side.At least we're still rich.

589
00:33:16,120 --> 00:33:18,750
Thank god for that.

590
00:33:26,610 --> 00:33:29,590
So it occurred to me...

591
00:33:31,160 --> 00:33:35,250
that I was really rudeat the morgue.

592
00:33:37,520 --> 00:33:41,200
When you told me about zach,I was so busy freaking out,

593
00:33:41,230 --> 00:33:44,230
I never actuallycongratulated you.

594
00:33:44,260 --> 00:33:45,600
Congratulated me?

595
00:33:45,640 --> 00:33:48,870
Yeah,I know how muchyou've always wanted a child,

596
00:33:48,910 --> 00:33:51,030
and now you have one.

597
00:33:51,120 --> 00:33:51,880
Thanks.

598
00:33:51,930 --> 00:33:54,770
Obviously,um,it was quite a shock,

599
00:33:55,990 --> 00:34:00,360
but it's good newsany way you slice it.

600
00:34:01,820 --> 00:34:03,010
What's wrong?

601
00:34:03,050 --> 00:34:06,370
So naturally you'll bewanting to...

602
00:34:06,390 --> 00:34:09,570
have a relationship with him,and that takes time,

603
00:34:09,610 --> 00:34:11,190
- a lot of time.
- Susan--

604
00:34:11,230 --> 00:34:15,740
and out of all the mixed-upteenagers in the world,

605
00:34:15,780 --> 00:34:20,720
zach is just the one kidthat I can't be around.

606
00:34:20,910 --> 00:34:23,870
I can't have juliearound him.

607
00:34:23,920 --> 00:34:28,500
So,um,what I'm tryingto say is...

608
00:34:29,060 --> 00:34:30,400
we can't move in together.

609
00:34:30,450 --> 00:34:32,850
But I am so happy for you.

610
00:34:33,010 --> 00:34:35,950
Really,you have a child,and that is good for you.

611
00:34:35,990 --> 00:34:36,920
Isn't there any way--

612
00:34:36,960 --> 00:34:39,630
no. No,I...

613
00:34:39,750 --> 00:34:41,950
so sorry.

614
00:34:42,160 --> 00:34:43,730
I'll--I'll,um,

615
00:34:43,770 --> 00:34:46,020
I'll see you around.

616
00:36:04,160 --> 00:36:06,480
today we've come togetherto celebrate the life

617
00:36:06,520 --> 00:36:08,860
of dr. Rex van de kamp...

618
00:36:08,920 --> 00:36:11,930
what is he wearing?

619
00:36:11,960 --> 00:36:13,510
What?

620
00:36:13,640 --> 00:36:14,760
I left him an hour ago,

621
00:36:14,790 --> 00:36:17,080
and he was wearingralph lauren.

622
00:36:17,170 --> 00:36:20,080
But it's what rexwould have wanted.

623
00:36:20,120 --> 00:36:23,290
He loved that prep school.

624
00:36:23,630 --> 00:36:25,770
...But whichever coathe was wearing,

625
00:36:25,820 --> 00:36:28,510
rex always broughtan irresistible enthusiasm

626
00:36:28,540 --> 00:36:30,620
and a single-mindeddetermination to...

627
00:36:30,650 --> 00:36:34,100
so as we mourn the passingof rex van de kamp,

628
00:36:34,140 --> 00:36:36,500
we give thanks to god,

629
00:36:36,540 --> 00:36:40,040
for we do not grieveas those who have no hope

630
00:36:40,070 --> 00:36:43,920
but as those who placetheir trust in god.

631
00:36:59,280 --> 00:37:01,080
wait!

632
00:37:01,720 --> 00:37:04,530
do not closethat coffin.

633
00:37:19,590 --> 00:37:21,560
Give me your tie.

634
00:37:22,760 --> 00:37:23,770
What?

635
00:37:23,820 --> 00:37:26,770
Give me your tie.

636
00:37:28,100 --> 00:37:30,600
give it to her!Give it to her.

637
00:38:26,880 --> 00:38:31,050
You look magnificent.

638
00:39:02,280 --> 00:39:05,930
so it looks like mary alicekilled zach's birth mother

639
00:39:05,960 --> 00:39:08,550
in order to keep herfrom taking zach away.

640
00:39:08,590 --> 00:39:10,410
Oh,my god.

641
00:39:11,070 --> 00:39:14,050
I mean,I knew mary alicehad killed herself

642
00:39:14,090 --> 00:39:17,910
over something big,but wow.

643
00:39:18,370 --> 00:39:21,350
Can you imagine livingwith that guilt?

644
00:39:21,370 --> 00:39:23,550
Isn't it bizarrethat paul and mary alice

645
00:39:23,590 --> 00:39:25,670
had this secretall those years,

646
00:39:25,700 --> 00:39:27,620
and we didn't evenknow about it?

647
00:39:27,660 --> 00:39:29,920
No,not really.

648
00:39:29,950 --> 00:39:32,880
I mean,what do we actuallyknow about our neighbors?

649
00:39:32,920 --> 00:39:35,050
I mean,we can tellif they keep their lawns nice

650
00:39:35,080 --> 00:39:36,710
or they taketheir trash cans in,

651
00:39:36,750 --> 00:39:39,320
but when they do those things,we stop asking questions

652
00:39:39,360 --> 00:39:43,290
'cause if people aregood neighbors...

653
00:39:43,330 --> 00:39:47,400
we don't really carewhat happens behind closed doors.

654
00:39:48,450 --> 00:39:51,640
It had been one year since my suicide...

655
00:39:51,670 --> 00:39:53,610
makes you wonder,doesn't it?

656
00:39:53,670 --> 00:39:57,590
And a lot had changed on wisteria lane.

657
00:39:57,630 --> 00:39:59,830
There were new flowers,

658
00:39:59,860 --> 00:40:01,340
new houses

659
00:40:01,380 --> 00:40:03,680
and new neighbors--

660
00:40:03,730 --> 00:40:09,020
the kind anyone would want living right next door.

661
00:40:14,370 --> 00:40:15,480
is that another hymn?

662
00:40:15,520 --> 00:40:17,780
I know. It's silly,

663
00:40:17,820 --> 00:40:19,610
but playing those songstoday at the funeral

664
00:40:19,640 --> 00:40:22,030
just got me in the mood.

665
00:40:22,070 --> 00:40:24,870
This isyour grandmother's favorite.

666
00:40:24,990 --> 00:40:26,820
Did you remember butter?

667
00:40:26,860 --> 00:40:28,470
I make up this trayevery night.

668
00:40:28,520 --> 00:40:31,950
Of course you do.I'm sorry.

669
00:40:32,420 --> 00:40:33,890
Oh,look.

670
00:40:33,940 --> 00:40:36,670
You added a flower.

671
00:40:36,970 --> 00:40:39,330
Thought it'd be nice.

672
00:40:40,740 --> 00:40:44,280
How'd I get so luckyto have a child like you?

673
00:40:44,320 --> 00:40:46,510
You really do try to thinkabout us.

674
00:40:46,540 --> 00:40:49,390
That flower isa small act of kindness

675
00:40:49,430 --> 00:40:51,220
you thoughtno one would notice,

676
00:40:51,260 --> 00:40:52,840
and yet you did it anyway.

677
00:40:52,890 --> 00:40:55,540
Says a lot abouthow you were raised.

678
00:40:56,600 --> 00:40:58,970
Well,I guessyou did your job.

679
00:40:59,030 --> 00:41:00,950
Thank yourself.

680
00:41:07,290 --> 00:41:09,470
I'll get the tray.

681
00:41:09,570 --> 00:41:11,570
You take the gun.

682
00:41:58,180 --> 00:42:01,160
It really is a lovely gesture.

683
00:42:01,220 --> 00:42:05,350
Desperate Housewives

684
00:42:05,400 --> 00:42:10,360
Sync:YTET-fisherchen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-

685
00:42:10,410 --> 00:42:15,310
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-

