1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:01,760
Previously on "desperate housewives,"

2
00:00:01,800 --> 00:00:02,920
as one affair ends...

3
00:00:02,950 --> 00:00:04,560
we don't have tosneak around anymore.

4
00:00:04,600 --> 00:00:06,320
We can havea real relationship.

5
00:00:06,360 --> 00:00:07,850
Another begins. Edie!

6
00:00:07,890 --> 00:00:10,000
I had asked her ifshe'd like to live together,

7
00:00:10,050 --> 00:00:10,760
and she said yes.

8
00:00:10,800 --> 00:00:11,600
And yet another...

9
00:00:11,630 --> 00:00:13,270
this is rex's motherphyllis.

10
00:00:13,310 --> 00:00:14,320
Claims.This is joe flannery.

11
00:00:14,350 --> 00:00:17,560
Are you awarethat my daughter-in-law has a boyfriend?

12
00:00:17,590 --> 00:00:18,720
Is exposed.

13
00:00:18,760 --> 00:00:21,670
It's not going tobreak your heart to leave those sad,little faces behind?

14
00:00:21,690 --> 00:00:24,740
And while some people can't wait to get out of the house,

15
00:00:24,770 --> 00:00:26,370
others are being kept there,

16
00:00:26,400 --> 00:00:28,960
against their will.

17
00:00:37,810 --> 00:00:39,530
Now which oneis rex's headstone?

18
00:00:39,580 --> 00:00:41,190
I always forget.

19
00:00:41,230 --> 00:00:43,120
It's right down this row.

20
00:00:43,160 --> 00:00:45,430
Oh. Oh,yes.

21
00:00:45,480 --> 00:00:47,030
That's right.

22
00:00:47,070 --> 00:00:51,540
Over the years,bree van de kamp had grown increasingly concerned

23
00:00:51,570 --> 00:00:54,310
over her mother-in-law's forgetfulness.

24
00:00:54,360 --> 00:00:58,410
Oh,honey,did I forget to takethe pins out of that dress?

25
00:00:58,460 --> 00:01:01,560
Her lapses had become more frequent...

26
00:01:01,710 --> 00:01:05,800
sweetie,didn't I tell youI was going to paint that chair?

27
00:01:05,870 --> 00:01:07,990
More glaring...

28
00:01:09,140 --> 00:01:12,740
oh,dear. Didn't I mentionI waxed the floor?

29
00:01:12,790 --> 00:01:15,820
And more dangerous.

30
00:01:16,180 --> 00:01:20,560
Yes,bree was worried about phyllis' faulty memory,

31
00:01:20,620 --> 00:01:23,610
but she was more than happy to remind her,

32
00:01:23,640 --> 00:01:27,070
especially when it came to the important things.

33
00:01:27,100 --> 00:01:31,230
So have you given any thought to when you might be endingyour visit?

34
00:01:32,360 --> 00:01:35,600
- What?
- Have I become a burden?

35
00:01:35,650 --> 00:01:37,120
Is that what you're saying?

36
00:01:37,160 --> 00:01:40,720
I was simply askingwhen you were planning to leave.

37
00:01:40,760 --> 00:01:43,590
There was no agendabehind the question.

38
00:01:43,710 --> 00:01:47,800
Oh. I-I don't know.

39
00:01:49,930 --> 00:01:52,280
Why don't we play it by ear?

40
00:01:52,350 --> 00:01:54,990
Yes,let'S.

41
00:01:57,980 --> 00:01:59,490
What on earth?

42
00:01:59,540 --> 00:02:01,150
Oh,my god.

43
00:02:01,200 --> 00:02:03,190
What happened?

44
00:02:03,250 --> 00:02:05,730
It looks like someonedug rex up.

45
00:02:05,760 --> 00:02:08,170
Well,I got that,but why?

46
00:02:08,210 --> 00:02:10,160
Why would they do that?

47
00:02:10,830 --> 00:02:13,140
I don't know.

48
00:02:13,440 --> 00:02:15,690
Unless...

49
00:02:16,000 --> 00:02:17,640
unless what?

50
00:02:17,680 --> 00:02:22,700
Maybe this has something to do with thatinsurance investigator.

51
00:02:22,740 --> 00:02:24,440
Insurance investigator?

52
00:02:24,480 --> 00:02:27,750
He came by askingall sorts of questions.

53
00:02:27,780 --> 00:02:29,960
I don't know whatyou're talking about,phyllis.

54
00:02:30,000 --> 00:02:31,680
Maybe you were at the store.

55
00:02:31,720 --> 00:02:35,640
Anyway,he was very suspicious.

56
00:02:35,680 --> 00:02:36,770
Suspicious?

57
00:02:36,820 --> 00:02:41,730
Oh,yes. He has a theory that rex didn't dieof a heart attack.

58
00:02:41,770 --> 00:02:43,920
He thinks he was poisoned.

59
00:02:43,970 --> 00:02:48,190
It was in that moment bree could finally see the truth.

60
00:02:48,230 --> 00:02:50,580
Did I not mention that?

61
00:02:50,620 --> 00:02:53,950
Her mother-in-law's memory was fine.

62
00:02:54,050 --> 00:02:57,490
It was her soul that was faulty.

63
00:02:58,710 --> 00:03:08,270
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents

64
00:03:27,390 --> 00:03:34,980
Sync:YTET-fisherchen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-

65
00:03:35,390 --> 00:03:40,720
Desprtate Housewives
Season 2 Episode 3

66
00:03:41,640 --> 00:03:46,270
The parties took place on the front lawn of 4347 wisteria lane

67
00:03:46,320 --> 00:03:49,410
every sunday afternoon.

68
00:03:49,520 --> 00:03:52,650
Chloe pendergast would bring the tea set,

69
00:03:52,700 --> 00:03:54,100
which was appropriate,

70
00:03:54,130 --> 00:03:57,180
since she was the hostess.

71
00:03:57,320 --> 00:04:02,790
Brittany chries provided formal attire from her mother's closet.

72
00:04:03,500 --> 00:04:08,180
And marissa anne mckay invited the additional guests,

73
00:04:08,220 --> 00:04:12,540
some of whom hadn't been to a party in years.

74
00:04:12,990 --> 00:04:16,380
Of course,it never occurred to the three young girls

75
00:04:16,400 --> 00:04:20,100
that while they were busy playing out their fantasy,

76
00:04:20,400 --> 00:04:22,790
one of the older girls in the neighborhood

77
00:04:22,830 --> 00:04:27,200
was engaging in a fantasy of her own.

78
00:04:59,920 --> 00:05:01,220
- hey...
- oh,hi,mrs. Solis.

79
00:05:01,270 --> 00:05:03,520
- Ralph.
- Off to the mall again?

80
00:05:03,570 --> 00:05:04,930
You know me.

81
00:05:04,980 --> 00:05:10,510
There was nothing gabrielle enjoyed as much as shopping.

82
00:05:12,610 --> 00:05:16,310
And even when she couldn't afford to take anything home,

83
00:05:16,340 --> 00:05:19,890
she took satisfaction in looking...

84
00:05:20,180 --> 00:05:22,990
at the merchandise.

85
00:05:47,680 --> 00:05:48,650
Hey,susan.

86
00:05:48,670 --> 00:05:49,760
What's goin' on?

87
00:05:49,790 --> 00:05:51,770
It's karl's weekend to have julie,

88
00:05:51,800 --> 00:05:52,940
and they're always back by 6.

89
00:05:52,970 --> 00:05:54,040
That's our custody agreement,

90
00:05:54,080 --> 00:05:56,010
back by 6,and it's after 6.

91
00:05:56,030 --> 00:05:57,190
It's like 6:15.

92
00:05:57,230 --> 00:05:59,340
Well,see?There you go.

93
00:05:59,370 --> 00:06:01,050
I'm sure they just forgot.

94
00:06:01,080 --> 00:06:02,320
Well,I have a court order.

95
00:06:02,370 --> 00:06:04,070
It's out of my hands.

96
00:06:04,190 --> 00:06:06,890
Yeah,it'd still be nice if you gave him a grace period.

97
00:06:06,940 --> 00:06:08,230
Oh,I'm being nice.

98
00:06:08,250 --> 00:06:09,740
I could have him arrested.

99
00:06:09,770 --> 00:06:10,870
I mean,don't get me wrong.

100
00:06:10,910 --> 00:06:13,090
I am all for julie spending time with karl.

101
00:06:13,130 --> 00:06:14,580
He is still her dad,

102
00:06:14,620 --> 00:06:15,840
and she loves him.

103
00:06:15,870 --> 00:06:16,520
But...

104
00:06:16,550 --> 00:06:18,210
but he's with edie.

105
00:06:18,240 --> 00:06:20,950
I mean,she's not exactly the maternal type.

106
00:06:20,980 --> 00:06:22,960
I wouldn't be a good mother if I wasn't concerned.

107
00:06:22,990 --> 00:06:25,740
I mean,who knows what passes for a kid-friendly,

108
00:06:25,760 --> 00:06:26,740
good time in there?

109
00:06:26,760 --> 00:06:30,640
Drugs? Porn? Smoking?

110
00:06:33,890 --> 00:06:37,360
doesn't sound like they're having an orgy in there.

111
00:06:45,670 --> 00:06:49,950
obviously,they saw us coming.

112
00:06:54,670 --> 00:06:56,210
whoo! That's a strike!

113
00:06:56,250 --> 00:06:57,190
Hey,guys!

114
00:06:57,220 --> 00:07:00,400
Hey! Look who's here!

115
00:07:00,490 --> 00:07:02,420
Parker,guess what I got.

116
00:07:02,460 --> 00:07:03,210
What?

117
00:07:03,250 --> 00:07:04,440
School supplies.

118
00:07:04,470 --> 00:07:05,740
School supplies?!

119
00:07:05,780 --> 00:07:14,450
Yeah,and the best part of it is I got you a really cool backpack.

120
00:07:14,480 --> 00:07:15,990
Whoa,look at that.

121
00:07:16,030 --> 00:07:17,460
Pretty neat,huh?

122
00:07:17,490 --> 00:07:19,100
Wow. Thanks.

123
00:07:19,140 --> 00:07:20,760
So on your first day of school,

124
00:07:20,810 --> 00:07:24,280
you and your dad can find your cubby and you can hang it up.

125
00:07:24,480 --> 00:07:26,100
You're not taking me?

126
00:07:26,140 --> 00:07:28,530
Actually,your dad's going to take you to school on your first day.

127
00:07:28,560 --> 00:07:30,260
Yeah,just me and you,big guy.

128
00:07:30,290 --> 00:07:31,780
I'll be right there to hold your hand.

129
00:07:31,820 --> 00:07:33,540
But I thought mommy was taking me.

130
00:07:33,580 --> 00:07:35,950
Yeah,well,honey,I have to work.

131
00:07:35,970 --> 00:07:39,250
Mommy's boss is a mean,mean lady and if I miss work,

132
00:07:39,290 --> 00:07:43,190
I'll lose my job and then we won't have any money to buy food.

133
00:07:44,800 --> 00:07:46,680
Honey,you gotta believe me,

134
00:07:46,710 --> 00:07:50,170
if I could be there,you know that I would.

135
00:07:59,210 --> 00:08:02,980
all right,I didn't know it was that important to you.

136
00:08:03,020 --> 00:08:05,870
I will talk to my boss and I will see what I can do.

137
00:08:05,930 --> 00:08:08,020
Thank you,mommy.

138
00:08:10,220 --> 00:08:11,930
Wow,I don't want to rain on your parade,

139
00:08:12,000 --> 00:08:15,370
but he just totally manipulated you.

140
00:08:15,560 --> 00:08:19,220
Well,hey,when a kid'sthat good,you gotta give him his due.

141
00:08:20,500 --> 00:08:21,800
An autopsy?

142
00:08:21,830 --> 00:08:24,230
Detective,rex diedof a heart attack.

143
00:08:24,280 --> 00:08:28,150
Well,there weresome anomalies in the doctor's report.

144
00:08:28,170 --> 00:08:29,860
Anomalies?What anomalies?

145
00:08:29,890 --> 00:08:35,230
Ma'am,I'm afraidI'm not at liberty to discuss thisany further with you.

146
00:08:36,140 --> 00:08:37,610
Am I a suspect?

147
00:08:37,640 --> 00:08:39,440
I didn't say that.

148
00:08:39,480 --> 00:08:41,920
Well,if I am,you're wasting your time.

149
00:08:41,940 --> 00:08:44,190
I loved rex and anyonewho knows me will tell you

150
00:08:44,220 --> 00:08:46,840
that I was incapableof hurting him.

151
00:08:47,540 --> 00:08:49,950
You sure about that?

152
00:08:52,450 --> 00:08:53,860
You talked to phyllis.

153
00:08:53,880 --> 00:08:56,100
Again,I can't discussthe case.

154
00:08:56,130 --> 00:08:57,620
She's my mother-in-law.

155
00:08:57,660 --> 00:08:59,820
Of course she saidhorrible things about me.

156
00:08:59,840 --> 00:09:00,380
Ma'am,lower your voice.

157
00:09:00,420 --> 00:09:02,980
She blamed me for every problemthat rex and I ever had.

158
00:09:03,030 --> 00:09:04,520
So there were problemswith the marriage?

159
00:09:04,570 --> 00:09:07,200
Well,it was a marriage.Of course there were problems.

160
00:09:07,240 --> 00:09:09,280
May I record thisjust so there's no confusion

161
00:09:09,320 --> 00:09:10,350
over your statement?

162
00:09:10,390 --> 00:09:12,320
No,you may not record this.

163
00:09:12,360 --> 00:09:13,700
So you refuseto make a statement?

164
00:09:13,750 --> 00:09:14,700
I'm not refusing anything.

165
00:09:14,730 --> 00:09:16,870
All I'm saying isstay away from phyllis.

166
00:09:16,910 --> 00:09:18,960
She's a--she's a raving loon.

167
00:09:18,980 --> 00:09:22,770
Ma'am,perhaps you'd bemore comfortable with an attorney present.

168
00:09:23,000 --> 00:09:27,800
You want a statement?Fine,I'll give you a statement.

169
00:09:29,610 --> 00:09:31,690
My husband diedof a heart attack.

170
00:09:31,750 --> 00:09:33,400
I loved him very deeply,

171
00:09:33,440 --> 00:09:36,540
and your motherdid a lousy job.

172
00:09:48,740 --> 00:09:50,680
To bree's way of thinking,

173
00:09:50,710 --> 00:09:54,250
there were two kinds of people in the world--

174
00:09:54,750 --> 00:09:58,800
those who were useless before their morning coffee...

175
00:10:00,410 --> 00:10:03,390
and those who weren'T.

176
00:10:08,800 --> 00:10:10,840
What's going on?

177
00:10:12,110 --> 00:10:14,280
Don't rush me,bree!

178
00:10:14,310 --> 00:10:18,430
I'm an old woman!Don't rush me.

179
00:10:19,300 --> 00:10:21,540
Get her out of here.

180
00:10:21,610 --> 00:10:22,690
I will tell you one thing--

181
00:10:22,740 --> 00:10:24,750
you wouldn't be actingthis way

182
00:10:24,780 --> 00:10:28,930
if you didn't feel guiltyabout something!

183
00:10:37,580 --> 00:10:39,580
what's the occasion?

184
00:10:39,620 --> 00:10:42,080
Uh,our anniversary?

185
00:10:42,170 --> 00:10:43,660
Oh,right.

186
00:10:43,700 --> 00:10:45,640
How could you forgetour anniversary?

187
00:10:45,680 --> 00:10:48,310
You sit in a cell all day longstaring at a calendar.

188
00:10:48,350 --> 00:10:49,950
What's the big deal?

189
00:10:49,990 --> 00:10:51,300
Our marriagewas a sham anyway.

190
00:10:51,350 --> 00:10:52,430
Oh,we're not doing thisagain.

191
00:10:52,470 --> 00:10:54,800
In real marriages,wives are faithful.

192
00:10:54,820 --> 00:10:57,140
Yeah,and husbandsremember anniversaries,

193
00:10:57,140 --> 00:10:58,650
so I guess we're even.

194
00:10:58,670 --> 00:11:01,680
Are you equating forgettingour anniversary with cheating on me?

195
00:11:01,720 --> 00:11:05,010
You are clearly determinedto ruin this special day for us.

196
00:11:05,010 --> 00:11:07,600
What is wrong with youthat you don't feel guilty?

197
00:11:07,630 --> 00:11:09,670
I feel tons of guilt,so back off.

198
00:11:09,700 --> 00:11:11,420
You never even apologized.

199
00:11:11,450 --> 00:11:13,420
I apologized a million times.

200
00:11:13,440 --> 00:11:15,910
Yeah,but you always followedit up with an excuse.

201
00:11:15,940 --> 00:11:18,290
"I was lonely,you weren't home enough,

202
00:11:18,310 --> 00:11:19,660
a woman needs to be loved."

203
00:11:19,710 --> 00:11:21,350
A womandoes need to be loved,

204
00:11:21,370 --> 00:11:22,430
and since you didn'tgive it to me,

205
00:11:22,480 --> 00:11:25,220
I had to find it elsewhere.

206
00:11:26,090 --> 00:11:29,720
So that's what the teenagerwas doing in our bedroom--

207
00:11:29,820 --> 00:11:32,340
filling you with love.

208
00:11:32,470 --> 00:11:34,170
Say what you want,

209
00:11:34,200 --> 00:11:36,680
but john rowland loved melike no one ever has.

210
00:11:36,700 --> 00:11:40,200
Not as a trophyor as a possession,but for me.

211
00:11:40,240 --> 00:11:42,240
He loved me.

212
00:11:43,850 --> 00:11:46,460
no,he really did.

213
00:11:46,950 --> 00:11:49,330
Let me count the ways.

214
00:11:49,500 --> 00:11:53,960
Um,gently,savagely,

215
00:11:54,000 --> 00:11:57,470
frequently,upside down...

216
00:11:57,910 --> 00:12:00,110
is there a problem here?

217
00:12:00,780 --> 00:12:03,620
No,it's our anniversary.

218
00:12:03,660 --> 00:12:06,790
We're just relivingthe good times.

219
00:12:16,510 --> 00:12:18,370
That's an amazing car.Aston martin,right?

220
00:12:18,420 --> 00:12:20,610
Uh-huh. Brand-new.Limited edition.

221
00:12:20,660 --> 00:12:23,140
A little anniversary presentfrom my husband.

222
00:12:23,180 --> 00:12:25,020
He's very generous.

223
00:12:25,070 --> 00:12:27,250
More than he knows.

224
00:12:27,380 --> 00:12:28,530
I'm sorry. What?

225
00:12:28,560 --> 00:12:31,090
I'm singing at church for the family follies.

226
00:12:31,130 --> 00:12:32,880
Edie's going to accompany meon guitar.

227
00:12:32,920 --> 00:12:34,760
She's really good.

228
00:12:34,830 --> 00:12:38,370
So you and edieare going to be an act.

229
00:12:38,430 --> 00:12:39,810
Is that a problem?

230
00:12:39,840 --> 00:12:47,740
No. No. I mean,I'm a little surprised that you didn't ask meto accompany you first.

231
00:12:47,770 --> 00:12:49,530
On what?

232
00:12:49,570 --> 00:12:51,160
You don't play an instrument.

233
00:12:51,180 --> 00:12:53,140
I play the piano.You know that.

234
00:12:53,190 --> 00:12:55,690
How would I know that?I've never seen you play.

235
00:12:55,730 --> 00:12:57,710
Well,I played in high school.

236
00:12:57,740 --> 00:13:00,830
So the last timeyou tickled the ivories was sometimein the late '70s?

237
00:13:00,890 --> 00:13:03,240
It was the early '80s.

238
00:13:03,280 --> 00:13:06,210
Well,I'm not goingto argue with you.

239
00:13:06,450 --> 00:13:08,100
You want to do the showwith edie,

240
00:13:08,130 --> 00:13:10,520
and I think that's super.

241
00:13:12,350 --> 00:13:14,490
So she's really good,huh?

242
00:13:14,530 --> 00:13:16,060
She knows her guitar.

243
00:13:16,120 --> 00:13:18,750
Apparently,there are a lotof musicians in her family,

244
00:13:18,800 --> 00:13:21,080
sort of likethe von trapps.

245
00:13:21,940 --> 00:13:24,950
Except,you know,her brother od'D.

246
00:13:26,490 --> 00:13:28,800
All I'm asking youis to go out and play a little bit of ball.

247
00:13:28,820 --> 00:13:29,980
Is that such a big deal?

248
00:13:30,020 --> 00:13:32,150
Matthew,you are suchan excellent player,darling,

249
00:13:32,200 --> 00:13:34,780
that people will wantto be your friend.

250
00:13:34,810 --> 00:13:36,070
Then next thing you know,

251
00:13:36,100 --> 00:13:39,840
god knows who will bewanting to drop by and calling.

252
00:13:39,890 --> 00:13:42,010
Sweetie,we needto keep a low profile.

253
00:13:42,060 --> 00:13:42,560
Yeah,I know,

254
00:13:42,610 --> 00:13:44,390
but I have got to get outof this house sometime.

255
00:13:44,420 --> 00:13:46,750
I'm going crazy here,okay?

256
00:14:23,130 --> 00:14:24,140
What is it?

257
00:14:24,170 --> 00:14:27,210
Oh,my daughter is singinga song at church

258
00:14:27,240 --> 00:14:29,050
and I want to accompany heron the piano

259
00:14:29,080 --> 00:14:30,680
and I haven't played in years.

260
00:14:30,720 --> 00:14:33,530
Oh,you were just so amazingat rex's funeral the other day,

261
00:14:33,560 --> 00:14:36,670
I was wondering--I don't give lessons.

262
00:14:36,720 --> 00:14:40,480
Oh. Oh,okay.

263
00:14:41,770 --> 00:14:45,830
Oh. You have a little,uh,on your...

264
00:14:49,030 --> 00:14:52,760
I'm baking cherry pie.Excuse me.

265
00:15:00,500 --> 00:15:03,620
What happened to maintaininga low profile?

266
00:15:03,800 --> 00:15:04,870
You keep being rudeto everybody,

267
00:15:04,910 --> 00:15:07,570
they're gonna startwhispering about us.

268
00:15:07,620 --> 00:15:09,460
You're right.

269
00:15:09,510 --> 00:15:12,160
We do want to fit in.

270
00:15:18,810 --> 00:15:21,300
Lynette,check it out.

271
00:15:24,160 --> 00:15:26,060
Jason's mouth.

272
00:15:28,990 --> 00:15:30,970
Stu,isn't that the newvideo conference setup?

273
00:15:31,030 --> 00:15:34,300
Yeah. Isn't the resolutionfantastic?

274
00:15:39,150 --> 00:15:40,710
Hey,nina.Mm-hmm?

275
00:15:40,750 --> 00:15:43,310
Uh,about tomorrow morning...

276
00:15:43,370 --> 00:15:44,850
mm-hmm?

277
00:15:44,910 --> 00:15:48,790
You know how the first hourof the morning meeting is always so slow?

278
00:15:48,830 --> 00:15:50,240
'Cause I've got this thing...

279
00:15:50,280 --> 00:15:54,680
good god,this is notabout your kids again,is it?

280
00:15:54,740 --> 00:15:56,870
I know,I promisedI wouldn't do this,

281
00:15:56,920 --> 00:16:01,570
but parker really needs meto be there on his first dayof kindergarten.

282
00:16:01,600 --> 00:16:02,700
He's so freaked outI can't be there.

283
00:16:02,740 --> 00:16:06,220
I'm sorry. How is thismy problem?

284
00:16:07,140 --> 00:16:10,180
Because we can't escapethe fact that I have kids.

285
00:16:10,200 --> 00:16:12,340
I love my job,but to be fair,

286
00:16:12,380 --> 00:16:13,820
there's gotta be some balance.

287
00:16:13,860 --> 00:16:17,700
Okay,how about the peoplethat don't have the kids?

288
00:16:17,740 --> 00:16:20,930
Did you ever considerthat they might need a little more balancein their lives,hmm?

289
00:16:20,960 --> 00:16:23,030
Like,maybe they wantto go see a matinee

290
00:16:23,080 --> 00:16:24,950
or perhaps they wantto come in a little late

291
00:16:24,990 --> 00:16:26,510
after a big crazy night out

292
00:16:26,540 --> 00:16:28,670
or maybe they justwant to get a hair cut,

293
00:16:28,670 --> 00:16:31,570
which I,myself,have notbeen able to do for two months.

294
00:16:31,620 --> 00:16:37,550
So,no,this is about fairness to the people who arechildless by choice,okay?

295
00:16:37,550 --> 00:16:40,080
Okay. Good point.

296
00:16:44,610 --> 00:16:47,400
And I'm sorry about your hair.

297
00:16:47,440 --> 00:16:49,780
I can see why you're upset.

298
00:16:52,560 --> 00:16:53,390
Open wide.

299
00:16:53,420 --> 00:16:55,390
Not now,stu.

300
00:16:57,730 --> 00:16:59,610
Hang on a sec.

301
00:17:00,490 --> 00:17:02,060
I don't understand.

302
00:17:02,090 --> 00:17:07,160
This system is gonna letmommy be with you on your first day of school.

303
00:17:09,450 --> 00:17:12,730
The resolution is fantastic.

304
00:17:19,030 --> 00:17:20,190
The next day,

305
00:17:20,230 --> 00:17:23,480
gabrielle decided to cheer herself up

306
00:17:23,530 --> 00:17:26,840
with another round of window shopping.

307
00:17:29,740 --> 00:17:32,840
But this time,she was taken aback

308
00:17:32,870 --> 00:17:35,690
by what was on display.

309
00:18:44,940 --> 00:18:47,500
Mrs. Tilman.Mr. Delfino.

310
00:18:47,550 --> 00:18:49,710
I,uh,heard you wereback from the hospital,

311
00:18:49,750 --> 00:18:51,500
so I brought you these.

312
00:18:51,550 --> 00:18:53,170
Oh,I can't tell youhow long it's been

313
00:18:53,210 --> 00:18:55,470
since I got flowersfrom a handsome man.

314
00:18:55,830 --> 00:19:00,280
I mean,I could,but I don't want your pity.

315
00:19:03,400 --> 00:19:05,050
Where are you off to?

316
00:19:05,100 --> 00:19:07,180
I'm going back to utahfor a few weeks.

317
00:19:07,210 --> 00:19:10,500
The recuperation'staking longer than the doctors anticipated.

318
00:19:10,540 --> 00:19:12,530
Speaking of my attack,

319
00:19:12,570 --> 00:19:15,190
have they caughtyoung zachary yet?

320
00:19:15,230 --> 00:19:17,900
No,actually,that's why I'm here.

321
00:19:18,280 --> 00:19:21,120
So the flowerswere just a ruse.

322
00:19:21,150 --> 00:19:24,480
Figures.I'm trying to find zach before he gets inany more trouble.

323
00:19:24,520 --> 00:19:26,370
Do you know any friendsthat he might have,

324
00:19:26,410 --> 00:19:28,240
anywhere he might be holed up?

325
00:19:28,260 --> 00:19:30,090
I know you were close to him.

326
00:19:30,120 --> 00:19:32,900
Funny thing,since he beat meand threw me down the stairs,

327
00:19:32,940 --> 00:19:36,270
we just don't stay in touchlike we should.

328
00:19:37,660 --> 00:19:40,740
Since when do you careso much about zach young?

329
00:19:40,790 --> 00:19:42,690
It's complicated.

330
00:19:42,750 --> 00:19:44,970
I'll bet.

331
00:19:45,660 --> 00:19:49,730
I'm sure he's out theresomewhere trying to find his father,

332
00:19:49,790 --> 00:19:53,140
which I trust you madeimpossible.

333
00:19:53,300 --> 00:19:55,650
No,I let paul go.

334
00:19:55,710 --> 00:19:58,390
I couldn'tgo through with it.

335
00:19:59,840 --> 00:20:02,300
That was a mistake.

336
00:20:02,700 --> 00:20:05,080
He will spendthe rest of his life running from the police.

337
00:20:05,110 --> 00:20:07,750
I think that'spunishment enough.

338
00:20:07,820 --> 00:20:11,770
Zach is the only connection that paul haswith his dead wife.

339
00:20:11,800 --> 00:20:15,940
At some point,he will runback here looking for him.

340
00:20:17,380 --> 00:20:19,960
I don't like to be negative,

341
00:20:20,460 --> 00:20:23,970
but you really should havekilled him.

342
00:20:32,410 --> 00:20:34,600
At the risk of ruininga lovely evening,

343
00:20:34,640 --> 00:20:37,720
I have some unpleasant news.

344
00:20:39,070 --> 00:20:42,360
The police dug upyour father today.

345
00:20:42,670 --> 00:20:44,510
What?Why?

346
00:20:44,550 --> 00:20:47,750
Well,apparently,they want to do an autopsy.

347
00:20:47,790 --> 00:20:49,440
They don't thinkthat he had a heart attack.

348
00:20:49,480 --> 00:20:51,540
They think that somebodywas poisoning him.

349
00:20:51,580 --> 00:20:53,450
Who would havepoisoned daddy?

350
00:20:53,490 --> 00:20:56,670
Well,apparently,I'm a suspect.

351
00:20:59,510 --> 00:21:01,560
Well,they always lookat spouses first.

352
00:21:01,590 --> 00:21:04,350
It has something to dowith statistics.

353
00:21:04,940 --> 00:21:09,080
It's just a formality.I'll be cleared in no time.

354
00:21:10,150 --> 00:21:11,930
Would you two pleasestop looking at me like that?

355
00:21:11,970 --> 00:21:13,740
Obviously,I did notkill your father.

356
00:21:13,790 --> 00:21:15,340
I loved him deeply.

357
00:21:15,380 --> 00:21:17,390
Yeah,but you and dadhad a lot of problems.

358
00:21:17,440 --> 00:21:18,680
Everyone knows that.

359
00:21:18,720 --> 00:21:21,540
Yes,we had issues,but I would never have hurt him.

360
00:21:21,570 --> 00:21:24,100
What about the night daddyhad his second heart attack?

361
00:21:24,140 --> 00:21:27,240
You must have loved hima lot to make the bed before takinghim to the hospital.

362
00:21:27,280 --> 00:21:31,360
I was in shock,danielle.You know that.

363
00:21:32,850 --> 00:21:36,170
Andrew,surely you don't thinkI murdered your father.

364
00:21:36,220 --> 00:21:38,260
I know you didn'T.

365
00:21:38,460 --> 00:21:40,180
You're not capable of murder.

366
00:21:40,220 --> 00:21:41,880
Thank you.

367
00:21:41,980 --> 00:21:44,490
That wasn't a compliment.

368
00:21:44,940 --> 00:21:48,090
It takes gutsto kill somebody.

369
00:21:51,690 --> 00:21:54,110
Thank you so much for changingyour mind about helping me.

370
00:21:54,140 --> 00:21:55,880
I really appreciate it.

371
00:21:55,920 --> 00:21:57,750
I'm happy to help...

372
00:21:58,150 --> 00:22:01,660
and I'm sorry if I seemedrude before.

373
00:22:01,700 --> 00:22:04,390
I-I was having a bad day.

374
00:22:10,010 --> 00:22:11,070
That's good.

375
00:22:11,110 --> 00:22:12,510
That's really good.

376
00:22:12,550 --> 00:22:15,650
You might want tolay off the pedal.

377
00:22:15,690 --> 00:22:16,950
Really?

378
00:22:16,980 --> 00:22:19,420
Oh,I thought it made it soundmore professional.

379
00:22:19,450 --> 00:22:21,440
It doesn'T.

380
00:22:26,260 --> 00:22:29,810
boy,your son really likesto play his hip-hop music loud.

381
00:22:30,530 --> 00:22:35,170
The good news is it drownsout the sound of the dryer.

382
00:22:38,160 --> 00:22:40,890
arch your fingers,susan.

383
00:23:00,220 --> 00:23:01,850
hi.I'm sorry to interrupt.

384
00:23:01,900 --> 00:23:04,470
I knocked,but I guessyou guys didn't hear me.

385
00:23:04,500 --> 00:23:05,360
No,we heard you.

386
00:23:05,400 --> 00:23:09,100
We were just hoping that whoeverit was would go away.

387
00:23:09,160 --> 00:23:10,880
I'm still hopingthat'll happen.

388
00:23:10,940 --> 00:23:13,140
What's up,mom?

389
00:23:13,140 --> 00:23:14,730
Well,I have good news.

390
00:23:14,770 --> 00:23:17,650
Um,I've been takingpiano lessons with betty applewhite,

391
00:23:17,680 --> 00:23:21,110
and,uh,well,I just thoughtmaybe I could join you guys.

392
00:23:21,140 --> 00:23:23,770
You know,like a trio.Doesn't that sound fun?

393
00:23:23,810 --> 00:23:27,590
I don't do trios,but thanks anyway.

394
00:23:27,730 --> 00:23:29,530
Well,I don't mean to betechnical here,

395
00:23:29,550 --> 00:23:31,000
but this show,

396
00:23:31,000 --> 00:23:33,430
I mean,it really is supposedto be a family thing,

397
00:23:33,460 --> 00:23:36,090
and I hate to point outyou're not family.

398
00:23:36,120 --> 00:23:38,110
No,but I have talent,

399
00:23:38,120 --> 00:23:41,650
and to most audiences,talent trumps family.

400
00:23:41,690 --> 00:23:45,240
Well,what makes you so sureI don't have talent?

401
00:23:45,580 --> 00:23:48,510
Hmm,just a hunch.

402
00:23:48,770 --> 00:23:51,220
Yeah,well,we've allseen your talent,

403
00:23:51,270 --> 00:23:52,500
which is a nice wayof telling you

404
00:23:52,520 --> 00:23:54,380
why don't you put some curtainson your bedroom window?

405
00:23:54,420 --> 00:23:56,090
Guys...oh,come on,be honest.

406
00:23:56,120 --> 00:23:57,410
You didn't wantany part of this

407
00:23:57,450 --> 00:23:59,010
until you found outthat I was involved.

408
00:23:59,040 --> 00:24:01,650
That is so not true!Oh,yes,it is.

409
00:24:01,700 --> 00:24:04,810
It burns you that yourown daughter picked me over you.

410
00:24:04,850 --> 00:24:06,360
She did not pick you.

411
00:24:06,380 --> 00:24:08,490
It just didn't occur to herthat I would agree to do it.

412
00:24:08,530 --> 00:24:09,670
Well,now she knows,

413
00:24:09,700 --> 00:24:11,620
and if she had it to doover again,she'd pick me.

414
00:24:11,670 --> 00:24:12,940
No,she wouldn'T.

415
00:24:12,960 --> 00:24:14,750
Well,why don'twe put it to a test?

416
00:24:14,800 --> 00:24:16,850
Julie,who would you ratherhave play with you?

417
00:24:16,880 --> 00:24:19,540
Oh,no,no,no,no.No,it's okay,honey.

418
00:24:19,590 --> 00:24:21,120
Who do you wantto be with you

419
00:24:21,150 --> 00:24:23,240
in the family talent show?

420
00:24:23,280 --> 00:24:25,340
Yes,who do you wantwith you

421
00:24:25,380 --> 00:24:28,030
in front ofall of those people?

422
00:24:28,050 --> 00:24:29,300
And remember,it's a church.

423
00:24:29,340 --> 00:24:32,380
They are goingto be judging you.

424
00:24:34,550 --> 00:24:36,860
Ohh... okay.

425
00:24:36,930 --> 00:24:39,460
Well,first of all,you both suck,

426
00:24:39,480 --> 00:24:42,730
but if I had to choose...

427
00:24:44,110 --> 00:24:47,720
I guess I'd pick my mom.

428
00:24:47,780 --> 00:24:49,510
Sorry,edie.

429
00:24:49,550 --> 00:24:51,700
Fair enough.

430
00:24:52,050 --> 00:24:55,330
I'd like my pitch pipe back,please.

431
00:25:01,360 --> 00:25:03,050
it was you,wasn't it?

432
00:25:03,090 --> 00:25:03,920
Hello,john.

433
00:25:03,960 --> 00:25:05,440
Long time,no see.

434
00:25:05,470 --> 00:25:08,840
One of the neighbors sawan aston martin driving away,

435
00:25:08,880 --> 00:25:10,360
and what do you know?

436
00:25:10,390 --> 00:25:12,280
Well,someone hadto tend to the yard.

437
00:25:12,330 --> 00:25:14,710
You were busy elsewhere.

438
00:25:15,360 --> 00:25:16,130
You saw us?

439
00:25:16,170 --> 00:25:19,350
Yes,and I have to say she'sold enough to be your mother.

440
00:25:19,390 --> 00:25:20,750
Hell,she's old enoughto be my mother.

441
00:25:20,780 --> 00:25:22,000
Joan's only 41.

442
00:25:22,050 --> 00:25:22,990
Joan?!

443
00:25:23,020 --> 00:25:24,450
You're calling her joan?!

444
00:25:24,500 --> 00:25:25,890
Why shouldn't I?She's my friend.

445
00:25:25,940 --> 00:25:26,970
I know your friends,

446
00:25:27,020 --> 00:25:28,440
and I have a hunchyou don't do to your friends

447
00:25:28,480 --> 00:25:31,230
what I saw you doingto that wrinkly old lady.

448
00:25:31,270 --> 00:25:34,280
Okay,so you caught medoing it with somebody else.

449
00:25:34,320 --> 00:25:35,100
What's the big deal?

450
00:25:35,140 --> 00:25:37,410
You're supposed to bein love with me.

451
00:25:37,490 --> 00:25:38,140
What?

452
00:25:38,180 --> 00:25:39,350
How many timesdid you say it?

453
00:25:39,400 --> 00:25:40,780
How many times did youwhisper in my ear,

454
00:25:40,820 --> 00:25:42,230
"you're the only womanI'll ever love"?

455
00:25:42,260 --> 00:25:44,070
I don't know. A bunch.

456
00:25:44,100 --> 00:25:45,180
So were you lying to me?

457
00:25:45,200 --> 00:25:46,430
Were you just trying to get me into bed?

458
00:25:46,470 --> 00:25:48,280
No,of course not.

459
00:25:48,310 --> 00:25:50,110
I loved you,but we broke up.

460
00:25:50,140 --> 00:25:51,790
Yeah,like five minutes ago!

461
00:25:51,820 --> 00:25:53,930
Haven't you ever heardof a mourning period?

462
00:25:53,980 --> 00:25:58,220
I know it seems quick,but I have feelings for her.

463
00:25:58,310 --> 00:26:01,310
In fact,I thinkI may be in love with her.

464
00:26:05,060 --> 00:26:06,220
Oh,my god.

465
00:26:06,270 --> 00:26:08,450
What's the matter?Is it the baby?

466
00:26:08,480 --> 00:26:10,130
No.

467
00:26:11,440 --> 00:26:14,520
Oh,no,no. It's me.

468
00:26:14,880 --> 00:26:17,930
I am beyond stupid.

469
00:26:19,380 --> 00:26:20,490
You're not stupid.

470
00:26:20,530 --> 00:26:22,310
Oh,no,I am.

471
00:26:22,510 --> 00:26:26,470
Yesterday,I was still fantasizing that it could work with you,

472
00:26:26,510 --> 00:26:28,790
that a one-bedroom apartmentmight be cozy.

473
00:26:28,830 --> 00:26:29,830
Mrs. Solis,please.

474
00:26:29,870 --> 00:26:35,620
Oh,my god.I almost left my husband for someone who calls memrs. Solis.

475
00:26:42,260 --> 00:26:45,620
So are you upset becauseyou want to get back together?

476
00:26:45,650 --> 00:26:48,640
Because I can break upwith joan.

477
00:26:50,060 --> 00:26:52,720
That's okay,sweetie.I'm good.

478
00:27:01,940 --> 00:27:04,740
So this is it for us?

479
00:27:04,840 --> 00:27:07,660
'Cause I really feel like weshould end it better than this.

480
00:27:07,700 --> 00:27:11,040
Actually,john,given howstupid both of us have been,

481
00:27:11,800 --> 00:27:15,160
this is an entirelyappropriate ending.

482
00:27:29,650 --> 00:27:30,890
mrs. Van de kamp.

483
00:27:30,930 --> 00:27:32,000
What can I do for you?

484
00:27:32,040 --> 00:27:34,640
I would like to submit myselfto a lie detector test

485
00:27:34,690 --> 00:27:36,370
to eliminate any uncertainty

486
00:27:36,410 --> 00:27:38,440
about what happenedwith my husband.

487
00:27:38,470 --> 00:27:40,400
Are you sure you don'twant a lawyer present?

488
00:27:40,440 --> 00:27:41,590
I'll waive all that.

489
00:27:41,630 --> 00:27:44,050
My only stipulationis that I want my children

490
00:27:44,070 --> 00:27:47,130
to be able to see meanswer the questions.

491
00:27:47,390 --> 00:27:50,430
I thinkwe can accommodate you.

492
00:27:50,480 --> 00:27:52,630
Is your namebree van de kamp?

493
00:27:52,670 --> 00:27:54,250
Yes.

494
00:27:54,300 --> 00:27:57,040
Were you marriedto rex van de kamp?

495
00:27:57,090 --> 00:27:58,600
yes.

496
00:27:58,780 --> 00:28:02,100
Did you and your husbandtemporarily separate last year?

497
00:28:02,130 --> 00:28:03,590
Yes.

498
00:28:03,640 --> 00:28:05,220
Did youkill your husband?

499
00:28:05,260 --> 00:28:07,170
No.

500
00:28:11,030 --> 00:28:15,570
Do you know a mannamed george williams?

501
00:28:15,820 --> 00:28:17,250
Yes.

502
00:28:17,270 --> 00:28:19,030
During your separationfrom your husband,

503
00:28:19,060 --> 00:28:22,330
did you have a relationshipwith mr. Williams?

504
00:28:22,360 --> 00:28:24,990
What does that haveto do with anything?

505
00:28:25,080 --> 00:28:27,340
Just yes or no responses,please.

506
00:28:27,370 --> 00:28:31,490
Well,I'm not gonna respondto something that's none of your business.

507
00:28:32,200 --> 00:28:33,740
Mrs. Van de kamp,

508
00:28:33,750 --> 00:28:36,130
if you want us to takethis polygraph seriously,

509
00:28:36,160 --> 00:28:39,620
answer the questionswe ask,okay?

510
00:28:42,750 --> 00:28:44,530
Who's george williams?

511
00:28:44,570 --> 00:28:47,110
He's our pharmacist.

512
00:28:47,160 --> 00:28:49,350
During your separation,did you have a relationship

513
00:28:49,390 --> 00:28:51,550
with mr. Williams?

514
00:28:51,590 --> 00:28:53,430
Yes.

515
00:28:54,140 --> 00:28:56,790
Are you in lovewith mr. Williams?

516
00:28:56,870 --> 00:28:57,770
What?

517
00:28:57,810 --> 00:29:01,350
Are you in lovewith mr. Williams?

518
00:29:01,440 --> 00:29:03,520
No.

519
00:29:07,890 --> 00:29:10,790
Um,I-I was thinkingof something else just then,

520
00:29:10,830 --> 00:29:14,310
so why don't you ask methe question again?

521
00:29:14,910 --> 00:29:17,230
Are you in lovewith mr. Williams?

522
00:29:17,280 --> 00:29:19,320
No.

523
00:29:24,290 --> 00:29:26,300
Did you see that?

524
00:29:27,060 --> 00:29:30,020
Yeah,I saw it.

525
00:29:38,950 --> 00:29:40,680
Hello,susan.

526
00:29:40,710 --> 00:29:42,300
Are you readyfor your lesson?

527
00:29:42,320 --> 00:29:43,870
Yep,I am.

528
00:29:43,890 --> 00:29:46,130
I think I'm going to makeanother push for using that pedal.

529
00:29:46,170 --> 00:29:48,600
I think it adds grandeur.

530
00:29:50,880 --> 00:29:52,470
I want to talk to you!

531
00:29:52,520 --> 00:29:53,680
I'm busy now.

532
00:29:53,710 --> 00:29:54,830
I cannot believe

533
00:29:54,860 --> 00:29:57,350
you kicked edieout of julie's performance!

534
00:29:57,400 --> 00:29:59,320
I did not kick edie out.

535
00:29:59,340 --> 00:30:00,420
Julie made that call.

536
00:30:00,450 --> 00:30:02,330
Because you playedthe mom card.

537
00:30:02,360 --> 00:30:05,790
Well,it is a family recital,and edie is not family.

538
00:30:05,810 --> 00:30:06,830
One day,she could be.

539
00:30:06,860 --> 00:30:08,580
Ohh,don't even joke like that.

540
00:30:08,610 --> 00:30:12,070
H-how about yourplumber/convicted murderer,huh?

541
00:30:12,100 --> 00:30:14,830
He seems to keep popping upat "family" events.

542
00:30:14,870 --> 00:30:16,910
It was not murder,it was manslaughter,

543
00:30:16,940 --> 00:30:17,990
and that's totally different.

544
00:30:18,020 --> 00:30:19,280
Mike and I aren't evenliving together,

545
00:30:19,300 --> 00:30:20,510
and he cares about julie.

546
00:30:20,560 --> 00:30:21,800
Well,so does edie,huh?

547
00:30:21,840 --> 00:30:24,170
She was really looking forwardto performing with julie.

548
00:30:24,200 --> 00:30:27,790
If you think edie britt cares about anybodyother than herself,

549
00:30:27,820 --> 00:30:29,780
you are living ina fool's paradise.

550
00:30:29,810 --> 00:30:31,290
You don't know herthe way I do,

551
00:30:31,340 --> 00:30:33,340
and the only reasonshe's interested in julie

552
00:30:33,370 --> 00:30:36,270
is to mess with my head.

553
00:30:37,060 --> 00:30:39,960
hey,that's both crazy and self-absorbed.

554
00:30:39,990 --> 00:30:43,030
That's a twofer!Way to go!

555
00:30:44,750 --> 00:30:46,920
Whether you chooseto believe it or not,

556
00:30:46,960 --> 00:30:48,170
they're both great together,

557
00:30:48,200 --> 00:30:51,640
and if you don't believe me,ask julie.

558
00:31:01,920 --> 00:31:04,690
I'm sorry you hadto witness that.

559
00:31:06,060 --> 00:31:08,020
Oh,that's okay,hon.

560
00:31:08,640 --> 00:31:11,950
I have lived my shareof family knock-down drag-outs.

561
00:31:12,010 --> 00:31:15,310
Well,I hope it wasn't as uglyas me and karl.

562
00:31:15,380 --> 00:31:17,440
You'd be surprised.

563
00:31:17,620 --> 00:31:20,790
Parker,honey,can you hear me?

564
00:31:20,840 --> 00:31:22,550
Tom,why isn't he talking?

565
00:31:22,600 --> 00:31:24,100
Um,honey,thereare a lot of kids here.

566
00:31:24,130 --> 00:31:25,270
He's a little stressed.

567
00:31:25,310 --> 00:31:27,500
Parker,say hi,say hi.Mommy?

568
00:31:27,540 --> 00:31:31,750
Oh,hey,honey,this is so exciting.

569
00:31:31,770 --> 00:31:33,400
Your first day of school.

570
00:31:33,450 --> 00:31:35,810
You're going to makeso many friends.

571
00:31:35,850 --> 00:31:38,440
Lynette,staff meeting,now.

572
00:31:38,480 --> 00:31:41,150
Uh,right,yeah.I'm going to be right there.

573
00:31:41,180 --> 00:31:44,250
Now. Now,now,now!

574
00:31:45,060 --> 00:31:47,550
Stu,this coffee,it's cold.

575
00:31:48,120 --> 00:31:50,630
Honey,I'm going to beright back.

576
00:31:50,660 --> 00:31:52,500
Mommy? Where are you going?

577
00:31:52,520 --> 00:31:54,100
Right back.

578
00:31:54,160 --> 00:31:56,390
Mommy,come back!

579
00:31:57,000 --> 00:32:00,330
Okay,let's turnto page five.

580
00:32:00,650 --> 00:32:03,850
Damn. I forgot my prospectus.Any extra copies?

581
00:32:03,900 --> 00:32:06,120
No? Oh,I'll be right back.

582
00:32:08,330 --> 00:32:10,740
Hi,I'm back.How's he doing?

583
00:32:10,790 --> 00:32:12,370
Um,um,honey,he's upset

584
00:32:12,400 --> 00:32:14,640
because he wanted to show youhis cubby. You left.

585
00:32:14,680 --> 00:32:16,440
Oh,honey,I'm here.I'm here.

586
00:32:16,480 --> 00:32:18,030
You can show meyour cubby now.

587
00:32:18,070 --> 00:32:21,150
Nina found extra copies.She wants you back now.

588
00:32:21,220 --> 00:32:24,840
Okay. I'll be backin two seconds for you.

589
00:32:24,900 --> 00:32:27,590
Mommy! Mommy!Don't go!

590
00:32:27,700 --> 00:32:31,050
So the big issue hereis second-quarter billing.

591
00:32:31,090 --> 00:32:33,240
Where are you going?Ladies' room.

592
00:32:33,280 --> 00:32:35,240
No.Nina,nature is calling.

593
00:32:35,270 --> 00:32:37,290
Lynette,hold itfor ten minutes.

594
00:32:37,330 --> 00:32:40,000
We have toget through this.

595
00:32:48,710 --> 00:32:51,680
What I'd like to do is trade outthe invoicing structure.

596
00:32:51,700 --> 00:32:55,470
Let's take a look at our graphson page ten,please.

597
00:32:55,500 --> 00:32:58,650
Lynette had been struggling to balance her career

598
00:32:58,680 --> 00:33:00,640
and her family.

599
00:33:00,670 --> 00:33:03,950
She finally saw an opportunity

600
00:33:03,980 --> 00:33:06,800
to tip the scales in her favor.

601
00:33:06,830 --> 00:33:07,950
Instead of badgeringclients with invoices

602
00:33:08,000 --> 00:33:11,490
on the shorter term campaigns,I say we bill on delivery.

603
00:33:11,540 --> 00:33:12,980
Yes!

604
00:33:13,020 --> 00:33:15,760
Bill on delivery,yes!

605
00:33:16,020 --> 00:33:17,960
are you having a seizure?

606
00:33:18,000 --> 00:33:21,190
No,no,I'm just--I'm very excited.

607
00:33:21,230 --> 00:33:23,970
It's a really good plan.

608
00:33:24,240 --> 00:33:26,450
Yeah,mmm.

609
00:33:26,540 --> 00:33:28,800
Now,what happenedon the burman account

610
00:33:28,830 --> 00:33:30,640
is that they were sentduplicate bills

611
00:33:30,670 --> 00:33:33,230
by tina and ronin accounting

612
00:33:33,250 --> 00:33:34,370
and I'm not pointingany fingers,

613
00:33:34,410 --> 00:33:36,450
but tina,ron,

614
00:33:36,480 --> 00:33:38,920
about walking inand seeing all my lines lit up

615
00:33:38,950 --> 00:33:42,100
with disgruntled--aah! Ohh! Hot! Hot!

616
00:33:43,230 --> 00:33:44,800
Help.

617
00:33:44,870 --> 00:33:47,390
Stu! Aah! Aah!

618
00:33:47,400 --> 00:33:49,240
And that's why we packed youextra cookies

619
00:33:49,300 --> 00:33:51,970
so you could share with allyour new friends,remember?

620
00:33:52,010 --> 00:33:52,780
Uh-huh.

621
00:33:52,830 --> 00:33:55,110
I think we're goodto go now,honey.

622
00:33:55,460 --> 00:33:57,320
You're going to be great,parker.

623
00:33:57,670 --> 00:33:58,830
I love you.

624
00:33:58,850 --> 00:34:00,880
I love you,too,mommy.

625
00:34:16,110 --> 00:34:18,140
Bree,hi. What canI do for you?

626
00:34:18,170 --> 00:34:20,280
Well,for starters,you canhelp me prove to the police

627
00:34:20,310 --> 00:34:23,720
that we didn't conspireto kill my husband.

628
00:34:24,370 --> 00:34:25,550
Okay.

629
00:34:25,610 --> 00:34:27,730
So because ofthe anomalies in rex's blood,

630
00:34:27,760 --> 00:34:30,340
the police started to wonderif I'd been poisoning rex.

631
00:34:30,370 --> 00:34:31,250
That's absurd.

632
00:34:31,290 --> 00:34:33,200
Lots of things can causehigh potassium levels--

633
00:34:33,220 --> 00:34:34,730
renal failure,low sodium.

634
00:34:34,780 --> 00:34:36,070
Well,that's why I tookthe polygraph,

635
00:34:36,090 --> 00:34:38,070
to prove to themthat I was innocent.

636
00:34:38,100 --> 00:34:40,580
Obviously,you passed.

637
00:34:41,490 --> 00:34:43,550
Sort of.

638
00:34:43,590 --> 00:34:45,570
Well,I think the policenow have a different theory,

639
00:34:45,600 --> 00:34:48,620
which is if I wasn't poisoningrex on my own,

640
00:34:48,640 --> 00:34:53,310
then maybe you werehelping me.

641
00:34:53,740 --> 00:34:54,550
You're kidding.

642
00:34:54,580 --> 00:34:58,300
No,that's why I need youto take the polygraph,too.

643
00:34:59,450 --> 00:35:00,420
W-what?

644
00:35:00,460 --> 00:35:02,090
It's the quickest wayto prove to the police

645
00:35:02,140 --> 00:35:03,310
that they're wrong.

646
00:35:03,350 --> 00:35:06,020
I-I don't understand.We're just friends.

647
00:35:06,060 --> 00:35:07,290
Why would the police assume

648
00:35:07,340 --> 00:35:09,720
that peoplein a platonic relationship

649
00:35:09,780 --> 00:35:12,650
would want to murder someone?

650
00:35:13,910 --> 00:35:15,830
Um...

651
00:35:16,850 --> 00:35:19,870
um,during the test,they asked me some questions

652
00:35:19,910 --> 00:35:22,570
about you and,um,us

653
00:35:22,590 --> 00:35:23,690
and whether we hada relationship

654
00:35:23,740 --> 00:35:26,900
and I said yes,because it's true.

655
00:35:26,930 --> 00:35:29,140
And then they asked mesomething else,

656
00:35:29,180 --> 00:35:32,150
something I hadn't considered.

657
00:35:32,420 --> 00:35:34,220
Which was?

658
00:35:34,280 --> 00:35:37,590
They asked meif I loved you.

659
00:35:39,100 --> 00:35:41,750
What did you say?

660
00:35:42,050 --> 00:35:44,910
I said no.

661
00:35:45,580 --> 00:35:46,600
Oh.

662
00:35:46,650 --> 00:35:48,490
But accordingto the polygraph,

663
00:35:48,550 --> 00:35:51,620
that wasn't exactly true.

664
00:35:54,280 --> 00:35:57,400
Well,I don't--I don't knowif that means anything.

665
00:35:57,440 --> 00:36:00,880
Polygraphs aren'tcompletely reliable.

666
00:36:00,980 --> 00:36:04,860
I think perhaps the machinepicked up on something,

667
00:36:04,880 --> 00:36:09,580
something that I wasn'taware of.

668
00:36:11,490 --> 00:36:12,420
Wow.

669
00:36:12,460 --> 00:36:14,040
What's why I need youto take the test

670
00:36:14,070 --> 00:36:15,730
and answerthe detective's questions,

671
00:36:15,770 --> 00:36:18,020
because I'm not going to knowexactly how I feel

672
00:36:18,070 --> 00:36:20,560
until we put this behind us,but then,once we do...

673
00:36:20,600 --> 00:36:23,030
we can move on.

674
00:36:25,330 --> 00:36:28,410
can those chicorelli sistersdance or what?

675
00:36:28,450 --> 00:36:30,420
Wow,look out,broadway!

676
00:36:30,450 --> 00:36:33,320
Now don't forget that we willhave cookies and juice

677
00:36:33,350 --> 00:36:35,200
set up in the basementafter we're done here.

678
00:36:35,230 --> 00:36:38,430
We want to see you all there.And for our next act,

679
00:36:38,470 --> 00:36:40,610
please welcomethe musical stylings

680
00:36:40,650 --> 00:36:43,860
of julie and susan mayer.

681
00:37:11,630 --> 00:37:13,300
I'll be right back.

682
00:37:13,350 --> 00:37:16,690
Oh,um,I'm just gonna needa couple of seconds,

683
00:37:16,740 --> 00:37:19,930
so feel free to pray.

684
00:37:22,490 --> 00:37:25,340
Edie,the other day when I sawyou making music with my family,

685
00:37:25,380 --> 00:37:27,450
I got a little jealousand I went a little crazy

686
00:37:27,480 --> 00:37:30,550
and I pushed you out.

687
00:37:30,590 --> 00:37:33,420
Seeing you sitting here today,

688
00:37:33,460 --> 00:37:36,960
well,I can see how muchyou care about julie,

689
00:37:37,420 --> 00:37:40,230
and she comes first,

690
00:37:40,330 --> 00:37:43,820
and it should be you up thereplaying with her,not me.

691
00:37:43,860 --> 00:37:46,760
So I'm sorry.

692
00:37:46,800 --> 00:37:49,090
Thank you,susan.

693
00:37:55,460 --> 00:37:57,630
How convenientthat you decided this

694
00:37:57,660 --> 00:38:00,990
after I showed upwithout my guitar.

695
00:38:02,190 --> 00:38:04,840
Well,like I said,I'm sorry.

696
00:38:04,900 --> 00:38:06,860
I wish it could be youup there.

697
00:38:06,920 --> 00:38:09,650
You know,I play piano.

698
00:38:11,710 --> 00:38:13,740
And so let's all welcomejulie mayer

699
00:38:13,780 --> 00:38:16,370
and her aunt edie.

700
00:38:16,490 --> 00:38:18,180
whoo-hoo!

701
00:38:21,770 --> 00:38:24,250
You did a good thing.

702
00:38:24,330 --> 00:38:26,550
Yeah,well,I try.

703
00:38:27,580 --> 00:38:33,620
this little light of mine

704
00:38:36,010 --> 00:38:40,860
I'm gonna let it shine

705
00:38:40,900 --> 00:38:45,890
this little light of mine

706
00:38:45,940 --> 00:38:52,380
I'm gonna let it shine ohh,give me a break.

707
00:38:52,440 --> 00:38:55,330
This thing has,like,90 flats in it.

708
00:38:56,570 --> 00:38:58,220
poor julie.

709
00:38:58,270 --> 00:39:01,270
Stop it. You're loving this.

710
00:39:01,470 --> 00:39:04,380
No,not at all

711
00:39:04,420 --> 00:39:08,950
let it shine,shine,shine

712
00:39:09,020 --> 00:39:14,150
let it shine

713
00:39:27,010 --> 00:39:30,690
so they said you neededto see me.

714
00:39:30,730 --> 00:39:33,510
What is it?What's goin' on?

715
00:39:33,880 --> 00:39:39,420
Um,I've been thinking...

716
00:39:40,480 --> 00:39:43,270
you know,about,um...

717
00:39:44,160 --> 00:39:46,480
everything that happenedwith john...

718
00:39:46,520 --> 00:39:48,570
and...

719
00:39:49,820 --> 00:39:51,910
and,um...

720
00:39:52,870 --> 00:39:59,090
I was really selfishand stupid.

721
00:40:02,420 --> 00:40:04,780
And I'm sorry.

722
00:40:06,780 --> 00:40:09,760
I really am sorry.

723
00:40:21,590 --> 00:40:25,520
That's all I had to say,really.

724
00:40:27,600 --> 00:40:30,110
You know what?

725
00:40:30,240 --> 00:40:33,820
That isthe best anniversary gift

726
00:40:33,870 --> 00:40:36,730
that you've ever given me.

727
00:40:36,980 --> 00:40:38,210
Really?

728
00:40:38,360 --> 00:40:40,470
Yeah.

729
00:40:42,790 --> 00:40:47,090
Actually,the one you gave meis really nice,too.

730
00:40:51,800 --> 00:40:55,400
Everyone enjoys a game of make-believe now and then.

731
00:40:55,450 --> 00:40:59,980
Of course,the ways in which we play can vary greatly.

732
00:41:00,930 --> 00:41:04,320
Sometimes we tell ourselves work won't interfere

733
00:41:04,380 --> 00:41:06,080
with our family life.

734
00:41:06,140 --> 00:41:07,510
lynette,staff meeting,now.

735
00:41:07,560 --> 00:41:09,090
Yeah.

736
00:41:11,120 --> 00:41:14,100
Sometimes,we imagine certain relationships

737
00:41:14,140 --> 00:41:18,440
to be more meaningful than they really are.

738
00:41:22,440 --> 00:41:25,170
Occasionally,we put on a show,

739
00:41:25,210 --> 00:41:28,150
as if to convince ourselves our secrets

740
00:41:28,200 --> 00:41:31,330
aren't really all that terrible.

741
00:41:32,250 --> 00:41:36,660
Yes,the game of make-believe is a simple one.

742
00:41:36,700 --> 00:41:39,180
Did you knowrex van de kamp?

743
00:41:39,220 --> 00:41:40,900
Yes.

744
00:41:41,040 --> 00:41:44,790
Did mrs. Van de kampask you to poison her husband?

745
00:41:44,820 --> 00:41:46,830
No.

746
00:41:47,450 --> 00:41:49,600
Did you poisonrex van de kamp?

747
00:41:49,660 --> 00:41:52,490
You start by lying to yourself...

748
00:41:52,530 --> 00:41:54,520
no.

749
00:41:57,510 --> 00:42:02,230
And if you can getothers to believe those lies...

750
00:42:02,280 --> 00:42:03,930
you win.

