1
00:00:00,260 --> 00:00:02,020
Previously on desperate housewives...

2
00:00:02,160 --> 00:00:03,140
you're glowing today,you know that?

3
00:00:03,280 --> 00:00:04,670
Gabrielle got pregnant...

4
00:00:04,790 --> 00:00:06,110
You walked out on me

5
00:00:06,220 --> 00:00:08,820
Yeah,but look how far I got

6
00:00:09,220 --> 00:00:10,130
I'm just up the street

7
00:00:10,270 --> 00:00:11,390
Trouble moved in...

8
00:00:11,520 --> 00:00:13,800
being with george made youfeel a bit guilty.

9
00:00:13,940 --> 00:00:15,720
Well,I'll just have to get over it,won't I?

10
00:00:15,840 --> 00:00:17,390
And bree moved on...

11
00:00:17,530 --> 00:00:19,430
"I know who really killed Melanie Foster

12
00:00:19,570 --> 00:00:20,750
"You arrested the wrong man"?

13
00:00:20,870 --> 00:00:22,060
But not everyone...

14
00:00:22,200 --> 00:00:23,110
call 9-1-1 and tell 'em

15
00:00:23,110 --> 00:00:24,670
you got a killer locked up in the basement

16
00:00:24,760 --> 00:00:25,600
He is not a killer.

17
00:00:25,740 --> 00:00:28,710
Got what they deserved.

18
00:00:32,230 --> 00:00:37,490
It is often said that necessity is the 
mother of invention.

19
00:00:37,630 --> 00:00:41,220
This is how mothers came to invent play dates--

20
00:00:41,370 --> 00:00:44,740
so they occasionally could have a 
little time for themselves.

21
00:00:44,870 --> 00:00:46,940
If you need me,I'll be at the salon.

22
00:00:47,080 --> 00:00:48,230
But there are some mothers

23
00:00:48,370 --> 00:00:52,120
who don't get to take advantage of this 
maternal innovation--

24
00:00:52,270 --> 00:00:55,140
mothers like lynette scavo,

25
00:00:55,280 --> 00:00:58,160
who was no longer able to rest on weekends

26
00:00:58,300 --> 00:01:02,270
because her twins no longer received play 
date invitations,

27
00:01:02,930 --> 00:01:05,400
ever since they had convinced sasha eden's boy

28
00:01:05,530 --> 00:01:09,980
that a pair of magic wings would allow him to fly.

29
00:01:10,570 --> 00:01:12,860
And they had double-dared sharon chazin's boy

30
00:01:13,060 --> 00:01:17,150
to ride his bike blindfolded.

31
00:01:18,250 --> 00:01:20,570
And they had encouraged lisa siegmann's boy

32
00:01:20,720 --> 00:01:25,290
to try an exciting new game called "toss the brick."

33
00:01:25,880 --> 00:01:29,610
The scavo twins had become persona non grata,

34
00:01:30,330 --> 00:01:31,830
and lynette's secret dream

35
00:01:31,970 --> 00:01:35,740
of being able to take an occasional nap on saturdays

36
00:01:35,880 --> 00:01:39,180
was growing dimmer and dimmer...

37
00:01:39,230 --> 00:01:41,800
aah!

38
00:01:42,140 --> 00:01:43,480
until one day...

39
00:01:43,620 --> 00:01:45,240
hey,hey,hey,hey!Porter,preston,knock it off!

40
00:01:45,380 --> 00:01:47,970
All right? Did you hear me?I said stop it. Stand up.

41
00:01:48,120 --> 00:01:51,180
Stand up. Come here.

42
00:01:51,310 --> 00:01:53,800
I'm so sorry.Did my son beat you up?

43
00:01:53,940 --> 00:01:56,200
No. We were beating them up.

44
00:01:56,320 --> 00:01:57,980
Is that true?Did they beat you up?

45
00:01:58,140 --> 00:02:00,130
Ah,it didn't hurt that much.

46
00:02:00,190 --> 00:02:03,160
Jimmy,P.J.,What are you doing?

47
00:02:03,300 --> 00:02:06,040
What have I told you about ganging up on people?

48
00:02:06,110 --> 00:02:07,260
I am so sorry.

49
00:02:07,410 --> 00:02:09,400
No,it's okay.You know,believe me,

50
00:02:09,550 --> 00:02:11,140
my boys can take careof themselves.

51
00:02:11,300 --> 00:02:13,710
If they got hurt at all,I'll pay for the doctor bills.

52
00:02:13,800 --> 00:02:14,610
No,not to worry.

53
00:02:14,750 --> 00:02:18,800
I got the feeling they were sort of 
enjoying themselves.

54
00:02:20,680 --> 00:02:22,380
Really?

55
00:02:25,460 --> 00:02:27,500
What would you say to bringing your boys 
over to my house

56
00:02:27,630 --> 00:02:30,430
and letting them hang out with mine sometime?

57
00:02:30,590 --> 00:02:34,210
And that's how lynette finally got 
what she needed--

58
00:02:34,410 --> 00:02:36,000
time for herself...

59
00:02:36,440 --> 00:02:39,470
and play dates for her kids...

60
00:02:41,580 --> 00:02:42,500
I'm sorry,

61
00:02:42,670 --> 00:02:45,850
but my boys decided to have a rock 
fight with your boys.

62
00:02:46,010 --> 00:02:48,120
It was fun!

63
00:02:48,540 --> 00:02:51,270
Play dates she was determined to keep...

64
00:02:51,430 --> 00:02:54,150
well,they look fine to me.

65
00:02:54,310 --> 00:02:55,990
At all costs.

66
00:02:56,110 --> 00:02:57,860
Same time next week?

67
00:02:58,010 --> 00:02:59,500
Okay.

68
00:03:01,000 --> 00:03:01,840
-------------------------- 
www.ydy.com/bbs
Proudly Presents
--------------------------

69
00:03:02,060 --> 00:03:03,710
Sync: YTET-Starry
-==www.ydy.com/bbs==-

70
00:03:03,870 --> 00:03:05,030
Desperate Housewives
Season 2 Episode 7

71
00:03:06,020 --> 00:03:09,810
Cameras are simple tools designed 
to capture images--

72
00:03:09,970 --> 00:03:14,610
images that tell us more about ourselves 
than we realized

73
00:03:14,830 --> 00:03:18,600
They remind us of the long journey we've taken

74
00:03:18,830 --> 00:03:22,530
the loved ones who traveled alongside us...

75
00:03:22,790 --> 00:03:26,060
those we lost along the way...

76
00:03:26,210 --> 00:03:30,510
and those waiting for us on the road ahead

77
00:03:30,810 --> 00:03:31,890
Okay.

78
00:03:32,080 --> 00:03:32,910
How am I supposed to eat with

79
00:03:33,040 --> 00:03:34,510
a uterus staring me in the face?

80
00:03:34,660 --> 00:03:36,640
Oh,gaby,I didn't know you got a sonogram

81
00:03:36,710 --> 00:03:38,770
Let me see. Oh.

82
00:03:38,920 --> 00:03:41,440
Honey,you need to put that in a frame 
or something

83
00:03:41,540 --> 00:03:42,800
I don't think so.

84
00:03:42,940 --> 00:03:45,300
Oh,come on. That's a picture of your baby

85
00:03:45,390 --> 00:03:47,540
You can't tell me you're not a little bit excited

86
00:03:47,690 --> 00:03:50,590
Fine. I'm pregnant. Whee!

87
00:03:50,860 --> 00:03:52,230
Now come on.

88
00:03:52,370 --> 00:03:54,010
We're supposed to be cheering up susan.

89
00:03:54,130 --> 00:03:55,440
This is a time of crisis,

90
00:03:55,590 --> 00:03:58,420
and I think you need another scoop of 
mint chocolate chip

91
00:03:58,560 --> 00:03:59,260
Thanks.

92
00:03:59,320 --> 00:04:02,810
Susan,why are you so eerily calm?

93
00:04:02,960 --> 00:04:04,440
Mike delfino just dumped you.

94
00:04:04,560 --> 00:04:06,170
The susan mayer I know would be a...

95
00:04:06,310 --> 00:04:08,330
...blubbering mess right now.

96
00:04:08,540 --> 00:04:10,230
Oh,come on. Trot her on out.

97
00:04:10,370 --> 00:04:11,320
She's fun to watch.

98
00:04:11,480 --> 00:04:13,650
Actually,I think I'm starting to feel pretty zen

99
00:04:13,720 --> 00:04:14,670
about the whole thing.

100
00:04:14,810 --> 00:04:16,000
Well,I think mike will calm down

101
00:04:16,150 --> 00:04:18,010
in a  couple of days and come to his senses.

102
00:04:18,040 --> 00:04:20,910
No. I came between the man and his son

103
00:04:21,050 --> 00:04:22,560
It was a huge betrayal.

104
00:04:22,630 --> 00:04:24,900
I can't even blame him for hating me

105
00:04:25,020 --> 00:04:27,370
But zach was starting to obsess with julie again

106
00:04:27,510 --> 00:04:29,900
Exactly. You're a mother tring to protect her child

107
00:04:29,980 --> 00:04:31,830
It's a natural impulse.

108
00:04:32,220 --> 00:04:34,190
Over the past couple of days,

109
00:04:34,340 --> 00:04:36,180
I gave myself a long,hard look in the mirror

110
00:04:36,300 --> 00:04:38,500
and I did not like what I saw.

111
00:04:38,630 --> 00:04:40,950
I'm with you. Carry on.

112
00:04:41,050 --> 00:04:44,260
I just think if I start acting like an adult for once

113
00:04:44,380 --> 00:04:46,610
maybe... who knows?

114
00:04:46,750 --> 00:04:47,540
Somewhere down the line,

115
00:04:47,710 --> 00:04:50,220
mike and I at least can be friends

116
00:04:50,340 --> 00:04:52,160
All right,you're not zen.

117
00:04:52,300 --> 00:04:53,130
You're numb.

118
00:04:53,250 --> 00:04:55,460
I'm fine.

119
00:04:56,630 --> 00:04:58,000
Do you got any pie?

120
00:04:58,150 --> 00:05:00,430
Not unless we make some.

121
00:05:00,900 --> 00:05:02,650
I can wait.

122
00:05:05,270 --> 00:05:06,880
Whoa

123
00:05:08,250 --> 00:05:09,680
so if you need us,

124
00:05:09,830 --> 00:05:10,630
we'll be at home,

125
00:05:10,700 --> 00:05:13,080
just having a quiet evening.

126
00:05:15,340 --> 00:05:17,790
funny. We're expecting quite the opposite

127
00:05:17,910 --> 00:05:19,650
Well,don't forget,next week it's our turn

128
00:05:19,770 --> 00:05:20,800
We'll be taking porter and...

129
00:05:20,950 --> 00:05:22,520
- preston. 
- Preston off your hands all weekend

130
00:05:22,610 --> 00:05:25,490
Rest assured,we have not forgotten

131
00:05:25,630 --> 00:05:26,930
See ya.

132
00:05:27,080 --> 00:05:27,620
Bye.

133
00:05:27,760 --> 00:05:28,970
don't worry.

134
00:05:32,240 --> 00:05:33,150
Whoa,guys.

135
00:05:33,230 --> 00:05:35,170
Whoa,why aren't you upstairs with 
P.J and Jimmy?

136
00:05:35,280 --> 00:05:37,370
They're watching this dumb video they brought

137
00:05:37,390 --> 00:05:38,260
It's boring.

138
00:05:38,420 --> 00:05:39,750
Well,you should be polite and watch it,too

139
00:05:39,930 --> 00:05:42,320
You know,they're our guests

140
00:05:44,140 --> 00:05:46,520
Guys.

141
00:05:48,430 --> 00:05:51,160
hey,guys,we have snacks.

142
00:05:51,190 --> 00:05:52,120
fix the light,

143
00:05:52,120 --> 00:05:54,230
then we're good to go.

144
00:05:54,630 --> 00:05:56,240
- Okay,ready? 
- Okay

145
00:05:56,390 --> 00:05:58,010
All right,hang on now.

146
00:05:58,770 --> 00:06:00,380
Guys,what is this?

147
00:06:00,600 --> 00:06:01,440
A movie.

148
00:06:01,600 --> 00:06:04,410
Mommy and daddy made it.

149
00:06:04,460 --> 00:06:04,980
Peekaboo.

150
00:06:05,140 --> 00:06:06,220
Whoa. What's under there?

151
00:06:06,360 --> 00:06:09,030
Peekaboo. Peekaboo.

152
00:06:09,240 --> 00:06:10,910
oh,my god! Oh,my god!

153
00:06:10,940 --> 00:06:12,230
Where's the "off" button?

154
00:06:12,350 --> 00:06:13,780
It's underneath the panel thing

155
00:06:13,840 --> 00:06:14,830
Well,it's stuck,it's stuck.

156
00:06:14,960 --> 00:06:17,100
Get the remote. Get the remote.

157
00:06:17,810 --> 00:06:19,640
What's wrong?

158
00:06:19,750 --> 00:06:21,210
Oh!

159
00:06:22,130 --> 00:06:23,880
I found it.

160
00:06:24,140 --> 00:06:26,750
oh. Ahem.

161
00:06:28,980 --> 00:06:31,880
So can we have the cocoa now?

162
00:06:36,540 --> 00:06:38,410
Well,what do you think?

163
00:06:40,430 --> 00:06:41,570
It is glorious.

164
00:06:41,710 --> 00:06:43,010
I have to have it.

165
00:06:43,160 --> 00:06:45,070
I'm not sure you deserve Dolce & gabbana

166
00:06:45,110 --> 00:06:45,680
Vern.

167
00:06:45,770 --> 00:06:47,050
You never call. You never write

168
00:06:47,080 --> 00:06:48,600
I know I haven't been in the store lately

169
00:06:48,750 --> 00:06:49,660
but I've been a little busy

170
00:06:49,790 --> 00:06:51,060
getting my husband out of jail.

171
00:06:51,200 --> 00:06:53,080
That is such a write trash thing to say

172
00:06:53,260 --> 00:06:55,850
Luckily,the judge dropped the hate crime charge

173
00:06:55,990 --> 00:06:57,250
so now all carlos has to do is

174
00:06:57,390 --> 00:06:59,490
serve out the slave labor thing.

175
00:06:59,580 --> 00:07:01,080
He'll be out in six months.

176
00:07:01,220 --> 00:07:02,140
If he's still in the hoosegow,

177
00:07:02,290 --> 00:07:03,610
why do you need a fancy party dress?

178
00:07:03,740 --> 00:07:04,930
Because some of my model friends

179
00:07:05,100 --> 00:07:07,160
are coming down from new york on friday,

180
00:07:07,330 --> 00:07:08,690
so I have to look better than ever.

181
00:07:08,860 --> 00:07:10,810
I can't have 'em thinking I moved to the suburbs

182
00:07:10,940 --> 00:07:12,310
and now I shop at strip malls.

183
00:07:12,450 --> 00:07:14,380
But when they see this dress,
they will crumple to the floor

184
00:07:14,510 --> 00:07:16,150
like the botoxed hags they are.

185
00:07:16,310 --> 00:07:17,290
Good

186
00:07:18,360 --> 00:07:20,360
you know,it's a little snug.

187
00:07:20,450 --> 00:07:22,910
Yeah,I see that. I have the same thing in a zero.

188
00:07:22,960 --> 00:07:24,820
Why not go up a size?

189
00:07:24,960 --> 00:07:26,860
Because I wear double zero,you twerp.

190
00:07:26,990 --> 00:07:27,900
Why you getting snippy?

191
00:07:28,040 --> 00:07:29,180
Because you just called me fat.

192
00:07:29,320 --> 00:07:33,340
Honey,you're pregnant.Your body's changing.

193
00:07:33,500 --> 00:07:34,830
But I'm only three months pregnant.

194
00:07:34,990 --> 00:07:37,030
Women don't show at three months.

195
00:07:37,140 --> 00:07:38,560
Some women do.

196
00:07:38,730 --> 00:07:40,910
Do you want the larger sizeor not?

197
00:07:42,550 --> 00:07:45,230
I'm just not gonna eat for two days.

198
00:07:45,980 --> 00:07:48,580
okay,you totally deserve to wear dolce & gabbana.

199
00:07:51,500 --> 00:07:53,620
I want an explanation,karl.

200
00:07:53,730 --> 00:07:54,600
Do you hear me?

201
00:07:54,680 --> 00:07:56,980
Edie,you just better get the hell off my back,

202
00:07:57,030 --> 00:07:57,680
so help me.

203
00:07:57,820 --> 00:08:00,000
Oh,what are you gonna do?
I'd like to hear this.

204
00:08:00,180 --> 00:08:01,880
The big man with the big threats.

205
00:08:02,010 --> 00:08:04,810
Back off.Just back the hell off.

206
00:08:08,870 --> 00:08:10,210
Hi.

207
00:08:11,280 --> 00:08:14,410
Okay,so I got the box of things
you left on my porch.

208
00:08:14,550 --> 00:08:16,810
Yeah,I figured you'd want your stuff back.

209
00:08:16,890 --> 00:08:18,660
Thanks. That's great,

210
00:08:18,730 --> 00:08:21,140
'cause if you decided to hang onto 
my joni mitchell cds,

211
00:08:21,270 --> 00:08:23,320
I would have had to come after you with a club.

212
00:08:26,520 --> 00:08:28,130
you're right.It's not funny.

213
00:08:28,760 --> 00:08:32,320
Actually,I did want to just see if 
you were aware that you

214
00:08:32,460 --> 00:08:35,400
gave me backthe valentine's day card 
I made you

215
00:08:35,790 --> 00:08:37,990
I was aware,yeah.

216
00:08:38,390 --> 00:08:43,450
Oh. Well,I mean,when two people split up,

217
00:08:43,670 --> 00:08:44,930
normally they don't give things back

218
00:08:45,040 --> 00:08:46,320
like valentine's day cards.

219
00:08:46,470 --> 00:08:48,290
If you don't want it,you can throw it away.

220
00:08:48,450 --> 00:08:52,340
Just please don't give it back to me. 
It's tacky.

221
00:08:52,640 --> 00:08:54,090
I'm sorry.

222
00:08:54,250 --> 00:08:58,830
That's okay.People make... mistakes.

223
00:08:58,960 --> 00:09:01,080
Anything else?

224
00:09:02,220 --> 00:09:04,960
Look,are you sure this is what you want to do?

225
00:09:05,120 --> 00:09:06,090
I mean,I understand

226
00:09:06,240 --> 00:09:07,970
that you don't want our relationship to continue.

227
00:09:08,130 --> 00:09:09,970
You have made that clear,but...

228
00:09:10,120 --> 00:09:13,100
I sort of thought down the long 
corridors of time,

229
00:09:13,250 --> 00:09:15,050
maybe you and I could be friends,

230
00:09:15,200 --> 00:09:16,540
and if you keep acting like this--

231
00:09:16,690 --> 00:09:19,600
susan,it's over on every level,okay? I...

232
00:09:19,830 --> 00:09:23,010
I've moved on.You should do the same.

233
00:09:23,120 --> 00:09:26,120
miserable son of a bitch!

234
00:09:26,750 --> 00:09:27,360
If I have secrets,

235
00:09:27,490 --> 00:09:31,600
I'm a hell of a lot betterat keeping them 
than you are!

236
00:09:34,700 --> 00:09:36,540
well,I'll say one thing for us.

237
00:09:36,690 --> 00:09:37,750
Even with all our problems,

238
00:09:37,890 --> 00:09:40,090
at least we're not acting like that.

239
00:09:45,330 --> 00:09:46,990
Okay,I'm starting to get the feeling

240
00:09:47,140 --> 00:09:49,300
that we're not going to a yard sale.

241
00:09:49,440 --> 00:09:52,380
That was just a clever ruse to 
get you into my car.

242
00:09:52,520 --> 00:09:53,810
Are you ready for your surprise?

243
00:09:53,970 --> 00:09:55,600
Mm-hmm.

244
00:09:57,750 --> 00:09:59,450
Oh.

245
00:10:00,170 --> 00:10:02,320
George,this is just an empty house.

246
00:10:02,460 --> 00:10:04,300
Why is this a surprise?

247
00:10:04,440 --> 00:10:06,430
I just bought it.

248
00:10:06,690 --> 00:10:09,340
Oh,my god! Congratulations.

249
00:10:09,620 --> 00:10:11,400
Oh,george,I didn't even know you were looking.

250
00:10:11,610 --> 00:10:14,030
Hurry,ceal. They're here!

251
00:10:14,160 --> 00:10:16,550
I'm coming.Hey,georgie.

252
00:10:16,610 --> 00:10:18,430
Bree,I'd like you to meet my mother.

253
00:10:18,550 --> 00:10:21,790
George never introduces me to anyone.

254
00:10:21,900 --> 00:10:24,690
So I knew you were special.

255
00:10:24,830 --> 00:10:27,030
And this is ceal,my mother's friend,

256
00:10:27,090 --> 00:10:29,050
and the real estate agent who sold me the house.

257
00:10:29,200 --> 00:10:29,990
Hi.

258
00:10:30,150 --> 00:10:31,150
Hi.

259
00:10:31,290 --> 00:10:33,280
Well,we're gonna go in the back

260
00:10:33,440 --> 00:10:38,000
so george can,you know...

261
00:10:41,950 --> 00:10:43,370
so...

262
00:10:44,690 --> 00:10:46,220
do you really like it?

263
00:10:46,390 --> 00:10:48,270
I do. I really do.

264
00:10:48,540 --> 00:10:51,970
Good,'cause I was sort of hoping that...

265
00:10:52,080 --> 00:10:54,950
you might like to live here.

266
00:10:56,450 --> 00:10:58,310
Bree...

267
00:11:00,440 --> 00:11:03,690
will you marry me?

268
00:11:04,850 --> 00:11:05,900
Huh?

269
00:11:06,220 --> 00:11:07,450
I love you,

270
00:11:07,600 --> 00:11:11,170
and I think I know how you feel about me,
so why wait?

271
00:11:11,320 --> 00:11:14,220
George,rex hasn't even been dead for two months.

272
00:11:14,350 --> 00:11:16,760
Yes,but if his death has taught us anything,

273
00:11:16,910 --> 00:11:20,940
it's that life is short.It's dumb to play it safe.

274
00:11:21,090 --> 00:11:22,390
If we see a chance for happiness,

275
00:11:22,540 --> 00:11:25,450
we should grab it and hold on tight.

276
00:11:25,870 --> 00:11:29,430
See,I thought we were going to a yard sale.

277
00:11:29,760 --> 00:11:32,560
Please. Just say the word,

278
00:11:32,730 --> 00:11:36,020
and you'll make methe happiest guy on earth.

279
00:11:36,840 --> 00:11:38,930
congratulations,you two.

280
00:11:39,060 --> 00:11:41,060
Mazel tov.

281
00:11:41,160 --> 00:11:44,310
Guys,wait.She hasn't said yes yet.

282
00:11:44,470 --> 00:11:45,150
Oh.

283
00:11:45,310 --> 00:11:48,990
I told you we should wait.

284
00:11:50,690 --> 00:11:53,140
Um... so,uh,bree...

285
00:11:53,290 --> 00:11:55,120
what do you say?

286
00:11:55,260 --> 00:11:59,070
See,george,um,the thing is...

287
00:12:10,120 --> 00:12:11,360
okay.

288
00:12:11,520 --> 00:12:12,960
You will?

289
00:12:13,050 --> 00:12:14,390
You'll marry me?

290
00:12:14,490 --> 00:12:16,120
Okay.

291
00:12:18,220 --> 00:12:20,540
oh!

292
00:12:23,120 --> 00:12:25,700
oh,my baby!

293
00:12:36,990 --> 00:12:38,190
Who is it?

294
00:12:38,300 --> 00:12:40,100
It's your ex-husband.

295
00:12:40,230 --> 00:12:42,910
Oh. Karl.

296
00:12:43,050 --> 00:12:44,840
What do you want?

297
00:12:45,150 --> 00:12:47,970
Edie and I just broke up.

298
00:12:48,110 --> 00:12:52,400
Oh. Well,come on in.

299
00:12:56,100 --> 00:12:57,770
Sorry to come over on such short notice,

300
00:12:57,810 --> 00:12:59,720
but I couldn't face going to a motel.

301
00:12:59,860 --> 00:13:01,930
That's okay. Julie's staying at a friend's tonight.

302
00:13:02,070 --> 00:13:03,460
You can sleep in her room.

303
00:13:03,580 --> 00:13:06,380
Well,the sofa's fine,but thanks.

304
00:13:08,550 --> 00:13:10,980
So am I allowed to ask what happened?

305
00:13:11,110 --> 00:13:13,280
You could ask,but I won't tell.

306
00:13:13,430 --> 00:13:16,410
- Why not?
- 'Cause it's embarrassing.

307
00:13:16,580 --> 00:13:18,080
Karl,did you cheat again?

308
00:13:18,220 --> 00:13:19,310
No.

309
00:13:19,460 --> 00:13:20,750
Did she cheat?

310
00:13:20,890 --> 00:13:21,590
No

311
00:13:21,670 --> 00:13:23,400
You finally saw her without her makeup.

312
00:13:23,540 --> 00:13:26,810
- Susan... 
- I'm sorry

313
00:13:27,790 --> 00:13:29,070
Are you okay?

314
00:13:29,200 --> 00:13:32,570
Yeah. It hadn't been working for 
quite a while.

315
00:13:32,710 --> 00:13:34,790
This was inevitable.

316
00:13:34,890 --> 00:13:36,610
Well,these days,

317
00:13:36,760 --> 00:13:39,130
anybody going through a breakup 
gets my sympathy.

318
00:13:39,290 --> 00:13:41,980
That's right. I heard you made 
the plumber angry.

319
00:13:42,120 --> 00:13:45,180
No,I made the plumber furious,

320
00:13:45,330 --> 00:13:49,280
and it's definitely over.

321
00:13:49,710 --> 00:13:52,860
So there will be no gloating from me.

322
00:13:53,200 --> 00:13:56,760
Well,here's to no gloating.

323
00:13:57,610 --> 00:14:00,500
mm. Actually,I'm trying to keep 
a positive outlook

324
00:14:00,650 --> 00:14:01,970
on the whole thing. um..

325
00:14:02,110 --> 00:14:04,720
last night,I started writing,and...

326
00:14:04,770 --> 00:14:06,220
well,I think there's a book in there.

327
00:14:06,280 --> 00:14:06,970
- A book?
- Yeah.

328
00:14:07,060 --> 00:14:08,130
Like one of your children's books?

329
00:14:08,280 --> 00:14:10,100
No. This one's for adults,

330
00:14:10,240 --> 00:14:13,050
about all my failed relationships.

331
00:14:13,190 --> 00:14:14,650
You're not writing about me,are you?

332
00:14:14,750 --> 00:14:17,540
You're like the first 14 chapters.

333
00:14:18,450 --> 00:14:19,790
Are you gonna be fair?

334
00:14:19,950 --> 00:14:21,490
I'm gonna be honest.

335
00:14:21,630 --> 00:14:24,840
I was afraid of that.

336
00:14:26,250 --> 00:14:28,390
it was just awful.

337
00:14:28,550 --> 00:14:29,660
George had a ring.

338
00:14:29,830 --> 00:14:31,820
His mother and her friend were there 
with champagne.

339
00:14:31,940 --> 00:14:35,030
If I had said "no,"it would have devastated him.

340
00:14:35,180 --> 00:14:38,100
So you agreed to marry him just to be polite?

341
00:14:38,140 --> 00:14:38,900
Well,obviously,

342
00:14:39,050 --> 00:14:42,010
there's a downside to having good manners.

343
00:14:42,270 --> 00:14:45,260
So when will you tell him how you really feel?

344
00:14:45,320 --> 00:14:46,530
That's why I wanted to talk to you.

345
00:14:46,560 --> 00:14:47,540
I mean,part of me

346
00:14:47,640 --> 00:14:50,380
keeps thingking maybe I should just do it.

347
00:14:50,570 --> 00:14:53,830
Do it?You mean actually marry him?

348
00:14:53,830 --> 00:14:55,560
Well,I know it sounds rash,but...

349
00:14:55,690 --> 00:14:58,600
well,there's something comfortable about george.

350
00:14:58,740 --> 00:15:01,220
We share the same tastes and interests.

351
00:15:01,270 --> 00:15:04,010
Oh,and best of all,he loves the opera.

352
00:15:04,130 --> 00:15:04,800
The opera?

353
00:15:04,920 --> 00:15:08,460
Yes,we saw "aida" last week,
and we both cried buckets

354
00:15:08,590 --> 00:15:10,950
It was fun.

355
00:15:11,160 --> 00:15:14,830
George loves art,poetry and music.

356
00:15:14,990 --> 00:15:16,920
It would be nice to be married to someone who

357
00:15:17,070 --> 00:15:20,970
looks for beauty in the world like I do.

358
00:15:25,820 --> 00:15:27,820
I don't know.That's why I'm here.

359
00:15:27,960 --> 00:15:30,510
I don't know what to do,dr. Goldfine.

360
00:15:31,560 --> 00:15:33,020
Bree,you've said many times

361
00:15:33,150 --> 00:15:34,840
how comfortable you are with george,

362
00:15:34,980 --> 00:15:39,230
but you don't feel for him the way you felt for rex.

363
00:15:39,450 --> 00:15:41,160
No.

364
00:15:44,820 --> 00:15:47,690
True love is great.

365
00:15:48,150 --> 00:15:50,650
But at this point in my life,

366
00:15:51,160 --> 00:15:54,610
I think I'd rather just go to the opera.

367
00:15:57,570 --> 00:15:58,310
Give me your glass

368
00:15:58,310 --> 00:15:59,090
-We gotta finish off this.
- Oh,no,no,wait

369
00:15:59,220 --> 00:16:02,780
No way,no way,no way.
Four glasses is my limit.

370
00:16:02,860 --> 00:16:05,040
If you help me finish off this bottle,

371
00:16:05,210 --> 00:16:09,170
I'll tell you what happened between me and edie.

372
00:16:09,310 --> 00:16:10,880
Hit me.

373
00:16:17,720 --> 00:16:20,400
edie was making the bed

374
00:16:20,560 --> 00:16:24,850
and found a picture I kept under the mattress--

375
00:16:25,010 --> 00:16:28,440
a picture I didn't want her to see.

376
00:16:28,600 --> 00:16:30,720
What was it?

377
00:16:31,680 --> 00:16:34,590
It was a picture of you.

378
00:16:35,190 --> 00:16:36,150
Why would you...

379
00:16:36,310 --> 00:16:38,330
because it's something I like to take a look at

380
00:16:38,490 --> 00:16:40,810
every now and then.

381
00:16:40,960 --> 00:16:42,820
Wow.

382
00:16:52,670 --> 00:16:54,480
- what the hell was that? 
- That was something

383
00:16:54,620 --> 00:16:56,650
I've been wanting to do for quite some time.

384
00:16:56,790 --> 00:17:00,010
Oh,that's just you're bounding from edie.

385
00:17:00,160 --> 00:17:01,770
So you're on the rebound from the plumber.

386
00:17:01,910 --> 00:17:04,390
No harm,no foul.

387
00:17:05,590 --> 00:17:07,430
Karl,it would be so weird.

388
00:17:07,580 --> 00:17:10,620
We're two old friends who suddenly 
find themselves single.

389
00:17:10,780 --> 00:17:12,350
There's nothing weird about us

390
00:17:12,510 --> 00:17:15,540
helping each other out to be...

391
00:17:16,440 --> 00:17:19,170
a little less lonely.

392
00:17:22,770 --> 00:17:24,660
Thanks so much for taking care of the boys.

393
00:17:24,810 --> 00:17:26,780
I'll be back on friday to pick your guys up.

394
00:17:26,960 --> 00:17:29,310
Leonard and I are gonna take them all 
to the water park.

395
00:17:29,440 --> 00:17:31,790
Yeah,um,before that happens...

396
00:17:31,840 --> 00:17:33,860
and we're gonna be able to take penny soon,
aren't we?

397
00:17:34,000 --> 00:17:37,840
She's getting so big

398
00:17:38,210 --> 00:17:40,390
peekaboo.

399
00:17:40,550 --> 00:17:42,660
Peekaboo. Peekaboo.

400
00:17:42,660 --> 00:17:45,060
Yeah,okay,enough of that

401
00:17:45,290 --> 00:17:46,350
is there something wrong?

402
00:17:46,510 --> 00:17:48,690
Actually,yes.

403
00:17:48,840 --> 00:17:52,480
We've agonized whether to tell you this,
norma,but...

404
00:17:52,650 --> 00:17:55,620
one of your...private videos

405
00:17:55,760 --> 00:18:00,370
made its way into jimmy and P.J.'S bag.

406
00:18:06,310 --> 00:18:09,110
Please... tell me the kids didn't see it.

407
00:18:09,110 --> 00:18:11,080
Oh,no,don't worry.I caught it,I caught it...

408
00:18:11,210 --> 00:18:13,910
right before you took off your bra.

409
00:18:16,010 --> 00:18:17,150
I have to go.

410
00:18:17,150 --> 00:18:18,450
Oh,norma. It's okay.

411
00:18:18,610 --> 00:18:21,040
We just thought you needed to know what happened.

412
00:18:21,170 --> 00:18:22,450
Seriously,we're cool with it

413
00:18:22,570 --> 00:18:24,080
so long as you keep it away from the kids

414
00:18:24,230 --> 00:18:26,880
I told leonard this was gonna happen!

415
00:18:26,970 --> 00:18:30,740
Jimmy,P.J.,Close the door!
Are we all buckled up?!

416
00:18:32,220 --> 00:18:33,950
Norma,wait!

417
00:18:34,070 --> 00:18:35,990
We're still on for next week!

418
00:18:36,130 --> 00:18:39,220
Norma! The water park!

419
00:18:39,350 --> 00:18:41,150
Right?

420
00:18:50,340 --> 00:18:52,480
Mom!

421
00:18:57,340 --> 00:18:59,220
Mom?

422
00:19:00,070 --> 00:19:01,810
Mom,are you up?

423
00:19:02,340 --> 00:19:03,250
Mom--

424
00:19:05,470 --> 00:19:07,480
oh,my god.

425
00:19:07,850 --> 00:19:10,850
Oh. Julie! I thought you were going 
straight to school.

426
00:19:10,990 --> 00:19:12,480
I-I needed money for lunch.

427
00:19:12,620 --> 00:19:14,790
There's a $20 in my pants...
if you can find 'em.

428
00:19:14,920 --> 00:19:17,140
Oh,uh,julie,uh...

429
00:19:17,430 --> 00:19:19,370
oh,julie,uh...honey.

430
00:19:24,150 --> 00:19:26,990
Okay,there is a good explanation 
for what happened.

431
00:19:27,150 --> 00:19:28,270
I doubt that.

432
00:19:28,400 --> 00:19:30,930
You probably don't know that your father and edie

433
00:19:31,050 --> 00:19:32,640
broke up last night.

434
00:19:32,780 --> 00:19:35,230
You slept with him the same night he 
broke up with her.

435
00:19:35,380 --> 00:19:38,290
Well,I said it was a good explanation,
not a great one.

436
00:19:38,590 --> 00:19:40,450
oh,julie.

437
00:19:40,580 --> 00:19:42,990
- Hey,pumpkin. 
- Don't even

438
00:19:43,800 --> 00:19:47,290
oh,now I feel really awful.

439
00:19:47,460 --> 00:19:48,800
Me too.

440
00:19:48,940 --> 00:19:51,450
We should not have done what we did.

441
00:19:51,600 --> 00:19:53,860
I know,I know.

442
00:19:57,000 --> 00:19:58,280
But I gotta tell you,

443
00:19:58,410 --> 00:20:00,550
last night was the best sex ever.

444
00:20:00,590 --> 00:20:02,990
Wasn't it,though?You were fantastic.

445
00:20:03,130 --> 00:20:06,430
Hey,I was just trying to keep up with you.

446
00:20:06,890 --> 00:20:09,410
Why do you think we got so good all of a sudden?

447
00:20:09,550 --> 00:20:13,130
Because we've been angry at each other 
for so long,

448
00:20:13,290 --> 00:20:16,170
and we finally found a way to channel it.

449
00:20:16,380 --> 00:20:18,710
Maybe.

450
00:20:19,060 --> 00:20:20,280
So what happens next?

451
00:20:20,410 --> 00:20:22,010
Well,I'm gonna take a shower.

452
00:20:22,180 --> 00:20:24,040
No,I-I mean with us.

453
00:20:24,180 --> 00:20:26,380
Us? What do you mean?There's no us.

454
00:20:26,430 --> 00:20:28,380
You can't tell me you can just walk away

455
00:20:28,530 --> 00:20:30,920
from this chemistry we got goin'.

456
00:20:31,050 --> 00:20:33,760
I mean,what happened last night was...

457
00:20:33,910 --> 00:20:35,220
whew. Explosive.

458
00:20:35,360 --> 00:20:37,390
Karl,last night was two old friends

459
00:20:37,530 --> 00:20:39,520
helping each other through a rough patch. 
That's it.

460
00:20:39,650 --> 00:20:40,240
Susie Q...

461
00:20:40,370 --> 00:20:43,360
karl,I want to move on.I don't want to go backwards.

462
00:20:43,480 --> 00:20:45,160
I'm sorry

463
00:20:46,080 --> 00:20:47,480
But thanks for the explosion

464
00:20:47,590 --> 00:20:49,670
I really needed it.

465
00:20:56,060 --> 00:20:58,550
After 48 hours of crash dieting,

466
00:20:58,680 --> 00:21:02,630
gabrielle prepared to savor the fruit of her labor.

467
00:21:02,780 --> 00:21:06,420
But she was dismayed to discover that she herself

468
00:21:06,560 --> 00:21:10,500
had ripened considerably.

469
00:21:11,110 --> 00:21:12,540
ohh!

470
00:21:17,240 --> 00:21:18,220
ralph!

471
00:21:19,130 --> 00:21:22,480
I need help getting dressed.Get in here!

472
00:21:24,880 --> 00:21:26,110
Now!

473
00:21:29,350 --> 00:21:30,640
I have to fit in this,so for god's sakes,

474
00:21:30,770 --> 00:21:32,220
put some muscle into it.

475
00:21:33,560 --> 00:21:35,200
I'm trying.

476
00:21:35,340 --> 00:21:36,400
It won't zip.

477
00:21:36,410 --> 00:21:38,930
Well,try harder.

478
00:21:39,420 --> 00:21:40,650
Ohh! Ow. My hands hurt.

479
00:21:40,900 --> 00:21:42,970
I'm sorry,ms. Solis,but ican't get you into this dress.

480
00:21:43,110 --> 00:21:44,960
It's just too small.

481
00:21:45,260 --> 00:21:46,040
Get me into this dress,

482
00:21:46,180 --> 00:21:49,420
and I will pay you $10 more a week.

483
00:21:50,850 --> 00:21:54,510
I think I got it. Hold on.Hold still. Here we go.

484
00:21:54,860 --> 00:21:56,160
One...

485
00:21:57,220 --> 00:21:57,930
two...

486
00:21:58,240 --> 00:21:59,800
three. There.

487
00:22:00,090 --> 00:22:02,370
Ohh! Thank god.

488
00:22:14,850 --> 00:22:17,310
we brought you some ice cream.

489
00:22:18,060 --> 00:22:20,970
I know how long it's been since you had any.

490
00:22:24,540 --> 00:22:27,030
We'll have that in a minute,sweetheart.

491
00:22:29,080 --> 00:22:32,580
First,I want youto talk to me

492
00:22:32,730 --> 00:22:34,630
about what happened...

493
00:22:34,770 --> 00:22:36,240
about melanie.

494
00:22:36,340 --> 00:22:37,830
I don't want to talk about her.

495
00:22:37,960 --> 00:22:41,310
You know it breaks my heart to keep you 
down here like this.

496
00:22:41,460 --> 00:22:44,870
But I can't let you out until I am positive

497
00:22:45,000 --> 00:22:47,750
that you will never hurt anyone else again.

498
00:22:47,900 --> 00:22:49,530
And the first step

499
00:22:49,730 --> 00:22:52,510
is for you to show me that you understand

500
00:22:52,630 --> 00:22:55,090
that what you did was wrong.

501
00:22:55,240 --> 00:22:58,040
She was a bad person.

502
00:22:59,420 --> 00:23:01,410
She deserved it.

503
00:23:02,550 --> 00:23:06,020
No one deserves to die like that,caleb.

504
00:23:07,060 --> 00:23:09,630
Don't you agree?

505
00:23:18,960 --> 00:23:21,000
Very well.

506
00:23:23,180 --> 00:23:26,310
If that's how it's going to be...

507
00:23:28,260 --> 00:23:31,180
this is how it's going to be.

508
00:24:03,280 --> 00:24:04,790
I can't believe we're doing this.

509
00:24:04,930 --> 00:24:06,940
If leonard and norma want to cut ties with us,

510
00:24:07,070 --> 00:24:08,510
who are we to stop them?

511
00:24:08,660 --> 00:24:10,450
They need to know we don't judge them

512
00:24:10,590 --> 00:24:13,810
for what they do in the privacy of 
their own home.

513
00:24:13,980 --> 00:24:15,970
And,well,it's not unheard of to tape yourself

514
00:24:16,110 --> 00:24:17,180
while you're having sex.

515
00:24:17,180 --> 00:24:18,190
Well,obviously,there were so embarrassed,

516
00:24:18,340 --> 00:24:19,460
they don't want anythingt o do with us.

517
00:24:19,600 --> 00:24:21,770
Maybe we need to respect that.

518
00:24:21,920 --> 00:24:25,400
I need these play dates

519
00:24:26,320 --> 00:24:28,300
tom,we need these play dates

520
00:24:28,440 --> 00:24:31,990
Fine. Fine.But you do all the talking.

521
00:24:32,130 --> 00:24:33,340
Okay.

522
00:24:34,870 --> 00:24:35,970
- Norma... 
- Aah!

523
00:24:36,120 --> 00:24:37,840
Wait!

524
00:24:38,390 --> 00:24:40,220
- Let's go. 
- No!

525
00:24:40,490 --> 00:24:44,050
Hey,scavos.What are you guys doing here?

526
00:24:44,180 --> 00:24:48,390
Hi. Sorry for just showing up unannounced,
but,um...

527
00:24:48,540 --> 00:24:49,570
could we talk to you for a minute?

528
00:24:49,730 --> 00:24:51,560
Sure,come on in.

529
00:24:51,660 --> 00:24:53,690
so,um,

530
00:24:53,790 --> 00:24:55,920
we've been trying to contact you,

531
00:24:56,050 --> 00:24:58,360
but you haven't been returning any of 
our messages.

532
00:24:58,500 --> 00:25:00,310
And we really hope it isn't because of the 
porno video.

533
00:25:00,430 --> 00:25:02,780
Home--home movies.

534
00:25:02,940 --> 00:25:05,670
The fact is,we really don't care,

535
00:25:05,800 --> 00:25:09,060
and it's certainly no reason to keep our boys apart.

536
00:25:09,620 --> 00:25:11,530
We just don't know how they found it.

537
00:25:11,670 --> 00:25:13,620
But you know boys--they get into everything,

538
00:25:13,620 --> 00:25:15,370
but seriously,it's not a big deal.

539
00:25:15,530 --> 00:25:17,440
I mean,just as long as you make sure 
it never happens again.

540
00:25:17,590 --> 00:25:20,200
It's the new millennium.We're--we're hip.

541
00:25:20,300 --> 00:25:22,970
You know,what we're saying is,we get it.

542
00:25:23,090 --> 00:25:27,090
You're just having fun.It's nothing to 
be ashamed of.

543
00:25:28,510 --> 00:25:30,070
I'm just so relieved this all worked out.

544
00:25:30,210 --> 00:25:31,480
At one point we actually talked

545
00:25:31,480 --> 00:25:33,660
about selling the house and moving.

546
00:25:33,810 --> 00:25:36,600
Oh,no!

547
00:25:37,040 --> 00:25:39,670
thank you for being so open-minded.

548
00:25:39,810 --> 00:25:42,900
Please,we're all adults.It'S...

549
00:25:44,040 --> 00:25:45,720
I gotta tell you,the most embrarrassing 
part of that video

550
00:25:45,860 --> 00:25:47,000
is how poorly it was shot.

551
00:25:47,140 --> 00:25:50,160
The production valuesare ca-ca.

552
00:25:51,180 --> 00:25:55,160
Well,from a lay perspective,
it looked very professional.

553
00:25:55,450 --> 00:25:58,730
What you saw was an example of 
my earlier work.

554
00:25:58,920 --> 00:26:02,000
Since then I've become much more 
adept at... production.

555
00:26:02,140 --> 00:26:03,070
Ah.

556
00:26:03,470 --> 00:26:04,940
You know,editing and lighting.

557
00:26:04,940 --> 00:26:10,060
Leonard has always dreamed of directing movies.

558
00:26:10,210 --> 00:26:11,450
Ironic,isn't it?I finally get my wish

559
00:26:11,600 --> 00:26:14,480
and no one ever gets to see my work.

560
00:26:15,520 --> 00:26:17,940
That is a damn shame.

561
00:26:19,240 --> 00:26:24,030
Norma,what do you think?
Should we show them the room?

562
00:26:24,490 --> 00:26:27,320
Let's show 'em the room.Huh?

563
00:26:30,940 --> 00:26:33,140
Check out this baby.3-chip high-def,

564
00:26:33,280 --> 00:26:36,570
1280x720 lines of resolution,
bounced lighting,

565
00:26:36,710 --> 00:26:39,540
and dark sheets so you don't get 
a kick off the pillows.

566
00:26:39,670 --> 00:26:42,340
Took me a while to learn that little trick,huh?

567
00:26:42,490 --> 00:26:44,440
These walls are completely soundproof.

568
00:26:44,560 --> 00:26:46,330
You could scream your lungs out in here,

569
00:26:46,480 --> 00:26:50,000
and nobody'd hear you.- It's true.

570
00:26:50,490 --> 00:26:55,240
so... anytime you wanna set up a shoot,
just let me know.

571
00:26:55,390 --> 00:26:57,160
You guys would love it.

572
00:26:57,310 --> 00:26:59,680
Once you get in front of that camera,

573
00:26:59,840 --> 00:27:03,070
you feel like a star.

574
00:27:05,200 --> 00:27:05,810
good night.

575
00:27:05,880 --> 00:27:08,020
Night.Night

576
00:27:08,200 --> 00:27:09,450
I'm thinking no more play dates.

577
00:27:09,450 --> 00:27:11,600
Not a one.

578
00:27:16,440 --> 00:27:19,120
Hey. We'd better hurry.
The movie starts in 20 minutes.

579
00:27:19,310 --> 00:27:20,570
There's been a slight change of plans.

580
00:27:20,710 --> 00:27:22,110
My mother had a couple of friends

581
00:27:22,260 --> 00:27:23,060
who really wanted to meet you,

582
00:27:23,210 --> 00:27:26,190
and I thought,"what the heck?It could be fun." Do you mind?

583
00:27:26,360 --> 00:27:29,390
Uh,no,I-I guess not.

584
00:27:29,570 --> 00:27:31,730
Hey,everybody,this is bree.

585
00:27:39,780 --> 00:27:42,030
- and this is my uncle sid. 
- Hi.

586
00:27:42,200 --> 00:27:43,950
- My aunt rosalie.
- hello

587
00:27:44,120 --> 00:27:47,070
Oh,and this is stan grazi,who does my mom's taxes.

588
00:27:47,260 --> 00:27:48,860
She's a knockout,george.

589
00:27:49,000 --> 00:27:51,960
Guess I owe you an apology.

590
00:27:52,110 --> 00:27:53,610
Since I was single all these years,

591
00:27:53,760 --> 00:27:55,900
stan kept telling my mom I was gay.

592
00:27:56,000 --> 00:27:57,670
I'm still gonna need some proof.

593
00:27:57,790 --> 00:27:58,600
But I guess I'll be getting that

594
00:27:58,740 --> 00:28:00,630
in about nine months,hey,bree?

595
00:28:00,780 --> 00:28:02,670
What happens in nine months?

596
00:28:02,670 --> 00:28:03,690
That's just stan's little joke

597
00:28:03,830 --> 00:28:05,430
about when we're gonna start our own family.

598
00:28:05,570 --> 00:28:06,490
Now just so you know,stan,

599
00:28:06,640 --> 00:28:09,910
it's gonna be a while before we even 
think about kids.

600
00:28:10,010 --> 00:28:12,000
I want bree all to myself for a while.

601
00:28:12,130 --> 00:28:14,190
Well,don't wanna wait too long.

602
00:28:14,330 --> 00:28:16,850
After 40,the eggs don't get any fresher.

603
00:28:17,000 --> 00:28:19,730
Am I right,bree?

604
00:28:21,880 --> 00:28:26,030
if you'll excuse me,I,uh,I have to go.

605
00:28:29,550 --> 00:28:31,420
Bree,bree,where are you going?

606
00:28:31,570 --> 00:28:33,530
I am taking my champagne and my aging eggs,

607
00:28:33,670 --> 00:28:34,450
and I'm going home.

608
00:28:34,450 --> 00:28:36,110
What's wrong?

609
00:28:36,820 --> 00:28:38,560
george,I'm starting to think that

610
00:28:38,700 --> 00:28:41,170
we made a mistake rushing into this engagement

611
00:28:41,210 --> 00:28:42,830
- what? 
- And I'm not the only one who thinks that.

612
00:28:42,970 --> 00:28:44,510
Other people have said the same thing

613
00:28:44,510 --> 00:28:46,120
What others? Andrew?

614
00:28:46,210 --> 00:28:49,560
No. Dr. Goldfine,my therapist.

615
00:28:49,710 --> 00:28:51,270
Your therapist?He doesn't know me.

616
00:28:51,420 --> 00:28:54,470
Well,he knows me,and certainly better than you do.

617
00:28:54,610 --> 00:28:55,560
How can you say that?

618
00:28:55,710 --> 00:28:57,330
Well,for starters,he knows the last thing

619
00:28:57,490 --> 00:28:59,700
I'd ever want to do is have more children.

620
00:28:59,840 --> 00:29:02,720
Really? Well,I didn't know.

621
00:29:02,840 --> 00:29:04,200
But you should know that.

622
00:29:04,340 --> 00:29:05,890
That's the kind of thing that people who are engaged

623
00:29:06,030 --> 00:29:08,960
are supposed to know about each other.

624
00:29:09,430 --> 00:29:12,030
Well,it doesn't matter.I don't need children.

625
00:29:12,340 --> 00:29:13,760
It's not just that,george.

626
00:29:13,930 --> 00:29:17,250
Dr. Goldfine has other concerns about 
us being together,

627
00:29:17,390 --> 00:29:19,790
and I'm starting to think he's right.

628
00:29:19,990 --> 00:29:21,040
Look...

629
00:29:22,830 --> 00:29:25,290
I'll agree with dr. Goldfine on one thing.

630
00:29:25,430 --> 00:29:27,990
We should slow things down.

631
00:29:28,120 --> 00:29:28,860
Really?

632
00:29:29,030 --> 00:29:30,940
Yes. Just because two people are engaged

633
00:29:31,080 --> 00:29:34,940
doesn't mean they have to get married 
anytime soon.

634
00:29:37,720 --> 00:29:40,000
I'll talk to dr. Goldfine about it tomorrow.

635
00:29:40,140 --> 00:29:42,610
Take whatever time you need.

636
00:29:57,790 --> 00:30:01,060
how many times am I gonna have to 
ask you to fix this step?

637
00:30:01,400 --> 00:30:03,510
Matthew,are you going to answer me?

638
00:30:03,650 --> 00:30:06,640
Did you leave the door open?

639
00:30:32,400 --> 00:30:33,370
How'd you do?

640
00:30:33,510 --> 00:30:34,410
Not good.

641
00:30:34,560 --> 00:30:36,850
People are gonna start coming home 
from work soon.

642
00:30:36,990 --> 00:30:41,230
Okay. We can't panic.Caleb is scared.

643
00:30:41,370 --> 00:30:44,960
He doesn't know the area,
so he's got to be close by.

644
00:30:45,110 --> 00:30:48,210
Which yards haven't you checked yet?

645
00:30:57,180 --> 00:31:00,540
Bree,I desperately need your help.

646
00:31:00,680 --> 00:31:02,480
Oh,dear. What's wrong?

647
00:31:02,650 --> 00:31:06,140
How do you get your hydrangeas to 
look so stunning?

648
00:31:06,320 --> 00:31:08,790
I'm systematically slaughtering my own garden.

649
00:31:08,930 --> 00:31:10,330
Do you really want to know my secret?

650
00:31:10,420 --> 00:31:11,960
Oh,yes.

651
00:31:12,090 --> 00:31:14,070
Horse manure.I have it delivered.

652
00:31:14,230 --> 00:31:18,140
Susan makes fun of me,
but the proof is in the pudding.

653
00:31:32,780 --> 00:31:34,490
Hello.

654
00:31:34,910 --> 00:31:36,310
Hey.

655
00:31:39,360 --> 00:31:41,190
Looking for something?

656
00:31:42,320 --> 00:31:46,560
Ahem. Uh... yeah.Actually,
I'm looking for you.

657
00:31:46,780 --> 00:31:48,350
Me?

658
00:31:49,230 --> 00:31:51,160
You're looking for me?

659
00:31:51,320 --> 00:31:53,020
Yeah. I've been thinking about you,

660
00:31:53,170 --> 00:31:55,300
and that time we met,
I thought you were really cool.

661
00:31:55,670 --> 00:31:58,830
So you came to ask me out?

662
00:32:05,860 --> 00:32:08,110
'Cause I'll say yes.

663
00:32:12,960 --> 00:32:14,700
Thank you.

664
00:32:20,650 --> 00:32:22,200
Anything?

665
00:32:24,860 --> 00:32:26,590
well,that was a waste of time.

666
00:32:26,730 --> 00:32:28,860
Pretty much.

667
00:32:31,800 --> 00:32:33,980
did you hear the big news?

668
00:32:34,200 --> 00:32:35,460
Uh,the big news?

669
00:32:35,590 --> 00:32:37,770
Karl and I are back together

670
00:32:37,920 --> 00:32:38,870
What?

671
00:32:39,070 --> 00:32:41,610
And I know that he stayed at 
your place last night,

672
00:32:41,760 --> 00:32:44,210
which leads me to why I'm here.

673
00:32:44,430 --> 00:32:45,620
There's some stuff that I have to say,

674
00:32:45,750 --> 00:32:47,400
and it's not going to be pleasant.

675
00:32:47,530 --> 00:32:48,820
Edie,uh...

676
00:32:48,960 --> 00:32:54,460
whatever it was that you said to him 
really helped.

677
00:32:54,690 --> 00:32:57,990
He showed up with flowers and 
he apologized for everything

678
00:32:58,120 --> 00:33:00,210
So...

679
00:33:02,520 --> 00:33:04,670
thank you.

680
00:33:05,290 --> 00:33:06,600
I'm sorry,what?

681
00:33:06,750 --> 00:33:07,650
Well,I'm not gonna say it again.

682
00:33:07,800 --> 00:33:09,460
It hurt my teeth the first time.

683
00:33:09,600 --> 00:33:13,060
No,edie. This is so unexpected 
on so many levels.

684
00:33:13,210 --> 00:33:14,460
I don't know what to say

685
00:33:14,600 --> 00:33:15,860
Then say nothing

686
00:33:16,010 --> 00:33:18,900
Oh,and,uh,here...

687
00:33:19,050 --> 00:33:21,280
is the photo of you I found in our bed.

688
00:33:21,420 --> 00:33:23,760
I know he told you about it.

689
00:33:24,220 --> 00:33:26,460
Why are you giving itto me?

690
00:33:27,410 --> 00:33:31,030
Look,I appreciate whatever 
it was that you did last night,

691
00:33:31,170 --> 00:33:34,100
but it's still important for you to 
understand that...

692
00:33:34,240 --> 00:33:36,290
I won.

693
00:33:37,130 --> 00:33:38,340
You won?

694
00:33:38,470 --> 00:33:40,890
Yeah. Whatever little hold you had on karl

695
00:33:41,020 --> 00:33:42,380
is officially over.

696
00:33:42,530 --> 00:33:44,350
So you can stop feeling all smug

697
00:33:44,570 --> 00:33:47,820
and superior that he kept that... thing.

698
00:33:47,980 --> 00:33:50,100
Believe me,I don't feel superior.

699
00:33:50,240 --> 00:33:51,680
Good,'cause you shouldn'T.

700
00:33:51,830 --> 00:33:55,860
He made his choice,and it's not you.

701
00:33:55,990 --> 00:34:00,340
You're right.He made his choice.

702
00:34:11,740 --> 00:34:13,950
no,bree,it's still too easyto breathe.

703
00:34:14,090 --> 00:34:15,040
You've gotta make it tighter.

704
00:34:15,140 --> 00:34:16,220
Gaby,if I make it any tighter,

705
00:34:16,370 --> 00:34:17,830
you won't be able to sit down.

706
00:34:17,950 --> 00:34:18,660
I don't care.

707
00:34:18,800 --> 00:34:21,370
I can't have these girls thinking I'm pregnant.

708
00:34:21,460 --> 00:34:24,020
Gosh,do you actually think they're
gonna make fun of you?

709
00:34:24,170 --> 00:34:26,590
Trust me. They're merciless.

710
00:34:27,720 --> 00:34:31,310
But why? I mean,surely they have friends 
who have children.

711
00:34:31,460 --> 00:34:33,320
When I decided to marry carlos,

712
00:34:33,470 --> 00:34:35,990
I told these girls I would spend the rest of my days

713
00:34:36,140 --> 00:34:38,870
being rich and in love and childless,

714
00:34:39,030 --> 00:34:40,080
and they laughed at me,

715
00:34:40,240 --> 00:34:42,200
and they said I would just end up being another

716
00:34:42,330 --> 00:34:46,450
fat hausfrau livinga life that I didn't plan.

717
00:34:47,140 --> 00:34:48,240
I'm not gonna give them the satisfaction

718
00:34:48,400 --> 00:34:49,730
of knowing they were right.

719
00:34:49,790 --> 00:34:51,980
Well,maybe they'll just be happy for you.

720
00:34:52,100 --> 00:34:55,900
Bree,my friends are models.
They're never happy for anyone.

721
00:34:56,410 --> 00:34:58,690
Do you ever thinkyou might like it?

722
00:34:58,850 --> 00:34:59,720
What?

723
00:34:59,870 --> 00:35:02,020
Motherhood.

724
00:35:02,060 --> 00:35:03,360
- No. 
- Oh,come on

725
00:35:03,420 --> 00:35:05,460
You don't think you're gonna love your own baby?

726
00:35:05,620 --> 00:35:07,990
Well,I'm not saying I'm not gonna grow 
attached to the little bugger

727
00:35:08,120 --> 00:35:10,790
I just don't have the motherhood gene.

728
00:35:10,940 --> 00:35:12,990
I wish I did,but I don'T.

729
00:35:14,530 --> 00:35:15,170
what?

730
00:35:15,210 --> 00:35:17,840
Well,I'm just smiling because 
I think a few months from now

731
00:35:17,980 --> 00:35:19,010
you are gonna come to me

732
00:35:19,010 --> 00:35:21,470
and tell me how madly in love you are with your

733
00:35:21,620 --> 00:35:22,490
new little baby,

734
00:35:22,610 --> 00:35:25,650
and I'm gonna have to resist the urge 
to say "I told you so."

735
00:35:25,800 --> 00:35:28,320
Maybe,but I doubt it

736
00:35:28,470 --> 00:35:31,040
There you go. All done.

737
00:35:32,070 --> 00:35:33,700
Ah

738
00:35:33,850 --> 00:35:34,850
How do I look?

739
00:35:35,020 --> 00:35:37,110
Positively glowing.

740
00:35:37,980 --> 00:35:40,200
Bree... aah!

741
00:36:43,110 --> 00:36:45,930
hi! Hello!

742
00:36:47,000 --> 00:36:49,030
oh,my god!

743
00:36:49,200 --> 00:36:51,550
You're pregnant!

744
00:36:56,450 --> 00:36:58,170
bree? It's gaby!

745
00:36:58,320 --> 00:37:00,810
Honey,it's open.Come on in.

746
00:37:05,820 --> 00:37:09,430
Hi. My,uh,friends just left,

747
00:37:09,580 --> 00:37:10,890
and I was hoping you could come over

748
00:37:11,040 --> 00:37:12,710
and cut me out of this thing.

749
00:37:12,820 --> 00:37:14,950
How was your little reunion?

750
00:37:15,100 --> 00:37:18,690
It was,um... weird.

751
00:37:18,840 --> 00:37:20,230
Weird?

752
00:37:20,390 --> 00:37:22,000
Well, allison's mad

753
00:37:22,050 --> 00:37:24,400
because she's losing jobs to 14-year-olds,

754
00:37:24,550 --> 00:37:27,940
holly is on a strict diet of cruciferous 
vegetables,and...

755
00:37:28,070 --> 00:37:31,670
yasmin is undergoing a new 
embryonic facial treatment

756
00:37:31,810 --> 00:37:35,230
that probably causesshort-term memory loss.

757
00:37:35,450 --> 00:37:37,970
You know,I just stood there the whole night

758
00:37:38,280 --> 00:37:41,390
trying to remember why we were ever friends.

759
00:37:42,170 --> 00:37:43,570
And I couldn'T.

760
00:37:43,720 --> 00:37:46,950
You know,honey,people change.

761
00:37:47,090 --> 00:37:49,150
Yeah,but that's the thing.
They haven't changed.

762
00:37:49,290 --> 00:37:51,620
That's who they've always been.

763
00:37:51,890 --> 00:37:56,160
I've changed,and I honestly don't know how.

764
00:37:56,300 --> 00:37:57,700
Well...

765
00:37:57,810 --> 00:38:02,040
maybe susan, lynette and I have had 
a good influence on you.

766
00:38:02,560 --> 00:38:04,870
I doubt that.

767
00:38:06,590 --> 00:38:08,590
Come on.When I finish up here,

768
00:38:08,760 --> 00:38:10,990
I will come over with my sewing kit

769
00:38:11,150 --> 00:38:12,470
and cut you out of that.

770
00:38:12,600 --> 00:38:14,040
All right,but hurry up,

771
00:38:14,160 --> 00:38:17,200
because I've been having to pee 
since hors d'oeuvres.

772
00:38:22,060 --> 00:38:25,060
are you free to go shopping tomorrow?

773
00:38:25,180 --> 00:38:27,020
I figured it's probably time I...

774
00:38:27,120 --> 00:38:29,530
bought some clothes that actually fit.

775
00:38:29,690 --> 00:38:31,700
Well,I know a store that carries maternity clothes

776
00:38:31,840 --> 00:38:33,730
with designer labels.

777
00:38:33,900 --> 00:38:36,760
I like the sound of that.

778
00:38:37,570 --> 00:38:39,120
Thanks.

779
00:39:24,310 --> 00:39:26,570
aah!

780
00:40:13,480 --> 00:40:14,740
thank you.

781
00:40:15,390 --> 00:40:20,570
Yes,cameras are tools designed to capture images.

782
00:40:20,790 --> 00:40:22,220
Wait.

783
00:40:22,580 --> 00:40:24,440
What is it?

784
00:40:25,380 --> 00:40:26,720
Uh,she needs me to get something for her.

785
00:40:26,720 --> 00:40:28,270
I will be right back.

786
00:40:28,420 --> 00:40:33,560
But in truth,they can capture so much more.

787
00:40:33,690 --> 00:40:36,600
They can uncover hidden longing

788
00:40:36,730 --> 00:40:41,000
of men who should no longer care.

789
00:40:42,620 --> 00:40:46,400
They can reveal the extraordinary secrets

790
00:40:46,480 --> 00:40:50,070
of the most ordinary marriages.

791
00:40:52,390 --> 00:40:54,050
Most amazing of all,

792
00:40:54,210 --> 00:41:00,590
cameras can quietly and clearly 
reveal to us our dreams--

793
00:41:00,720 --> 00:41:05,710
dreams we didn't even know we had.

794
00:41:08,600 --> 00:41:09,580
-------------------------- 
www.ydy.com/bbs
Proudly Presents
--------------------------

795
00:41:09,680 --> 00:41:10,580
Desperate Housewives
Season 2 Episode 7

