1
00:00:00,050 --> 00:00:02,070
Previously on "Desperate Housewives"

2
00:00:02,180 --> 00:00:04,870
All this time my father has been right across town

3
00:00:04,990 --> 00:00:06,460
running the feed store?

4
00:00:06,590 --> 00:00:08,360
Susan found her real father

5
00:00:08,560 --> 00:00:10,430
Ed wants to make the final decision

6
00:00:10,660 --> 00:00:12,200
Ed Furarer ,lynette Scoval

7
00:00:12,330 --> 00:00:14,030
lynette met her new boss

8
00:00:14,160 --> 00:00:16,770
I've learned my lesson. Ok, when I get out of here

9
00:00:16,900 --> 00:00:18,230
Everything's gotta be different

10
00:00:18,350 --> 00:00:20,960
Carlos promised to change his old ways

11
00:00:21,090 --> 00:00:23,430
Dr. Goldfine has concerns about us being together

12
00:00:23,540 --> 00:00:25,070
and I'm starting to thinking he's right

13
00:00:25,220 --> 00:00:28,410
While Bree discovered George's true colors

14
00:00:28,550 --> 00:00:29,260
George, I don't want to!

15
00:00:29,340 --> 00:00:31,560
We are engaged! You have to wear it!

16
00:00:31,690 --> 00:00:33,210
I don't think we are any more

17
00:00:35,970 --> 00:00:39,050
Anyone who'd ever been to a party of Bree van de kamp's 

18
00:00:39,150 --> 00:00:41,720
thought of her as the perfect hostes

19
00:00:41,850 --> 00:00:45,150
Because Bree knew how to take care of her guests

20
00:00:46,740 --> 00:00:49,570
Her dinners will always served properly

21
00:00:50,720 --> 00:00:53,680
Her licer always flow freely

22
00:00:54,690 --> 00:00:58,560
And her anicdoses were always enjoyable

23
00:00:59,570 --> 00:01:01,920
But on this night,the perfect hostess

24
00:01:02,050 --> 00:01:04,460
was about to find herself...

25
00:01:05,200 --> 00:01:09,320
Where's that musiccoming from?

26
00:01:10,360 --> 00:01:13,510
in a very imperfect predicament.

27
00:01:13,640 --> 00:01:17,120
Uh,I'm not sure.

28
00:01:18,980 --> 00:01:22,280
Don't give upon us,baby

29
00:01:22,390 --> 00:01:25,600
we're still worth one more try

30
00:01:25,790 --> 00:01:28,660
um,if you'll excuse mefor just one minute.

31
00:01:28,880 --> 00:01:33,790
I know we putour last one by

32
00:01:33,920 --> 00:01:35,940
just for a rainy evening

33
00:01:36,060 --> 00:01:37,360
george!

34
00:01:37,500 --> 00:01:38,650
I have guests.

35
00:01:38,790 --> 00:01:40,970
- What do you thinkyou're doing? 
- We had a tiff.I upset you.

36
00:01:41,090 --> 00:01:42,780
And now I'm just trying to make things right again.

37
00:01:42,880 --> 00:01:44,120
It was not a tiff

38
00:01:44,260 --> 00:01:46,060
We broke up. It's over.

39
00:01:46,190 --> 00:01:49,010
- We can still come through  
- I am not kidding.

40
00:01:49,140 --> 00:01:51,380
If you do not knock it off,I am gonna call the police.

41
00:01:51,380 --> 00:01:52,130
All right,go ahead.

42
00:01:52,250 --> 00:01:54,920
I really lost my head last night

43
00:01:55,020 --> 00:01:56,560
call the police.If they drag me away,

44
00:01:56,690 --> 00:01:57,860
I'm just gonna comeright back here.

45
00:01:57,980 --> 00:01:59,620
I want you to hearthe whole medley

46
00:01:59,760 --> 00:02:01,530
Come on!

47
00:02:05,810 --> 00:02:07,600
Why don't you all take your seats?

48
00:02:07,880 --> 00:02:11,160
dessert is aboutto be served.

49
00:02:27,110 --> 00:02:30,800
I really lost my headlast night

50
00:02:30,940 --> 00:02:32,730
you've got a right

51
00:02:32,880 --> 00:02:33,790
to...

52
00:02:38,500 --> 00:02:42,710
yes,bree knew how to take care of her guests,

53
00:02:42,840 --> 00:02:46,960
especially those who weren't invited.

54
00:02:47,680 --> 00:02:48,710
-------------------------- 
www.ydy.com/bbs
Proudly Presents
--------------------------

55
00:02:48,990 --> 00:02:50,150
Sync: YTET-Starry
-==www.ydy.com/bbs==-

56
00:02:50,560 --> 00:02:51,920
Desperate housewives
Season 2 Episode 9

57
00:02:55,270 --> 00:02:57,220
Good guys wear white hats,

58
00:02:57,330 --> 00:02:59,540
and bad guys wear black.

59
00:02:59,670 --> 00:03:01,550
This is how children distinguish

60
00:03:01,690 --> 00:03:04,860
between good and evil.

61
00:03:05,000 --> 00:03:06,800
But they soon learn that bad guys

62
00:03:06,940 --> 00:03:08,820
don't always look so bad.

63
00:03:08,950 --> 00:03:10,670
In fact,sometimes

64
00:03:10,790 --> 00:03:13,190
they even seem down right friendly.

65
00:03:13,330 --> 00:03:15,110
That is,until you get to know them

66
00:03:15,230 --> 00:03:16,840
a little bit better.

67
00:03:16,980 --> 00:03:18,980
Hey,fancy seeing you here.

68
00:03:19,130 --> 00:03:20,080
I was just out for a little ride.

69
00:03:20,200 --> 00:03:21,530
Don't lie to me,george.

70
00:03:21,660 --> 00:03:24,720
You've been riding up and down this street 
for the last hour.

71
00:03:24,840 --> 00:03:25,800
I don't want to do this,bree,

72
00:03:25,800 --> 00:03:27,210
but you won't return any of my phone calls.

73
00:03:27,320 --> 00:03:31,100
So stalking me is plan "b"?

74
00:03:32,960 --> 00:03:34,260
Bree,I know I messed up.

75
00:03:34,400 --> 00:03:36,760
I know I got some issues to work on,

76
00:03:36,960 --> 00:03:38,270
but I'd be willing to see a therapist

77
00:03:38,370 --> 00:03:39,790
if that's what you want.

78
00:03:39,910 --> 00:03:41,190
I'll do anything,but

79
00:03:41,310 --> 00:03:42,740
how can I show you that I can--

80
00:03:42,900 --> 00:03:45,500
I can change if you don't give me a second chance?

81
00:03:45,750 --> 00:03:46,780
Come on.

82
00:03:46,910 --> 00:03:49,170
You know I'm not a bad person.

83
00:03:49,310 --> 00:03:50,310
I do know that,

84
00:03:50,440 --> 00:03:54,110
but I'm just not sure you're a good one,either.

85
00:04:00,280 --> 00:04:02,780
and we integrated the corporate logo

86
00:04:02,910 --> 00:04:04,220
into the jungle background,

87
00:04:04,350 --> 00:04:06,370
creating not only an ad for the clothing,

88
00:04:06,500 --> 00:04:09,580
but for the company itself.

89
00:04:13,620 --> 00:04:15,140
I don't get it.

90
00:04:15,330 --> 00:04:17,460
What,um,don't you get?

91
00:04:17,580 --> 00:04:20,950
The whole idea just kinda makes my head hurt.

92
00:04:21,110 --> 00:04:21,980
Is it just me?

93
00:04:22,120 --> 00:04:23,320
No,nuh-unh.

94
00:04:23,440 --> 00:04:25,090
You're right. It stinks.

95
00:04:25,330 --> 00:04:27,230
Sorry,guys. Back to the drawing board.

96
00:04:27,350 --> 00:04:29,830
Well,I got tickets to a game.

97
00:04:29,990 --> 00:04:31,000
Nina,you do whatever you have to do

98
00:04:31,110 --> 00:04:32,420
to keep us afloat here.

99
00:04:32,550 --> 00:04:33,920
You got it.

100
00:04:34,040 --> 00:04:36,980
Looks like it's gonna be another late night at the office.

101
00:04:37,100 --> 00:04:38,110
Nice work,everybody.

102
00:04:38,220 --> 00:04:39,270
Thank you.

103
00:04:39,470 --> 00:04:42,430
Could you can the attitude,nina?

104
00:04:42,690 --> 00:04:43,940
I'm sorry. What did you just say?

105
00:04:44,070 --> 00:04:45,050
You're being rude.

106
00:04:45,190 --> 00:04:46,410
And it's totally out of line.

107
00:04:46,540 --> 00:04:48,730
You know how hard we all worked on this.

108
00:04:48,870 --> 00:04:50,580
Yeah,I do.

109
00:04:50,720 --> 00:04:53,040
Nina,I think I speak for everyone here

110
00:04:53,210 --> 00:04:56,420
when I say we are sick and tired of your abuse.

111
00:04:56,550 --> 00:04:59,330
Frankly,you owe us an apology.

112
00:04:59,530 --> 00:05:01,190
Is--is this true?

113
00:05:01,320 --> 00:05:02,750
I mean,I would be mortified

114
00:05:02,950 --> 00:05:06,340
if I thought that I'd hurt any of you.

115
00:05:06,580 --> 00:05:09,790
I mean,If anybody feels like I owe them an apology,

116
00:05:09,980 --> 00:05:14,740
please,speak up.

117
00:05:14,900 --> 00:05:16,830
You? You?

118
00:05:16,980 --> 00:05:18,470
You?

119
00:05:18,900 --> 00:05:19,880
Gee,lynette.

120
00:05:20,000 --> 00:05:22,080
I guess you were mistaken.

121
00:05:22,250 --> 00:05:24,350
All right,let's recap,shall we?

122
00:05:24,480 --> 00:05:30,090
Stinky pitch,workin' late,no apologies.

123
00:05:31,780 --> 00:05:33,090
Guys!

124
00:05:33,270 --> 00:05:34,190
We talked about this.

125
00:05:34,320 --> 00:05:36,500
What happened to standing up for ourselves?

126
00:05:36,620 --> 00:05:37,580
Hot muffins.

127
00:05:37,710 --> 00:05:38,550
Any takers?

128
00:05:38,690 --> 00:05:43,100
No,stu. These people don't deserve muffins.

129
00:05:48,430 --> 00:05:49,670
hello?

130
00:05:49,710 --> 00:05:51,410
hello. My name is mark martinez.

131
00:05:51,430 --> 00:05:53,860
I'm the assistant warden down at fairvew county jail.

132
00:05:54,070 --> 00:05:55,230
Is mrs. Solis available?

133
00:05:55,360 --> 00:05:57,340
Uh,yeah,this is her.

134
00:05:57,450 --> 00:05:59,010
Did somethin' happen with carlos?

135
00:05:59,230 --> 00:06:00,560
At 7:43 this morning,

136
00:06:00,700 --> 00:06:02,490
your husband held two guards at gunpoint

137
00:06:02,610 --> 00:06:04,360
and successfully escaped.

138
00:06:04,510 --> 00:06:05,760
He what?!

139
00:06:05,880 --> 00:06:07,590
I take it you had no prior knowledge

140
00:06:07,700 --> 00:06:08,700
he had planned to do this?

141
00:06:08,880 --> 00:06:10,310
No,of course not.

142
00:06:10,450 --> 00:06:11,610
He's a moron!

143
00:06:11,730 --> 00:06:13,050
We have every reason to believe

144
00:06:13,170 --> 00:06:16,220
your husband may come to find you.

145
00:06:16,370 --> 00:06:18,510
We believe him to be armed...

146
00:06:18,650 --> 00:06:21,060
and very,very horny.

147
00:06:21,230 --> 00:06:22,890
What?

148
00:06:23,340 --> 00:06:24,800
Surprise,baby.

149
00:06:25,850 --> 00:06:27,710
I got paroled early.

150
00:06:28,390 --> 00:06:30,640
It's so good to see you!

151
00:06:30,960 --> 00:06:32,010
What happened?

152
00:06:32,150 --> 00:06:33,030
Well,there's this church group

153
00:06:33,140 --> 00:06:34,630
that helps out catholic prisoners.

154
00:06:34,870 --> 00:06:36,740
And they really,really stepped up for me.

155
00:06:36,870 --> 00:06:37,930
Well,what did they do?

156
00:06:38,060 --> 00:06:41,030
They lobbied the parole board and it worked.

157
00:06:42,630 --> 00:06:44,780
I guess I owe the pope a thank-you note.

158
00:06:44,910 --> 00:06:46,630
Less talking,

159
00:06:46,770 --> 00:06:49,170
more stripping.

160
00:06:57,060 --> 00:06:58,670
prudy's feed store.

161
00:06:58,960 --> 00:07:01,120
Apparently,he owns the place.

162
00:07:01,230 --> 00:07:02,490
How are you gonna do it?

163
00:07:02,610 --> 00:07:04,130
What do you mean?

164
00:07:04,270 --> 00:07:06,860
I mean,how are you gonna tell him you're his daughter?

165
00:07:07,020 --> 00:07:08,700
Oh,I'm not.

166
00:07:08,830 --> 00:07:11,300
Julie,the man abandoned me before I was born.

167
00:07:11,410 --> 00:07:14,750
I don't have a desire to have a relationship with him.

168
00:07:14,870 --> 00:07:16,510
Okay,then I'm really confused

169
00:07:16,640 --> 00:07:18,410
why we're here spying on him.

170
00:07:18,520 --> 00:07:20,810
Well,I just wanna see what he's like

171
00:07:20,980 --> 00:07:23,180
and satisfy my curiosity and

172
00:07:23,290 --> 00:07:25,730
get it out of my system.

173
00:07:32,960 --> 00:07:35,180
Well,here you go.

174
00:07:35,300 --> 00:07:36,250
Now you tell charlie that

175
00:07:36,380 --> 00:07:38,500
addison prudy says drop in some time.

176
00:07:38,620 --> 00:07:40,450
I miss that ugly mug of his around here

177
00:07:40,620 --> 00:07:42,360
I will.

178
00:07:47,540 --> 00:07:49,700
I bet I know what you're here for.

179
00:07:49,840 --> 00:07:50,920
Oh?

180
00:07:51,060 --> 00:07:52,800
You heard about the giveaway.

181
00:07:52,940 --> 00:07:55,010
Well,I got the cowboy hats right here.

182
00:07:55,160 --> 00:07:56,590
Oh,oh,no,that's okay.

183
00:07:56,720 --> 00:07:58,520
You don't have to give me anything,really.

184
00:07:58,640 --> 00:08:00,890
Relax. This is a promotional item.

185
00:08:01,020 --> 00:08:03,400
Didn't cost me a dime.

186
00:08:08,360 --> 00:08:10,280
There you go.

187
00:08:10,680 --> 00:08:13,470
Pretty as a picture.

188
00:08:22,220 --> 00:08:23,290
I have a dad.

189
00:08:23,420 --> 00:08:24,420
He's great!

190
00:08:24,570 --> 00:08:26,510
He gave me a hat.

191
00:08:32,810 --> 00:08:34,800
That biting thing at the end...

192
00:08:34,940 --> 00:08:37,640
Totally blew my mind.

193
00:08:37,790 --> 00:08:40,360
Please tell me you didn't learn that in prison.

194
00:08:40,510 --> 00:08:42,500
Yeah.

195
00:08:43,300 --> 00:08:47,230
Wait. I'm not done with you yet.

196
00:08:47,370 --> 00:08:50,000
Just give me ten minutes,please.

197
00:08:50,130 --> 00:08:51,700
What is wrong with you?

198
00:08:51,820 --> 00:08:54,460
You are totally useless after sex.

199
00:08:54,640 --> 00:08:58,460
I know. I should probably get my thyroid 
checked out.

200
00:09:06,640 --> 00:09:09,540
who's sister mary bernard?

201
00:09:09,810 --> 00:09:11,710
those are private.Give me--

202
00:09:12,370 --> 00:09:13,970
she's this nun,okay?

203
00:09:14,160 --> 00:09:15,690
She visited me in prisona couple times.

204
00:09:15,830 --> 00:09:17,350
She's part of the group that got me early release.

205
00:09:17,500 --> 00:09:19,480
Now can I please have them back?

206
00:09:19,550 --> 00:09:21,290
"When you walk with godevery day,

207
00:09:21,420 --> 00:09:23,590
"you learn that truth is understood in the mind

208
00:09:23,730 --> 00:09:27,060
but faith burns in the heart"?

209
00:09:28,360 --> 00:09:30,540
You don't know what it was like in there.

210
00:09:30,670 --> 00:09:34,650
All right? 20 hours a day,8x10 cell.

211
00:09:34,820 --> 00:09:37,360
Just you and your mind.

212
00:09:38,070 --> 00:09:40,520
So pretty much just you.

213
00:09:42,200 --> 00:09:44,750
It forces you to rexamine everything.

214
00:09:44,890 --> 00:09:47,110
I was a very bad person for a very long time,

215
00:09:47,290 --> 00:09:49,090
but now all that is gonna change

216
00:09:49,220 --> 00:09:51,590
because I'm on a new path.

217
00:09:53,360 --> 00:09:54,550
A new path?

218
00:09:54,550 --> 00:09:57,380
I am going to livea virtuous life.

219
00:09:57,480 --> 00:09:59,270
I wanna do right by you,

220
00:09:59,390 --> 00:10:01,210
by my mama

221
00:10:01,340 --> 00:10:03,650
and by my god.

222
00:10:06,690 --> 00:10:09,760
What the hell did they do to you in that prison?

223
00:10:10,010 --> 00:10:11,880
All right,this is my last hand,

224
00:10:12,030 --> 00:10:13,180
and then I gotta go.

225
00:10:13,320 --> 00:10:14,270
Already?

226
00:10:14,310 --> 00:10:16,320
I left a proposalon my desk at work.

227
00:10:16,440 --> 00:10:18,090
I have to go over it tonight,or

228
00:10:18,220 --> 00:10:19,820
you-know-who is gonna have my head.

229
00:10:19,960 --> 00:10:21,990
Nina.

230
00:10:22,420 --> 00:10:23,820
You know,this gainful employment thing

231
00:10:23,950 --> 00:10:26,030
is really starting to cut into our social life.

232
00:10:26,140 --> 00:10:28,480
Well,if one of you would just gree to raise my kids,

233
00:10:28,590 --> 00:10:31,210
I wouldn't need a job.Any takers?

234
00:10:31,340 --> 00:10:34,000
- Ha ha. 
- No,I didn't think so.

235
00:10:34,130 --> 00:10:35,610
Ante up.

236
00:10:36,140 --> 00:10:37,900
Speaking of child abandonment,

237
00:10:38,020 --> 00:10:39,050
when are you gonna tell your father

238
00:10:39,180 --> 00:10:41,990
that he has a bouncing,middle-aged baby girl?

239
00:10:42,130 --> 00:10:44,220
Soon. I don't wanna ambush him.

240
00:10:44,350 --> 00:10:45,560
I'm gonna ease into it.

241
00:10:45,680 --> 00:10:48,470
How do you ease into,"hi.I'm your illegitimate daughter"?

242
00:10:48,530 --> 00:10:50,230
Well,actually,there's a "help wanted" sign

243
00:10:50,360 --> 00:10:52,570
in the window,so I was thinking about 
getting a job there.

244
00:10:52,700 --> 00:10:54,280
And you know,he would get to know me,

245
00:10:54,470 --> 00:10:57,690
and I'm sure he would like me and 
I would like him,and...

246
00:10:57,800 --> 00:10:59,390
then one day,he'd say,

247
00:10:59,520 --> 00:11:01,020
"you're like the daughterI never had,"

248
00:11:01,070 --> 00:11:06,010
and I'd say,"well,actually,now that you mention it..."

249
00:11:09,130 --> 00:11:11,430
okay,I'll go first.

250
00:11:11,560 --> 00:11:14,100
That is the most idiotic plan I've ever heard of.

251
00:11:14,320 --> 00:11:15,380
Why?

252
00:11:15,530 --> 00:11:18,930
Because it all hinges on him responding 
to your personality.

253
00:11:19,050 --> 00:11:22,130
And let's face it,you are an acquired taste.

254
00:11:22,260 --> 00:11:25,720
Edie,I am sure susan's father will like her just fine.

255
00:11:25,720 --> 00:11:26,450
Thank you.

256
00:11:26,570 --> 00:11:28,960
I just hope you don't expecttoo much from this relationship.

257
00:11:29,090 --> 00:11:30,840
I mean,aside from D.N.A.,You might find

258
00:11:30,970 --> 00:11:32,440
that you don't have that much in common.

259
00:11:32,580 --> 00:11:36,530
I know,but I gotta find outif there's something there.

260
00:11:36,670 --> 00:11:38,410
I've always wanted a dad.

261
00:11:38,560 --> 00:11:40,750
I mean,I know not having oneaffected me.

262
00:11:40,930 --> 00:11:42,140
Well,of course it did.

263
00:11:42,440 --> 00:11:45,110
Everyone needsa strong male role model.

264
00:11:45,250 --> 00:11:46,310
No,they don'T.

265
00:11:46,450 --> 00:11:50,050
I grew up without a father,and it didn't affect me one bit.

266
00:11:50,350 --> 00:11:54,110
Edie,how old were you when you lost your virginity?

267
00:11:54,820 --> 00:11:57,080
Point well taken.

268
00:12:11,690 --> 00:12:13,000
Hey.

269
00:12:13,140 --> 00:12:16,970
Look what I foundin ed's fridge.

270
00:12:40,950 --> 00:12:43,320
hey,stu.

271
00:12:44,740 --> 00:12:48,450
and nina!

272
00:12:48,590 --> 00:12:51,210
Hey,lynette,can I see you for a sec?

273
00:12:51,360 --> 00:12:53,130
Sure.

274
00:12:55,020 --> 00:12:57,100
Tsk,tsk,tsk.

275
00:12:57,210 --> 00:12:58,630
Having sex with the support staff--

276
00:12:58,810 --> 00:12:59,730
that's a big no-no.

277
00:12:59,860 --> 00:13:03,160
Ed's been known to fire peoplefor that sort of thing.

278
00:13:03,750 --> 00:13:04,620
lynette,

279
00:13:04,740 --> 00:13:08,220
I know that we've had our little differences.

280
00:13:08,350 --> 00:13:10,440
But at the core,

281
00:13:10,550 --> 00:13:13,940
I believe that we're both good people,

282
00:13:14,050 --> 00:13:17,990
both smart women who are just trying to make it

283
00:13:18,100 --> 00:13:21,160
in this vicious male-dominated jungle--

284
00:13:21,300 --> 00:13:22,570
okay,what do you want?

285
00:13:22,710 --> 00:13:24,240
Do you want a raise?

286
00:13:24,360 --> 00:13:25,980
You want a better office?

287
00:13:26,110 --> 00:13:28,200
My demands are simple.

288
00:13:28,350 --> 00:13:31,900
I want you to be nicer.

289
00:13:32,070 --> 00:13:33,220
What?

290
00:13:33,340 --> 00:13:34,460
No more belittling,

291
00:13:34,610 --> 00:13:35,640
berating,

292
00:13:35,760 --> 00:13:37,760
rude sarcasm.

293
00:13:37,890 --> 00:13:40,070
And in exchange I get your silence?

294
00:13:40,180 --> 00:13:42,540
Yeah. Pretty sweet deal,don't you think?

295
00:13:42,690 --> 00:13:45,270
Um...

296
00:13:45,630 --> 00:13:48,100
I'll see what I can do.

297
00:13:48,390 --> 00:13:50,800
Great.Okay.

298
00:13:50,940 --> 00:13:53,660
And I'm gonna take your parking space.

299
00:13:54,690 --> 00:13:56,840
I kid the nina.

300
00:14:05,210 --> 00:14:06,500
you're up early.

301
00:14:06,630 --> 00:14:08,120
I'm going to mass.

302
00:14:08,220 --> 00:14:10,340
- Huh? - Yeah.

303
00:14:10,500 --> 00:14:12,380
But it's not even sunday.

304
00:14:12,530 --> 00:14:14,530
They have mass every day of the week.

305
00:14:14,690 --> 00:14:18,000
Really? When did they start doing that?

306
00:14:18,920 --> 00:14:20,280
that's sister mary bernard.

307
00:14:20,410 --> 00:14:23,000
Did you see where I put my bible?

308
00:14:47,440 --> 00:14:49,760
- What?- I saw your nun.

309
00:14:49,960 --> 00:14:51,560
So? So she's hot.

310
00:14:51,680 --> 00:14:54,750
She's a hot nun.

311
00:14:55,650 --> 00:14:57,580
you cann'tseriously be jealous.

312
00:14:57,700 --> 00:15:00,420
You mean to tell me that this 
miraculous conversion of yours

313
00:15:00,420 --> 00:15:01,950
has nothing to do with the fact

314
00:15:02,080 --> 00:15:05,970
that the woman standing outside is a knockout?

315
00:15:07,550 --> 00:15:10,530
That's what I'm telling you.

316
00:15:29,140 --> 00:15:31,540
Um,who are you hereto see?

317
00:15:31,690 --> 00:15:34,130
I'm lynette scavo

318
00:15:34,290 --> 00:15:35,800
I work here

319
00:15:35,940 --> 00:15:36,660
Who are you?

320
00:15:36,800 --> 00:15:38,740
Pat. It's my first day.

321
00:15:38,850 --> 00:15:41,170
Oh. Well,welcome.

322
00:15:41,400 --> 00:15:42,790
What happened to stu?

323
00:15:43,430 --> 00:15:45,710
You fired stu?

324
00:15:45,910 --> 00:15:47,770
Oh,lynette,hey.Come on in.

325
00:15:47,930 --> 00:15:51,050
I can't believe you would sink so low.

326
00:15:51,190 --> 00:15:52,250
I'm going to ed.

327
00:15:52,380 --> 00:15:58,020
Ed knows. This is stu's employee evaluation file right here.

328
00:15:58,150 --> 00:16:00,330
This thing is full of black marks.

329
00:16:00,460 --> 00:16:03,280
Come on,nina. We both know why you got rid of him.

330
00:16:03,390 --> 00:16:05,870
Well,good luck proving it.

331
00:16:06,040 --> 00:16:09,730
Oh,and on a completely unrelated topic,

332
00:16:09,830 --> 00:16:11,570
there's going to be another round of firings

333
00:16:11,710 --> 00:16:13,050
coming down the pike.

334
00:16:13,170 --> 00:16:15,280
Ed's been after me to trim the fat.

335
00:16:15,450 --> 00:16:17,920
- You threatening me? 
- No,no. Unh-unh.

336
00:16:18,500 --> 00:16:19,910
It's just that it's gonna be my job

337
00:16:20,030 --> 00:16:22,240
to evaluate those who are team players

338
00:16:22,370 --> 00:16:23,890
and those who are not.

339
00:16:24,000 --> 00:16:27,170
Just a little heads up.

340
00:16:27,240 --> 00:16:30,070
Just trying to be nice.

341
00:16:33,710 --> 00:16:36,980
I don't know. You seem kinda overqualified.

342
00:16:37,080 --> 00:16:38,430
Why,'cause I went to college?

343
00:16:38,570 --> 00:16:41,990
No,because you finished high school.

344
00:16:42,580 --> 00:16:45,510
well,I just wanna change my life,and...

345
00:16:45,720 --> 00:16:46,570
ever since I was a little girl,

346
00:16:46,680 --> 00:16:49,980
I've always liked horses and the outdoors,and...

347
00:16:50,140 --> 00:16:52,740
well,I'm just fascinated with...

348
00:16:52,860 --> 00:16:54,730
feed

349
00:16:54,850 --> 00:16:59,120
Well,I suppose we could give you a try.

350
00:17:01,290 --> 00:17:02,140
What?

351
00:17:02,280 --> 00:17:04,250
Something on my nose?

352
00:17:04,350 --> 00:17:09,890
Oh,no. Um,I was just lookingat the color of your eyes.

353
00:17:10,180 --> 00:17:11,170
You were?

354
00:17:11,290 --> 00:17:14,120
Yeah.They're just like mine.

355
00:17:14,240 --> 00:17:16,970
They're--they're nice.

356
00:17:17,410 --> 00:17:19,770
Carol sent you to test me,didn't she?

357
00:17:19,890 --> 00:17:21,440
What? Who's carol?

358
00:17:21,540 --> 00:17:22,820
You go back and tell my wife

359
00:17:22,930 --> 00:17:25,210
if a private detectivecouldn't fool me,

360
00:17:25,340 --> 00:17:27,130
well,you're not gonna either.

361
00:17:27,360 --> 00:17:28,280
I don't know whatyou're talking about.

362
00:17:28,450 --> 00:17:30,600
- I just came in to get a little-- - a cute little thing like you

363
00:17:30,720 --> 00:17:33,490
struts in here,flirts with an old codger like me--

364
00:17:33,700 --> 00:17:35,130
how dumb do you thinkI am?

365
00:17:35,230 --> 00:17:38,280
Hey,look at you. Pretty hair.You got a sexy walk.

366
00:17:38,420 --> 00:17:39,920
You got a tight little ass--

367
00:17:40,030 --> 00:17:43,070
oh,I'm your daughter.

368
00:17:43,620 --> 00:17:45,420
What?

369
00:17:46,660 --> 00:17:50,480
Back in the '60s,you had a brief...

370
00:17:50,620 --> 00:17:54,630
relationship with a young girl,sophia bremmer.

371
00:17:54,750 --> 00:17:56,330
She got pregnantand had a baby,

372
00:17:56,450 --> 00:17:59,370
and that baby was me,

373
00:17:59,510 --> 00:18:03,080
which makes you my father.

374
00:18:03,220 --> 00:18:05,540
Hi.

375
00:18:08,410 --> 00:18:09,430
Mr. Prudy,I'm sorry.

376
00:18:09,550 --> 00:18:10,830
I didn't want to spring on you like this.

377
00:18:10,940 --> 00:18:12,120
Where are you going?

378
00:18:12,530 --> 00:18:13,980
You see,when I found out you were alive

379
00:18:14,110 --> 00:18:16,030
and that we both lived in the same city,

380
00:18:16,150 --> 00:18:18,890
I just wanted to meet you.

381
00:18:19,300 --> 00:18:21,350
Mr. Prudy?

382
00:18:21,750 --> 00:18:24,610
mr. Prudy.

383
00:18:25,090 --> 00:18:28,170
Hello?

384
00:18:28,880 --> 00:18:31,530
hello?

385
00:18:43,610 --> 00:18:46,890
And knock wood,the doctors say I'll keep improving

386
00:18:47,090 --> 00:18:49,800
slowly but surely.

387
00:18:49,930 --> 00:18:52,170
So how are you?

388
00:18:52,280 --> 00:18:54,530
Good,good.I'm seeing friends,

389
00:18:55,210 --> 00:18:57,500
and I just startedco-chairing a charity event

390
00:18:57,740 --> 00:19:00,380
for the junior league,and,um,

391
00:19:00,600 --> 00:19:03,830
and I broke up with george.

392
00:19:03,870 --> 00:19:05,170
Really?

393
00:19:05,290 --> 00:19:09,290
Dr. Goldfine,do you ever really cure people,

394
00:19:09,380 --> 00:19:11,480
I mean,even if they're really crazy?

395
00:19:11,640 --> 00:19:13,710
I'm not a big fan of that word.

396
00:19:13,820 --> 00:19:17,060
People either have mental health or they don'T.

397
00:19:17,200 --> 00:19:18,730
When they do have a problem,

398
00:19:18,850 --> 00:19:21,490
you treat them as if they had any other disease,

399
00:19:21,620 --> 00:19:23,700
and sometimes they get better.

400
00:19:23,830 --> 00:19:25,340
Well,when I broke up with george,

401
00:19:25,470 --> 00:19:28,380
I saw something in his eyes.

402
00:19:28,510 --> 00:19:31,370
It was a kind of malevolence,

403
00:19:31,500 --> 00:19:32,400
and it just didn't seem to me

404
00:19:32,580 --> 00:19:34,740
to be the sort of thing that you could cure.

405
00:19:34,940 --> 00:19:36,470
I don't believe in evil either.

406
00:19:36,590 --> 00:19:37,600
We're all just people.

407
00:19:37,750 --> 00:19:38,960
How can you notbelieve in evil?

408
00:19:39,100 --> 00:19:41,950
A man just threw youoff a bridge for no reason.

409
00:19:42,070 --> 00:19:44,800
Exactly. He didn't know anything about me.

410
00:19:44,990 --> 00:19:48,140
He just rode upon his little blue bike

411
00:19:48,270 --> 00:19:49,170
and tried to hurt me.

412
00:19:49,300 --> 00:19:53,650
Do I think he's wicked? No. He's disturbed.

413
00:19:53,830 --> 00:19:57,360
His problems probably stem from a chemical imbalance.

414
00:19:57,470 --> 00:20:02,180
I believe with enough time and treatment,
I could help him.

415
00:20:03,030 --> 00:20:05,800
Did you say a blue bike?

416
00:20:06,220 --> 00:20:07,160
Black?

417
00:20:07,300 --> 00:20:09,140
Great.

418
00:20:10,220 --> 00:20:11,540
I gotta say,lynette,

419
00:20:11,740 --> 00:20:13,290
I was surprised to get your call.

420
00:20:13,430 --> 00:20:15,520
I didn't even think you'd notice I was fired.

421
00:20:15,640 --> 00:20:18,860
Of course I noticed.You are one of my favorites.

422
00:20:19,080 --> 00:20:22,470
And I thought it was really unfair 
how it all went down.

423
00:20:22,670 --> 00:20:24,080
It wasn't that unfair,

424
00:20:24,210 --> 00:20:25,850
I was late all those times

425
00:20:25,990 --> 00:20:27,490
and I broke the copier.

426
00:20:27,620 --> 00:20:29,510
And I stole all those paper clips.

427
00:20:29,620 --> 00:20:33,630
See,I don't think that's why you got fired.

428
00:20:33,760 --> 00:20:36,760
Really?That's what nina said.

429
00:20:36,910 --> 00:20:41,070
Word got out thatyou and nina were...

430
00:20:41,240 --> 00:20:43,010
shagging?

431
00:20:43,400 --> 00:20:44,710
being intimate.

432
00:20:44,850 --> 00:20:48,770
And nina fired youto keep ed from finding out.

433
00:20:48,910 --> 00:20:49,880
You're kidding.

434
00:20:49,980 --> 00:20:51,670
And that wasn't rightof her.

435
00:20:51,830 --> 00:20:53,210
She shouldn't have beenhaving sex with you.

436
00:20:53,350 --> 00:20:55,600
She's upper management.

437
00:20:55,720 --> 00:20:58,520
Technically,it's sexual harassment.

438
00:20:58,640 --> 00:21:01,090
But I was into it.I consented.

439
00:21:01,250 --> 00:21:04,930
Stu,you're A... gofer.

440
00:21:05,140 --> 00:21:08,000
You can't consent to anything.

441
00:21:08,730 --> 00:21:12,880
So I think you should talk to ed about 
getting your job back.

442
00:21:13,000 --> 00:21:14,430
Why would he care?

443
00:21:14,530 --> 00:21:16,260
Oh,he'll care.

444
00:21:16,390 --> 00:21:19,960
He doesn't want you suing him for millions of dollars.

445
00:21:20,410 --> 00:21:23,130
Wow!

446
00:21:24,200 --> 00:21:26,200
So would nina get in trouble?

447
00:21:26,330 --> 00:21:27,830
Well,I'm not gonna lie to you.

448
00:21:27,960 --> 00:21:31,420
There is a possibility she'd get A...

449
00:21:31,640 --> 00:21:34,610
slap on the wrist.

450
00:21:34,900 --> 00:21:36,480
So...

451
00:21:36,620 --> 00:21:38,500
you'll think about talking to ed?

452
00:21:38,600 --> 00:21:40,670
Definitely.

453
00:21:44,690 --> 00:21:46,930
The nurse told meyou were waiting out there.

454
00:21:47,050 --> 00:21:49,140
I just wanted to seeif you were okay.

455
00:21:49,280 --> 00:21:53,260
Sorry if I spooked you.I've got a bad heart.

456
00:21:53,410 --> 00:21:56,600
It's genetic,so you mightwanna get that checked.

457
00:21:56,810 --> 00:21:59,810
Oh. Okay.

458
00:22:00,000 --> 00:22:04,120
Look,don't take this wrong,but I need you to clear out.

459
00:22:04,470 --> 00:22:05,930
What? I just got here.

460
00:22:06,100 --> 00:22:07,760
My wife is on her way.

461
00:22:07,870 --> 00:22:09,290
The thing is,if carol finds out

462
00:22:09,410 --> 00:22:12,280
I'e got an adult love childrunning around,

463
00:22:12,410 --> 00:22:15,450
that's gonna be the strawthat breaks the camel's back.

464
00:22:15,580 --> 00:22:20,920
I mean,it's not exactlythe only time I've strayed.

465
00:22:21,040 --> 00:22:22,160
Charming.

466
00:22:22,280 --> 00:22:23,600
But believe me

467
00:22:23,780 --> 00:22:26,230
it was niceto finally get to meet you.

468
00:22:26,340 --> 00:22:29,490
You're a lovely woman.

469
00:22:30,300 --> 00:22:35,620
Hon,you really need to leave now.

470
00:22:38,270 --> 00:22:40,720
It's susan.

471
00:22:40,850 --> 00:22:42,300
My name is susan. And

472
00:22:43,440 --> 00:22:45,840
no,that's not good enough.

473
00:22:45,890 --> 00:22:46,950
Look,I'M...

474
00:22:47,070 --> 00:22:50,770
I'm trying really hard to be nice about this,

475
00:22:50,830 --> 00:22:52,310
but you're backing meinto a corner.

476
00:22:52,450 --> 00:22:54,420
It's not like I want an invitation to thanksgiving.

477
00:22:54,690 --> 00:22:59,180
I just wanna have coffee or lunch now and then.

478
00:22:59,220 --> 00:23:01,240
I can't start up something with you.

479
00:23:01,370 --> 00:23:02,840
It wouldn't be fair to my wife.

480
00:23:02,970 --> 00:23:03,870
Oh,that's funny.

481
00:23:03,980 --> 00:23:05,400
So all the times you were cheating on her,

482
00:23:05,580 --> 00:23:07,500
that was okay,but having lunch with your daughter--

483
00:23:07,640 --> 00:23:10,100
that just crosses the line.

484
00:23:11,260 --> 00:23:14,070
I just want a chanceto get to know you.

485
00:23:14,460 --> 00:23:18,840
Well,I don't want toknow you.

486
00:23:19,790 --> 00:23:23,010
I've already got a family.

487
00:23:23,460 --> 00:23:26,330
Years ago,your mother and icame to an understanding.

488
00:23:26,460 --> 00:23:28,150
I gave her a bunch of money,

489
00:23:28,300 --> 00:23:32,370
and she agreedto keep things quiet.

490
00:23:32,690 --> 00:23:36,450
Well,I wasn't consulted on that little arrangement.

491
00:23:36,570 --> 00:23:38,610
I don't think it's fair to punish me for

492
00:23:38,720 --> 00:23:40,590
a mistake I madeyears ago.

493
00:23:40,630 --> 00:23:44,200
Is that what you think of me?I'm a mistake?

494
00:23:44,320 --> 00:23:47,440
That's what you need to hear,yeah.

495
00:23:47,570 --> 00:23:50,920
That's what I think.

496
00:23:52,960 --> 00:23:54,990
Oh,addy!

497
00:23:55,200 --> 00:23:57,800
Addy! Oh!

498
00:23:58,400 --> 00:24:00,280
Oh,are you okay?

499
00:24:00,510 --> 00:24:01,920
I'm good,baby.

500
00:24:02,210 --> 00:24:05,020
The kidsare on their way over.

501
00:24:06,470 --> 00:24:09,400
Hi. I'M... carol.

502
00:24:09,500 --> 00:24:13,170
You are...

503
00:24:13,740 --> 00:24:16,710
do you wanna tell her,or should I?

504
00:24:22,320 --> 00:24:26,230
I'm your husband'sguardian angel.

505
00:24:26,720 --> 00:24:28,410
Excuse me?

506
00:24:28,530 --> 00:24:30,550
My name's susan.

507
00:24:30,700 --> 00:24:32,750
I was buying some horse feed when

508
00:24:32,880 --> 00:24:35,750
mr. Prudy had an attack behind the counter.I

509
00:24:35,870 --> 00:24:37,800
gave him C.P.R.,Called 9-1-1.

510
00:24:37,930 --> 00:24:41,570
Oh! Thank you.

511
00:24:41,740 --> 00:24:43,930
Thank you.

512
00:24:44,710 --> 00:24:48,620
When I think what--what could have happened...

513
00:24:49,470 --> 00:24:52,000
well,I'm gonna get out of here.

514
00:24:52,120 --> 00:24:53,510
Mr. Prudy,I want you to hurry up

515
00:24:53,650 --> 00:24:56,230
and get back on your feet.

516
00:24:56,770 --> 00:24:59,040
I'm not giving up.

517
00:24:59,120 --> 00:25:00,770
I'm gonna be back in the store next week.

518
00:25:01,010 --> 00:25:04,670
I never got that darn horse feed.

519
00:25:04,810 --> 00:25:07,720
I guess I'll puta bag aside for you.

520
00:25:07,840 --> 00:25:10,030
You do that.

521
00:25:33,240 --> 00:25:34,460
Bree,it's me.

522
00:25:34,570 --> 00:25:36,370
The police are at my house.
They're going through my stuff.

523
00:25:36,480 --> 00:25:38,200
What the hell is going on?

524
00:25:38,330 --> 00:25:40,560
Look,I know you're there.Pick up!

525
00:25:40,680 --> 00:25:42,330
Did you have anythingto do with this?

526
00:25:42,460 --> 00:25:45,550
Bree? Bree!

527
00:25:46,970 --> 00:25:51,170
George,I know what you did to dr. Goldfine,

528
00:25:51,290 --> 00:25:53,800
and I can see now just how sick you really are,

529
00:25:53,950 --> 00:25:55,580
so please just turn yourself in,

530
00:25:55,720 --> 00:25:58,990
and that way you can get the help you really need.

531
00:25:59,670 --> 00:26:01,690
George?

532
00:26:21,930 --> 00:26:23,260
What's going on?

533
00:26:23,390 --> 00:26:26,850
Oh,I invited sister mary hotpants over for lunch.

534
00:26:26,990 --> 00:26:27,760
What?

535
00:26:27,870 --> 00:26:28,800
You said she touchedyour soul,

536
00:26:28,900 --> 00:26:32,340
so I just want to make sure her hands are clean.

537
00:26:34,570 --> 00:26:36,630
so,sister mary,tell me,

538
00:26:36,770 --> 00:26:38,690
what's it likemeeting men in prison?

539
00:26:38,870 --> 00:26:42,180
Do you bond with all convicts,or was carlos just special?

540
00:26:42,320 --> 00:26:44,730
Well,of course,carlos is special,

541
00:26:44,860 --> 00:26:48,220
but our mission doesa ton of 
evangelical work with several prisons.

542
00:26:48,480 --> 00:26:49,240
Oh,I get it.

543
00:26:49,380 --> 00:26:52,610
Sort of like,today's convictis tomorrow's convert.

544
00:26:52,850 --> 00:26:54,030
Something like that,

545
00:26:54,170 --> 00:26:56,110
but mostly I do charity work.

546
00:26:56,250 --> 00:26:58,390
Are you two involvedin any charities?

547
00:26:58,510 --> 00:27:01,150
Currently? No.

548
00:27:01,290 --> 00:27:04,250
But we should be.I mean,let's face it,gaby.

549
00:27:04,360 --> 00:27:06,890
Buying more stuff isn't gonna make our lives any better.

550
00:27:07,020 --> 00:27:08,340
Exactly.

551
00:27:08,500 --> 00:27:10,930
Money can't buy happiness.

552
00:27:11,040 --> 00:27:12,160
Well,sure it can.

553
00:27:12,280 --> 00:27:13,340
That's just a lie we tell poor people

554
00:27:13,430 --> 00:27:15,450
to keep 'em from rioting.- Gaby!

555
00:27:15,690 --> 00:27:17,680
It's a joke. Lighten up.

556
00:27:17,840 --> 00:27:20,250
Can you believe this? 
I'm married to a woman so selfish,

557
00:27:20,350 --> 00:27:22,880
she makes fun of the entireconcept of charity.

558
00:27:23,000 --> 00:27:24,290
You are a hypocrite.

559
00:27:24,530 --> 00:27:25,930
The money you spentto buy your sports car

560
00:27:26,050 --> 00:27:28,600
could buy a mud hutfor every peasant in ecuador.

561
00:27:28,730 --> 00:27:29,840
Okay,you're right.

562
00:27:29,960 --> 00:27:33,330
But I'm evolving,starting right now.

563
00:27:33,460 --> 00:27:36,660
Sister,I would like to donatemy car to your mission.

564
00:27:36,780 --> 00:27:37,500
What?

565
00:27:37,610 --> 00:27:40,800
- Carlos,are you sure?
- Absolutely.

566
00:27:40,920 --> 00:27:43,130
Gabrielle and I don't need two cars. We can share one.

567
00:27:43,260 --> 00:27:46,610
Share? What if you have the car,
and I need to go shopping?

568
00:27:46,770 --> 00:27:48,930
We're gonna cut back on shopping,too.

569
00:27:49,110 --> 00:27:51,880
Okay,I think we should all just calm down a little bit.

570
00:27:51,990 --> 00:27:53,740
I'm gonna get you that pink slipright now.

571
00:27:53,940 --> 00:27:56,940
- Carlos...
- we're doing this.

572
00:27:58,460 --> 00:28:01,380
I have to--ahem.Uh,here have some of this.

573
00:28:01,510 --> 00:28:03,940
No one needs to know.

574
00:28:08,940 --> 00:28:11,050
Don't even bother. You're not talking me out of this.

575
00:28:11,160 --> 00:28:13,250
I'm not here to talk you out of anything.

576
00:28:13,380 --> 00:28:15,980
Check in this drawer.

577
00:28:18,480 --> 00:28:21,510
Carlos,I wanna apologize for the way I've been acting.

578
00:28:21,740 --> 00:28:24,340
I mean,here you are trying to turn your life around,

579
00:28:24,470 --> 00:28:28,840
and all I can think about are my stupid jealousy issues.

580
00:28:29,130 --> 00:28:31,170
Yeah,well,let's just get back down there.

581
00:28:31,300 --> 00:28:33,410
No,I mean it.I'm sorry.

582
00:28:33,550 --> 00:28:36,310
I wanna be a better person,too.

583
00:28:36,450 --> 00:28:39,930
I'm sick of being bad.

584
00:28:40,240 --> 00:28:42,890
Forgive me?

585
00:28:43,070 --> 00:28:44,180
You're not a bad person.

586
00:28:44,320 --> 00:28:46,230
Really?

587
00:28:48,030 --> 00:28:50,270
No,of course not.

588
00:28:50,390 --> 00:28:52,860
That's so sweet.

589
00:28:52,980 --> 00:28:56,550
I feel so close to youright now.

590
00:28:57,650 --> 00:28:58,420
gaby.

591
00:28:58,560 --> 00:29:03,820
I'm sorry.Guess i am bad.

592
00:29:03,960 --> 00:29:08,000
Look,we got a nun downstairs.

593
00:29:08,110 --> 00:29:12,950
She can wait five minutes.We're giving her a car.

594
00:29:28,130 --> 00:29:29,160
Hey,pat,what's going on?

595
00:29:29,260 --> 00:29:30,620
I'm not sure.

596
00:29:30,750 --> 00:29:33,280
Ed keeps calling people into his office.

597
00:29:33,410 --> 00:29:35,140
I think people are getting fired.

598
00:29:35,370 --> 00:29:37,570
Lynette.

599
00:29:37,780 --> 00:29:39,420
Yeah.

600
00:29:47,450 --> 00:29:48,960
Lynette...

601
00:29:49,290 --> 00:29:50,590
nina's out. You're in.

602
00:29:50,720 --> 00:29:52,830
You areour new V.P. Of accounts.

603
00:29:52,970 --> 00:29:54,930
I... am?

604
00:29:55,040 --> 00:29:55,990
I just gave her the ax,

605
00:29:56,100 --> 00:29:57,810
along with a bunch of other people.

606
00:29:57,940 --> 00:29:59,600
Why? What happened?

607
00:29:59,780 --> 00:30:01,990
Our old pal stu just filed a sexual harassment

608
00:30:02,110 --> 00:30:04,220
suit against the company.

609
00:30:04,350 --> 00:30:05,990
He did what?

610
00:30:06,040 --> 00:30:08,030
He fired a fancy lawyer whothreatened 
to go to the press.

611
00:30:08,150 --> 00:30:09,840
I had no choicebut to pay him off.

612
00:30:09,970 --> 00:30:14,480
He had a video of himand nina together.

613
00:30:14,600 --> 00:30:18,510
Okay. I... get nina,but

614
00:30:18,640 --> 00:30:20,770
why are you firingeverybody else?

615
00:30:20,940 --> 00:30:22,450
Stu's taking us to the cleaners.

616
00:30:22,580 --> 00:30:23,940
If I don't cut backon staff,

617
00:30:24,060 --> 00:30:27,000
the next roundof paychecks are gonna bounce.

618
00:30:27,080 --> 00:30:31,040
Oh,god,ed.I am so sorry.

619
00:30:31,190 --> 00:30:34,030
Well,it's not your fault.We'll get through this.

620
00:30:34,130 --> 00:30:38,480
You and me together.

621
00:30:38,740 --> 00:30:40,580
Oh,can you run down to the art department?

622
00:30:40,790 --> 00:30:43,230
Someone's gotta can jeff and elizabeth.

623
00:30:43,350 --> 00:30:48,120
Yeah. Sure. I'm gonna goand take care of that.

624
00:30:49,300 --> 00:30:52,330
Hey. Congratulations.

625
00:30:52,530 --> 00:30:56,410
This...is not what I wanted.

626
00:30:56,540 --> 00:30:58,610
I just wanted youto be nicer.

627
00:30:58,720 --> 00:31:03,060
You know what?I used to be nice.but

628
00:31:03,300 --> 00:31:07,880
our boss--I'm sorry. Your boss...

629
00:31:08,010 --> 00:31:10,670
is incompetent and selfish

630
00:31:10,810 --> 00:31:14,100
and has the attention spanof a poodle.

631
00:31:14,240 --> 00:31:17,290
I mean,from day one, 
I have been the only one around here

632
00:31:17,380 --> 00:31:18,990
keeping this placefrom crumbling down

633
00:31:19,130 --> 00:31:20,710
around his stupid ears.

634
00:31:20,840 --> 00:31:22,620
Oh,nina,come on.

635
00:31:22,750 --> 00:31:24,760
This is the truth here.

636
00:31:24,890 --> 00:31:28,520
Nice is a luxury that I gave up

637
00:31:28,650 --> 00:31:33,110
along with vacations and relationships

638
00:31:33,240 --> 00:31:35,010
and eating at home.

639
00:31:35,150 --> 00:31:38,730
This job sucks you dry.

640
00:31:38,950 --> 00:31:41,940
So you better kiss those four little kiddies 
of yours good-bye

641
00:31:42,070 --> 00:31:43,880
because you have just adopted

642
00:31:44,010 --> 00:31:48,490
the neediest little childin the world.

643
00:31:48,740 --> 00:31:49,640
Here.

644
00:31:49,780 --> 00:31:52,920
You're gonna need this more than I do.

645
00:32:04,640 --> 00:32:06,330
Hi.

646
00:32:06,450 --> 00:32:08,340
Carlos will be down in a little while.

647
00:32:08,480 --> 00:32:11,090
We had an intense talk.

648
00:32:11,210 --> 00:32:12,770
He's resting.

649
00:32:12,900 --> 00:32:17,270
Yeah,I overheard some of your... talk.

650
00:32:17,380 --> 00:32:21,010
Sorry. He's such an animal

651
00:32:21,220 --> 00:32:22,500
but since we have a couple of minutes,

652
00:32:22,600 --> 00:32:26,000
why don't we,uh,chat?

653
00:32:31,260 --> 00:32:33,160
Look,I don't meanany disrespect.

654
00:32:33,280 --> 00:32:35,560
It's just,now that carlos is home,

655
00:32:35,690 --> 00:32:37,890
we need to get backon our routine,

656
00:32:38,020 --> 00:32:40,250
and we can't do that if he keeps running off to church

657
00:32:40,420 --> 00:32:42,840
and charity bake sales.

658
00:32:42,960 --> 00:32:46,420
We need "us" time.Do you know what I mean?

659
00:32:46,540 --> 00:32:47,460
I do.

660
00:32:47,580 --> 00:32:49,860
Oh,good. Good.

661
00:32:49,980 --> 00:32:52,020
So it would really help our marriage

662
00:32:52,150 --> 00:32:57,900
if you just backed off for a while,okay?

663
00:32:58,030 --> 00:32:59,600
No.

664
00:32:59,830 --> 00:33:01,380
Huh?

665
00:33:01,520 --> 00:33:03,460
I said no.

666
00:33:03,990 --> 00:33:07,560
I know what you said.I'm wondering why you said it.

667
00:33:07,680 --> 00:33:09,930
Carlos isa diamond in the rough,

668
00:33:10,060 --> 00:33:11,250
a flawed man to be sure,

669
00:33:11,370 --> 00:33:13,530
but someone who is desperately searching

670
00:33:13,650 --> 00:33:15,340
for something to believe in.

671
00:33:15,680 --> 00:33:18,310
To satisfy your materialism,
he ended up breaking the law.

672
00:33:18,420 --> 00:33:21,330
To deal with your adultery,he resorted to assault.

673
00:33:21,480 --> 00:33:22,430
As long as he's with you,

674
00:33:22,550 --> 00:33:24,560
he will never find what he's looking for.

675
00:33:24,720 --> 00:33:26,210
Well,I guess he should have thought of that

676
00:33:26,330 --> 00:33:28,170
before he married me.

677
00:33:28,270 --> 00:33:31,870
Some marriagesare meant to be annulled.

678
00:33:32,020 --> 00:33:34,740
What the hell kind of nunare you?

679
00:33:34,810 --> 00:33:36,760
Look,if you try to comebetween me and my husband,

680
00:33:36,890 --> 00:33:39,030
I will take you down.

681
00:33:39,570 --> 00:33:41,960
I grew up onthe south side of chicago.

682
00:33:42,030 --> 00:33:42,780
If you wanna threaten me,

683
00:33:42,870 --> 00:33:44,910
you're gonna have to doa lot better than that.

684
00:33:45,070 --> 00:33:47,960
You listen to me,you little bitch.

685
00:33:48,090 --> 00:33:51,200
You do not want to start a war with me.

686
00:33:52,180 --> 00:33:54,910
well,I have god on my side.

687
00:33:55,070 --> 00:33:58,950
Bring it on.

688
00:34:16,000 --> 00:34:16,970
you called for a bellman?

689
00:34:17,090 --> 00:34:19,460
There's a charity dinnertaking place downstairs.

690
00:34:19,580 --> 00:34:22,610
My friend bree van de kampis one of the co-chairs.

691
00:34:22,720 --> 00:34:25,090
Give her this noteand walk away.

692
00:34:25,210 --> 00:34:29,180
If she comes upin the elevator,call me.

693
00:34:29,310 --> 00:34:31,460
You think you can do that?

694
00:34:31,590 --> 00:34:34,010
Yes,sir.

695
00:34:37,690 --> 00:34:39,320
- Excuse me,ma'am? 
- Yes

696
00:34:39,440 --> 00:34:40,700
I was asked to give this to you.

697
00:34:40,820 --> 00:34:42,480
Oh,thank you.

698
00:34:57,840 --> 00:34:58,610
Barton.

699
00:34:58,730 --> 00:35:00,190
Hello,detective barton.This is bree van de kamp.

700
00:35:00,310 --> 00:35:01,610
I need to talk to you about george williams.

701
00:35:01,720 --> 00:35:03,500
Yeah,I was just gettingready to call you, 
mrs. Van de kamp.

702
00:35:04,640 --> 00:35:06,370
My men are at his house right now,

703
00:35:06,510 --> 00:35:09,500
and they've uncovered evidence that suggests

704
00:35:09,640 --> 00:35:13,800
mr. Williams was responsible 
for your husband's death.

705
00:35:14,460 --> 00:35:16,510
- What? - Yeah,we found

706
00:35:16,640 --> 00:35:18,050
rex's prescription bottles

707
00:35:18,180 --> 00:35:20,800
and doctored potassium pills

708
00:35:20,920 --> 00:35:26,790
as well as some disturbing diary entries.

709
00:35:28,170 --> 00:35:30,960
Mrs. Van de kamp?

710
00:35:42,770 --> 00:35:44,060
Hello,sir.

711
00:35:44,200 --> 00:35:47,870
Yes.She's,uh,on her way up.

712
00:35:47,990 --> 00:35:50,310
Thank you very much.

713
00:35:55,840 --> 00:35:58,080
She loves me.

714
00:35:59,490 --> 00:36:01,110
She loves me not.

715
00:36:10,130 --> 00:36:12,490
She loves me.

716
00:36:16,650 --> 00:36:17,740
she loves me not.

717
00:36:26,030 --> 00:36:28,880
She loves me.

718
00:37:10,370 --> 00:37:12,570
operator,

719
00:37:12,680 --> 00:37:15,130
this is a bit embarrassing, but I've...

720
00:37:15,260 --> 00:37:17,220
I've swallowed some pillsby mistake.

721
00:37:17,350 --> 00:37:19,730
I think you need to callan ambulance.

722
00:37:21,020 --> 00:37:24,400
uh,uh,uh,they were--

723
00:37:24,540 --> 00:37:27,090
they were just vitamins

724
00:37:27,350 --> 00:37:30,790
see? False alarm.I'm fine.

725
00:37:31,310 --> 00:37:32,690
Door's open.

726
00:37:44,650 --> 00:37:46,330
Hey.

727
00:37:49,200 --> 00:37:52,780
What were you thinking,taking the pills?

728
00:37:52,910 --> 00:37:56,210
I didn't hurt dr. Goldfine.

729
00:37:56,350 --> 00:37:58,280
And for you to...

730
00:37:58,540 --> 00:38:01,690
think me capable of...

731
00:38:01,830 --> 00:38:04,610
that sort of...

732
00:38:06,900 --> 00:38:08,650
violence...

733
00:38:08,800 --> 00:38:10,890
george.

734
00:38:13,890 --> 00:38:15,780
George.

735
00:38:18,030 --> 00:38:20,710
I'm sorry.It's the pills.

736
00:38:20,920 --> 00:38:22,590
Why are you telling me this?

737
00:38:22,720 --> 00:38:25,490
Because maybe I don't have to die.

738
00:38:26,040 --> 00:38:28,270
I could face the police

739
00:38:28,410 --> 00:38:31,420
knowing that youwould be there for me...

740
00:38:32,580 --> 00:38:35,110
that you'd stay my friend.

741
00:38:36,490 --> 00:38:39,520
Then I'll have somethingto live for.

742
00:38:39,660 --> 00:38:44,120
And then we'll call an ambulance 
and they'll pump your stomach.

743
00:38:44,250 --> 00:38:46,720
Yes.

744
00:39:02,890 --> 00:39:05,360
I want to help you,

745
00:39:05,720 --> 00:39:09,220
but in order to do that,
I need to forgive you, and...

746
00:39:10,000 --> 00:39:13,990
I can't do that until you admit what you've done.

747
00:39:15,660 --> 00:39:19,460
I didn't push goldfine.

748
00:39:19,790 --> 00:39:21,840
Yes,you did.

749
00:39:22,170 --> 00:39:26,490
But that's not what I'm talking about.

750
00:39:28,160 --> 00:39:31,100
You killed rex.

751
00:39:32,080 --> 00:39:34,150
But I know it wasn't totally your fault

752
00:39:34,280 --> 00:39:37,050
because you're not well.

753
00:39:37,370 --> 00:39:41,630
So if you'll just be honest with me,

754
00:39:41,900 --> 00:39:44,530
I can forgive you.

755
00:39:44,900 --> 00:39:46,860
It'll be the hardest thing I've ever done,

756
00:39:47,000 --> 00:39:49,520
but I'll do it.

757
00:39:49,680 --> 00:39:55,770
But you have to--you have to tell me the truth.

758
00:39:58,050 --> 00:40:01,300
look,I'm in trouble here.

759
00:40:01,430 --> 00:40:02,920
We need to call someone.

760
00:40:03,050 --> 00:40:06,480
Not until you admit what you've done.

761
00:40:08,710 --> 00:40:11,360
I love you.

762
00:40:12,510 --> 00:40:16,270
Anything I may have done,I did for you.

763
00:40:18,550 --> 00:40:21,010
Because you wanted me to.

764
00:40:24,190 --> 00:40:27,820
You know you did.

765
00:40:44,810 --> 00:40:47,670
we need to callthe ambulance.

766
00:40:50,950 --> 00:40:55,980
I... called them while you were asleep.

767
00:40:57,630 --> 00:41:01,040
They're already on their way.

768
00:41:25,410 --> 00:41:28,310
It's not always that easy to distinguish

769
00:41:28,440 --> 00:41:31,860
the good guys from the bad guys.

770
00:41:31,990 --> 00:41:35,200
Sinners can surprise you.

771
00:41:36,180 --> 00:41:41,580
And the same is true for saints.

772
00:41:41,970 --> 00:41:48,040
Why do we try to define people 
as simply good or simply evil?

773
00:41:48,450 --> 00:41:52,850
Because no one wants to admit that 
compassion and cruelty

774
00:41:53,000 --> 00:41:57,990
can live side by side in one heart...

775
00:42:04,610 --> 00:42:10,610
and that anyone is capable of anything.

776
00:42:10,860 --> 00:42:11,530
-------------------------- 
www.ydy.com/bbs
Proudly Presents
--------------------------

777
00:42:11,730 --> 00:42:12,580
Desperate Housewives
Season 2 Episode 9



