1
00:00:00,400 --> 00:00:02,500
Previously on... “Desperate Housewives”

2
00:00:02,640 --> 00:00:03,800
did you leave the door open?

3
00:00:03,950 --> 00:00:04,950
Call the police!

4
00:00:05,110 --> 00:00:06,220
Is that the guy who broke into your house?

5
00:00:06,360 --> 00:00:08,450
Arrests were made... yeah,that's him.

6
00:00:08,570 --> 00:00:10,290
I just want a chance to get to know you.

7
00:00:10,780 --> 00:00:11,840
Well,I don't want to know you.

8
00:00:11,840 --> 00:00:13,240
Fathers were confronted...

9
00:00:13,360 --> 00:00:14,940
who's sister mary bernard?

10
00:00:14,940 --> 00:00:16,990
You do not want to start a war with me.

11
00:00:17,110 --> 00:00:18,110
Bring it on.

12
00:00:18,110 --> 00:00:19,620
Boundaries were drawn...

13
00:00:19,750 --> 00:00:22,030
mr. Williams was responsible for your husband's death.

14
00:00:22,160 --> 00:00:25,330
And everyone learned that sometimes justice is served...

15
00:00:25,480 --> 00:00:26,840
we need to call an ambulance.

16
00:00:27,050 --> 00:00:29,460
Without saying a word.

17
00:00:32,910 --> 00:00:37,120
There were many ways to tell Bree van de kamp was a lady.

18
00:00:37,200 --> 00:00:38,250
Thank you very much.

19
00:00:38,370 --> 00:00:41,270
She was courteous to those around her,

20
00:00:41,430 --> 00:00:44,430
she moved with elegance and grace

21
00:00:44,570 --> 00:00:48,140
and she was very careful to never let others know

22
00:00:48,270 --> 00:00:49,900
what she was thinking.

23
00:00:50,040 --> 00:00:53,100
Mrs. Van de kamp,thank you for coming on such short notice.

24
00:00:53,230 --> 00:00:54,610
So what's happened?

25
00:00:54,750 --> 00:00:56,440
Have you had any luck finding george?

26
00:00:56,580 --> 00:00:59,100
You see,like most well-bred women...

27
00:00:59,230 --> 00:01:01,050
george is dead.

28
00:01:01,180 --> 00:01:03,060
He committed suicide last night at a hotel.

29
00:01:03,180 --> 00:01:05,240
Bree had something to hide.

30
00:01:05,370 --> 00:01:08,470
Oh,um...

31
00:01:09,750 --> 00:01:15,850
well,um,it was very good of you to tell me in person,truly.

32
00:01:15,990 --> 00:01:20,410
Actually,uh,there's more.

33
00:01:20,710 --> 00:01:22,580
More?

34
00:01:24,510 --> 00:01:26,830
Do you recognize this?

35
00:01:26,960 --> 00:01:30,710
Those are my panties.How did you...

36
00:01:30,850 --> 00:01:33,270
we assume mr. Williams stole them.

37
00:01:33,420 --> 00:01:34,440
Where did you find them?

38
00:01:34,580 --> 00:01:40,730
Mr. Williams had a room filled with,um...unsavory items.

39
00:01:40,870 --> 00:01:42,060
It was like a shrine.

40
00:01:42,150 --> 00:01:44,870
"Unsavory items"?Well,what does that mean?

41
00:01:45,010 --> 00:01:46,590
You don't want to know.

42
00:01:46,730 --> 00:01:48,090
Just so you're aware,the "daily tribune"

43
00:01:48,240 --> 00:01:49,780
is starting to sniff around this story.

44
00:01:49,930 --> 00:01:51,110
The editor's a good friend of mine.

45
00:01:51,260 --> 00:01:52,450
I'm pretty sure I can quash it,

46
00:01:52,600 --> 00:01:54,440
but you might want to tell your family what's going on,

47
00:01:54,580 --> 00:01:56,270
just in case.

48
00:01:58,770 --> 00:01:59,990
What is that?

49
00:02:00,030 --> 00:02:01,830
I am so sorry. You weren't supposed to see that.

50
00:02:01,900 --> 00:02:03,240
Mudge,get that out of here.

51
00:02:03,370 --> 00:02:07,600
No,wait!Is that supposed to be me?

52
00:02:07,740 --> 00:02:10,330
Well...

53
00:02:11,910 --> 00:02:13,640
it's hard to say.

54
00:02:13,920 --> 00:02:15,000
I don't understand. I mean

55
00:02:15,140 --> 00:02:19,590
what would george be doing with a life-size doll?

56
00:02:23,150 --> 00:02:24,240
oh,dear lord.

57
00:02:24,450 --> 00:02:26,070
- Go ahead. 
- Oh,hold it

58
00:02:26,200 --> 00:02:27,300
What are you gonna do with that?

59
00:02:27,450 --> 00:02:29,810
Well,until we close the file on mr. Williams,

60
00:02:29,900 --> 00:02:31,540
she's considered evidence.

61
00:02:31,600 --> 00:02:33,020
We'll have to take her back to the station.

62
00:02:33,150 --> 00:02:35,920
I am so sorry about this,Mrs. Van de kamp.

63
00:02:36,030 --> 00:02:38,900
I know how difficult all this must be.

64
00:02:42,060 --> 00:02:44,760
Don't you worry about me,detective Barton.

65
00:02:44,890 --> 00:02:46,830
I will be just fine.

66
00:02:46,980 --> 00:02:51,290
Yes,there were many ways to tell that bree was a lady,

67
00:02:51,440 --> 00:02:55,920
but the surest was to watch how she maintained her dignity

68
00:02:56,060 --> 00:03:01,110
in even the most undignified of situations.

69
00:03:01,890 --> 00:03:03,440
--------------------------  
www.ydy.com/bbs 
Proudly Presents 
--------------------------

70
00:03:03,550 --> 00:03:04,700
Sync: YTET-Starry 
-==www.ydy.com/bbs==-

71
00:03:04,990 --> 00:03:06,310
Desperate Housewives 
Season 2 Episode 10

72
00:03:08,060 --> 00:03:12,550
It's a story as old as time itself--

73
00:03:12,690 --> 00:03:16,510
the return of the prodigal son.

74
00:03:17,970 --> 00:03:22,340
And no matter how many times it's repeated...

75
00:03:23,970 --> 00:03:28,550
or how the details might vary...

76
00:03:28,750 --> 00:03:31,790
or how the names might change...

77
00:03:31,930 --> 00:03:36,750
the story always ends the same way...

78
00:03:38,280 --> 00:03:42,200
in the tender embrace of a loving father.

79
00:03:42,490 --> 00:03:44,720
Hi,dad.

80
00:03:51,400 --> 00:03:54,370
Susan mayer told me she gave you some money to go to Utah.

81
00:03:54,510 --> 00:03:56,640
Yeah,I had no idea where to look for you,though,

82
00:03:56,770 --> 00:03:58,100
and the money started to run out,

83
00:03:58,240 --> 00:04:00,010
so I thought that maybe you'd come back here.

84
00:04:00,150 --> 00:04:02,000
You're a smart kid.

85
00:04:02,090 --> 00:04:03,500
Can I ask you something?

86
00:04:03,650 --> 00:04:05,840
Of course. Anything.

87
00:04:08,320 --> 00:04:10,870
Well,when you left town,

88
00:04:11,010 --> 00:04:14,040
Mrs. Tillman said that my real mother was

89
00:04:14,180 --> 00:04:17,080
a junkie from Utah.

90
00:04:20,100 --> 00:04:21,880
That's right.

91
00:04:22,200 --> 00:04:24,230
So...

92
00:04:25,600 --> 00:04:28,810
who's my dad?

93
00:04:31,810 --> 00:04:33,240
I don't know.

94
00:04:33,370 --> 00:04:36,620
It could have been anyone.

95
00:04:45,430 --> 00:04:46,580
Thanks for the faucet.

96
00:04:46,720 --> 00:04:48,890
This leak is driving me crazy.

97
00:04:49,040 --> 00:04:49,730
What do I owe you?

98
00:04:49,800 --> 00:04:50,540
Oh,it's no rush.

99
00:04:50,700 --> 00:04:52,600
Just pay me when I install it.

100
00:04:53,360 --> 00:04:55,520
Hey,there!

101
00:04:56,060 --> 00:04:57,300
Have you seen today's paper?

102
00:04:57,440 --> 00:04:59,190
No,not yet.

103
00:04:59,970 --> 00:05:02,310
Ohh. There's a follow-up on that guy you caught last week.

104
00:05:02,460 --> 00:05:05,920
"Police seek help in identifying mystery vagrant."

105
00:05:06,070 --> 00:05:07,400
They don't know the man's name yet?

106
00:05:07,540 --> 00:05:09,520
They're not even sure that he knows how to talk.

107
00:05:09,660 --> 00:05:11,060
Think they're going to hold him in the psych ward

108
00:05:11,220 --> 00:05:13,590
until they figure out who he is

109
00:05:14,440 --> 00:05:16,970
Well,I will certainly rest easier knowing that

110
00:05:17,110 --> 00:05:19,030
he's not roaming around our neighborhood.

111
00:05:19,240 --> 00:05:21,160
see you!

112
00:05:22,500 --> 00:05:24,450
Thanks again for the faucet.

113
00:05:24,620 --> 00:05:26,080
Sure.

114
00:05:31,130 --> 00:05:33,320
What are we gonna do about Caleb?

115
00:05:33,730 --> 00:05:37,850
Obviously,we are going to go and get him

116
00:05:48,440 --> 00:05:51,230
- Where are my cuffs? 
- Bottom drawer.

117
00:05:51,880 --> 00:05:53,210
Ah.

118
00:05:53,250 --> 00:05:54,970
So when do I tell people you'll be back?

119
00:05:55,130 --> 00:05:57,390
Couple,maybe three days.

120
00:06:02,090 --> 00:06:03,470
What the hell's this?

121
00:06:03,630 --> 00:06:04,670
It's the ball gag.

122
00:06:04,820 --> 00:06:06,550
I thought you wanted it.

123
00:06:06,720 --> 00:06:09,100
We do not recycle ball gags.

124
00:06:09,260 --> 00:06:11,270
Take a look at the teeth marks.

125
00:06:11,440 --> 00:06:13,690
it's gross.

126
00:06:14,640 --> 00:06:18,130
I'd like to think that we're better than that.

127
00:06:18,910 --> 00:06:20,240
Hey, Monroe?

128
00:06:20,410 --> 00:06:21,530
You sure you don't want any help?

129
00:06:21,680 --> 00:06:23,270
The guy's dangerous.

130
00:06:24,970 --> 00:06:26,740
He's a half-wit,Jerry.

131
00:06:26,910 --> 00:06:28,280
If I can handle you,

132
00:06:28,450 --> 00:06:30,390
I can handle him.

133
00:06:33,540 --> 00:06:35,900
So he poisoned Rex?

134
00:06:36,040 --> 00:06:37,450
Sweet,little George Williams.

135
00:06:37,600 --> 00:06:40,660
Well,it turns out he wasn't so sweet after all.

136
00:06:40,800 --> 00:06:43,710
Anyway,there's a chance that some of this may wind up in the paper,

137
00:06:43,840 --> 00:06:46,040
so I wanted you to hear it from me first.

138
00:06:46,180 --> 00:06:48,020
Bree,I'm so sorry.

139
00:06:48,160 --> 00:06:50,820
Yeah,like you haven't been through enough.

140
00:06:50,970 --> 00:06:53,020
God,and he's our pharmacist.

141
00:06:53,180 --> 00:06:54,730
It's enough to turn you holistic.

142
00:06:54,900 --> 00:06:56,020
I know this sounds awful,

143
00:06:56,150 --> 00:06:57,820
but I'm kind of glad the guy's dead.

144
00:06:58,000 --> 00:07:01,200
Oh,I hope that little creep suffered.

145
00:07:01,900 --> 00:07:03,820
Well,we'll never know.

146
00:07:08,980 --> 00:07:11,150
That's Andrew back from camp hennessey.

147
00:07:11,280 --> 00:07:12,120
I've got to go.

148
00:07:12,290 --> 00:07:13,730
Does he know yet?

149
00:07:13,890 --> 00:07:15,250
He hasn't got a clue.

150
00:07:15,390 --> 00:07:17,680
How do you think he's gonna react?

151
00:07:18,090 --> 00:07:20,270
All right,what the hell is going on?

152
00:07:20,410 --> 00:07:23,590
I know you didn't take me out of kid jail for my health.

153
00:07:26,470 --> 00:07:29,330
I'll get back to you later.

154
00:07:35,430 --> 00:07:36,510
So are the police sure?

155
00:07:36,650 --> 00:07:37,840
Yeah.

156
00:07:38,000 --> 00:07:41,550
They found data in George's personal computer

157
00:07:41,710 --> 00:07:44,060
and also records at his pharmacy that

158
00:07:44,220 --> 00:07:47,290
pretty much proves that he was poisoning your father.

159
00:07:47,450 --> 00:07:50,860
Did they say why he killed him?

160
00:07:52,660 --> 00:07:54,610
Well,the detective seems to think he was trying to

161
00:07:54,750 --> 00:07:57,360
get your father out of the way so...

162
00:07:57,510 --> 00:07:59,880
he could marry me.

163
00:08:01,770 --> 00:08:03,890
Honey,please use your coaster.

164
00:08:04,040 --> 00:08:05,020
That's gonna leave a ring.

165
00:08:05,170 --> 00:08:07,680
My father was murdered because of you,

166
00:08:07,830 --> 00:08:08,950
so as far as I'm concerned,

167
00:08:09,110 --> 00:08:10,730
you no longer get to tell me what to do.

168
00:08:10,880 --> 00:08:13,340
Andrew,that is not fair.

169
00:08:13,500 --> 00:08:15,430
You brought that psycho into our house!

170
00:08:15,570 --> 00:08:16,680
You sat him down at our table.

171
00:08:16,830 --> 00:08:18,400
Just how fair do you expect me to be?

172
00:08:18,550 --> 00:08:20,270
Andrew,George williams fooled a lot of people.

173
00:08:20,400 --> 00:08:22,640
Yeah,well,he didn't fool me.

174
00:08:22,790 --> 00:08:26,080
Andrew,I'm not trying to minimize my part in this.

175
00:08:26,230 --> 00:08:29,180
Believe me,I hate myself for what's happened.

176
00:08:29,330 --> 00:08:30,540
Good.

177
00:08:30,690 --> 00:08:33,330
Now we have something in common.

178
00:08:34,020 --> 00:08:35,070
Oh,by the way,

179
00:08:35,220 --> 00:08:36,710
I'm gonna call my friend justin

180
00:08:36,870 --> 00:08:38,700
and have him come over and spend the night tonight.

181
00:08:38,850 --> 00:08:42,430
Justin? Is he a friend of yours from school or church?

182
00:08:42,590 --> 00:08:45,040
What kind of friend is he?

183
00:08:45,290 --> 00:08:49,710
The real good kind.

184
00:08:50,480 --> 00:08:53,680
Andrew,it is inappropriate for you to have somebody over.

185
00:08:53,840 --> 00:08:55,440
You just got home.

186
00:08:55,590 --> 00:08:56,910
Like I said,

187
00:08:57,070 --> 00:09:00,670
you don't get to tell me what to do anymore.

188
00:09:07,730 --> 00:09:09,370
You came.

189
00:09:09,470 --> 00:09:10,510
Did I have a choice?

190
00:09:10,650 --> 00:09:12,380
Well,sure.

191
00:09:12,570 --> 00:09:14,330
Because at the hospital,you sounded like you were

192
00:09:14,540 --> 00:09:15,960
fully prepared to blackmail me

193
00:09:16,090 --> 00:09:18,470
into having some kind of a relationship with you.

194
00:09:18,590 --> 00:09:20,100
That was just the heat of the moment,

195
00:09:20,250 --> 00:09:21,780
and once you get to know me,you'll understand that

196
00:09:21,920 --> 00:09:25,300
I am not the kind of person who could ever,ever resort to blackmail.

197
00:09:25,440 --> 00:09:27,730
Well,I wish you'd made that clear in the hospital.

198
00:09:27,890 --> 00:09:30,590
Could have saved me a trip.

199
00:09:30,730 --> 00:09:32,070
So are you coming in?

200
00:09:32,240 --> 00:09:35,710
Well,I got a lunch hour to kill.

201
00:09:40,080 --> 00:09:41,930
That was my first halloween.I was 2.

202
00:09:42,070 --> 00:09:43,800
What do you think I am?

203
00:09:44,130 --> 00:09:45,280
I don't know

204
00:09:45,450 --> 00:09:46,950
Oh,come on,just guess.You can tell.

205
00:09:47,150 --> 00:09:49,470
Uh,a homeless person?

206
00:09:49,630 --> 00:09:52,000
No,Addison,I'm a chicken.

207
00:09:52,030 --> 00:09:53,660
See? Those are feather shanging around.

208
00:09:53,830 --> 00:09:57,930
Oh. I thought that was supposed to be trash.

209
00:09:58,270 --> 00:10:00,400
Uh,look,are we done here?

210
00:10:00,820 --> 00:10:03,240
You haven't even finished your coffee.

211
00:10:03,400 --> 00:10:05,000
I got to get back to work.

212
00:10:05,070 --> 00:10:07,960
Oh,well,we--we haven't even finished the high school years.

213
00:10:08,120 --> 00:10:09,180
I wanted to show you this one.

214
00:10:09,330 --> 00:10:11,180
This was from the father-daughter dance.

215
00:10:11,360 --> 00:10:14,360
I had to take my mother'shairstylist.

216
00:10:15,520 --> 00:10:18,280
What do you want from me,susan?

217
00:10:19,030 --> 00:10:23,590
Well,I-I just want to share more than our D.N.A. I...

218
00:10:23,960 --> 00:10:25,710
I wanted to have a relationship with you.

219
00:10:25,850 --> 00:10:29,680
None of this means anything to you?

220
00:10:30,750 --> 00:10:32,300
I'll take the hobo picture.

221
00:10:32,430 --> 00:10:36,810
Actually,it was...fine.

222
00:10:37,900 --> 00:10:38,670
What's this?

223
00:10:38,830 --> 00:10:41,120
Our company insurance policy.You ever bother to read it?

224
00:10:41,300 --> 00:10:43,130
I'm going to say no,but don't tell.

225
00:10:43,280 --> 00:10:45,830
We have day care, Ed, day care.

226
00:10:45,980 --> 00:10:48,560
Do you realize that since we fired half the staff,

227
00:10:48,740 --> 00:10:51,070
you and I have barely left the building?

228
00:10:51,220 --> 00:10:52,540
My kids are forgetting who I am.

229
00:10:52,750 --> 00:10:54,210
I hear you.I have 17-month-old

230
00:10:54,370 --> 00:10:55,920
who I haven't actually seen awake in weeks.

231
00:10:56,070 --> 00:11:00,110
See? All we need isa minimum participation

232
00:11:00,230 --> 00:11:04,100
of,uh...16 kids.

233
00:11:04,240 --> 00:11:05,950
My kids,your baby,

234
00:11:06,080 --> 00:11:07,510
sally in accounting has three,

235
00:11:07,660 --> 00:11:09,580
that new guyin human resources has two

236
00:11:09,750 --> 00:11:12,100
and we hit the mother lode with the mormon receptionist.

237
00:11:12,320 --> 00:11:15,280
She just popped out number 6.There. 16.

238
00:11:15,440 --> 00:11:16,860
15. My wife won't do it.

239
00:11:17,030 --> 00:11:18,070
Well,maybe if I talkedto her.

240
00:11:18,180 --> 00:11:21,210
No,I'm telling you,this day care thing is a non-starter.

241
00:11:21,340 --> 00:11:23,360
Fran won't even let anyone else hold the baby.

242
00:11:23,520 --> 00:11:26,090
Well,she won't just take sometime off for a couple of hours?

243
00:11:26,230 --> 00:11:29,770
Lynette,if I hadn'tcut that umbilical cord with my own two hands,

244
00:11:29,930 --> 00:11:33,320
I swear they would still be attached.

245
00:11:33,610 --> 00:11:35,830
But if you want to try...

246
00:11:35,980 --> 00:11:38,850
more power to you.

247
00:11:46,280 --> 00:11:49,700
You! What the hell did you do with my husband?!

248
00:11:49,850 --> 00:11:51,100
Please restrain yourself,gabrielle.

249
00:11:51,240 --> 00:11:52,410
You're in a house of god.

250
00:11:52,560 --> 00:11:54,470
Tell me where he is!

251
00:11:54,640 --> 00:11:56,730
Everywhere,of course.

252
00:11:56,950 --> 00:11:59,510
Not god,my husband.

253
00:11:59,650 --> 00:12:01,870
Gaby,what are you doing here?

254
00:12:02,020 --> 00:12:03,870
I was just about to ask you the same thing.

255
00:12:04,010 --> 00:12:05,740
You were supposed to meet me at the spa.

256
00:12:05,890 --> 00:12:08,240
I was just helping sister mary with the mailings for the fund-raiser.

257
00:12:08,360 --> 00:12:10,590
The church is about to senda relief team to Botswana

258
00:12:10,770 --> 00:12:12,570
to help with the drought.

259
00:12:12,710 --> 00:12:14,210
That's your excuse?

260
00:12:14,370 --> 00:12:16,350
We missed side-by-side water massages.

261
00:12:16,440 --> 00:12:18,720
I had to book them weeks in advance.

262
00:12:18,880 --> 00:12:20,570
Okay,you missed a massage.

263
00:12:20,730 --> 00:12:23,840
It's unfortunate,but there are people dying in Botswana.

264
00:12:23,990 --> 00:12:25,650
There are going to be people dying in this church

265
00:12:25,800 --> 00:12:28,590
if you don't wipe that patronizing look off your face!

266
00:12:28,870 --> 00:12:31,570
What is your problem?

267
00:12:31,860 --> 00:12:34,710
Sister mary,will you excuse us,please?

268
00:12:34,840 --> 00:12:36,930
Certainly.

269
00:12:39,330 --> 00:12:41,800
We are supposed to be working on our marriage,carlos,

270
00:12:41,930 --> 00:12:45,110
but we can't do thatas long as our lady of perpetual stick-up-her-butt

271
00:12:45,250 --> 00:12:48,060
has you worrying about thirsty orphans.

272
00:12:48,210 --> 00:12:51,030
You're blaming sister mary for the tension in our marriage?

273
00:12:51,180 --> 00:12:52,490
She wants us fighting.

274
00:12:52,620 --> 00:12:53,840
She wants you to get tired of me

275
00:12:53,970 --> 00:12:55,760
and walk out so she can have you all to herself.

276
00:12:55,890 --> 00:12:57,390
That's crazy. She's a nun.

277
00:12:57,530 --> 00:12:59,420
She may wear a habit and the beads,

278
00:12:59,570 --> 00:13:00,640
but at the end of the day,

279
00:13:00,770 --> 00:13:02,730
she is still a woman,just like me,

280
00:13:02,880 --> 00:13:04,920
and I know what I'm capable of.

281
00:13:05,070 --> 00:13:06,930
She is a woman...

282
00:13:08,050 --> 00:13:11,360
but she is nothing like you.

283
00:13:12,710 --> 00:13:14,860
Carlos,where are you going?

284
00:13:16,680 --> 00:13:18,910
Carlos!

285
00:13:21,960 --> 00:13:23,420
You look tense,gabrielle.

286
00:13:23,560 --> 00:13:27,110
Perhaps you should think about getting a massage.

287
00:13:32,650 --> 00:13:35,480
hi, Susan,it's Addison. Are you there?

288
00:13:35,610 --> 00:13:37,650
Hi. Hi,yeah,I'm here.

289
00:13:37,800 --> 00:13:39,300
Good. You're home.

290
00:13:39,450 --> 00:13:40,690
Uh-huh. What's up?

291
00:13:40,850 --> 00:13:43,310
You know you were saying you wanted to be part of my life?

292
00:13:43,440 --> 00:13:44,480
Yeah.

293
00:13:44,610 --> 00:13:45,880
I'm at the police station.

294
00:13:46,000 --> 00:13:48,240
I need you to come bail me out.

295
00:13:49,170 --> 00:13:51,910
Solicitation? You were arrested for solicitation?

296
00:13:52,060 --> 00:13:54,080
It was entrapment.I'm the victim here.

297
00:13:54,210 --> 00:13:56,060
But you were with a prostitute.

298
00:13:56,200 --> 00:13:57,710
Apparently not.

299
00:13:57,860 --> 00:14:00,100
I asked her three times--"are you a cop?"

300
00:14:00,240 --> 00:14:02,600
They got to tell you,but she didn't say "boo."

301
00:14:02,730 --> 00:14:04,220
I thought this was America!

302
00:14:04,360 --> 00:14:07,000
Addison,you just got caught paying for sex.

303
00:14:07,130 --> 00:14:09,120
Now is not the time to wrap yourself in the flag.

304
00:14:09,240 --> 00:14:10,340
Don't give me that look.

305
00:14:10,600 --> 00:14:12,190
It wasn't my fault.I'm sorry.

306
00:14:12,330 --> 00:14:15,210
How is trying to pick up a hooker not your fault?

307
00:14:15,350 --> 00:14:17,690
I was at the store,I was working on my computer

308
00:14:17,830 --> 00:14:19,640
and then,you know,they have these ads?

309
00:14:19,880 --> 00:14:23,460
They pop up on the screen and they ask if you want to have a hot date.

310
00:14:23,620 --> 00:14:25,750
Well,it gets a fellow worked up.

311
00:14:25,900 --> 00:14:29,610
Can't you just go home and have sex with your wife like a normal person?

312
00:14:29,760 --> 00:14:31,950
She's a 68-year-old woman.

313
00:14:32,100 --> 00:14:34,060
That bell stopped ringing for me years ago.

314
00:14:34,090 --> 00:14:37,090
Oh,my god.Stop. Right now.

315
00:14:37,630 --> 00:14:39,690
I'm gonna gopay this thing.

316
00:14:45,800 --> 00:14:48,090
So am I off the hook now?

317
00:14:48,530 --> 00:14:49,520
What?

318
00:14:49,660 --> 00:14:51,960
This whole father-daughter thing,

319
00:14:52,100 --> 00:14:54,090
we're done,right?

320
00:14:55,030 --> 00:14:57,890
Thursday,coffee at 2.Be on time.

321
00:14:58,110 --> 00:15:01,030
Don't take this the wrong way,but are you dim?

322
00:15:01,240 --> 00:15:05,390
Okay,I didn't exactly love what I found out about you today,

323
00:15:05,540 --> 00:15:10,270
but the goal was to learn,not to judge.

324
00:15:11,660 --> 00:15:13,190
I bring the coffee.

325
00:15:13,310 --> 00:15:17,290
That crap you made burnt a hole in my stomach.

326
00:15:39,450 --> 00:15:41,030
This is tunde.

327
00:15:41,190 --> 00:15:43,860
He lost both his parents to this drought.

328
00:15:43,990 --> 00:15:46,620
In fact,water is always scarce in botswana.

329
00:15:46,770 --> 00:15:49,300
The national currency is called the pula or raindrop...

330
00:15:49,300 --> 00:15:51,590
hello, Gabrielle. What brings you here?

331
00:15:51,740 --> 00:15:54,380
I'm concerned about the drought in Kenya.

332
00:15:54,620 --> 00:15:55,850
Botswana.

333
00:15:55,990 --> 00:15:58,180
Yeah,and you?

334
00:15:58,310 --> 00:16:00,380
Well,I'm organizing this relief trip.

335
00:16:00,520 --> 00:16:02,000
We leave in a week.

336
00:16:02,060 --> 00:16:03,820
Well, Bon voyage,father.

337
00:16:04,070 --> 00:16:05,520
I'm not going myself.

338
00:16:05,670 --> 00:16:07,590
We had to scale back our relief efforts this year.

339
00:16:07,790 --> 00:16:10,040
We even had to cut a few of the aid workers from the trip.

340
00:16:10,180 --> 00:16:13,320
Sister Mary,sister Gret awere so disappointed.

341
00:16:13,880 --> 00:16:15,620
If you just want to hand some of...

342
00:16:15,760 --> 00:16:17,610
sister mary was going on the trip?

343
00:16:17,730 --> 00:16:20,880
Well,sister mary always goes for at least a few months,

344
00:16:21,040 --> 00:16:22,580
but when our funding came up short,

345
00:16:22,720 --> 00:16:24,980
she graciously offered to step aside,

346
00:16:25,120 --> 00:16:28,080
said there's plenty of god's work to do here.

347
00:16:28,270 --> 00:16:29,610
Thank you, Carlos. Appreciate it.

348
00:16:30,820 --> 00:16:33,350
I bet she did.

349
00:16:35,220 --> 00:16:37,820
How much cash are you short,father?

350
00:16:39,170 --> 00:16:42,110
We plan to set up a modern system of irrigation.

351
00:16:42,290 --> 00:16:43,650
I'm sorry to interrupt,sister mary,

352
00:16:43,790 --> 00:16:45,560
but I have an announcement.

353
00:16:45,730 --> 00:16:50,490
I have just received a donation of $8,000,

354
00:16:50,680 --> 00:16:52,790
which means that sister Mary and sister Greta

355
00:16:52,840 --> 00:16:56,150
will be able to join our relief trip to Botswana.

356
00:17:00,390 --> 00:17:05,020
it just goes to show angels are everywhere.

357
00:17:15,490 --> 00:17:18,220
Hey. I'm here to see Lynette Scavo.

358
00:17:18,390 --> 00:17:20,350
Oh,hi. Excuse me. Hi.

359
00:17:20,400 --> 00:17:22,050
I'm lynette.You must be Fran.

360
00:17:22,190 --> 00:17:24,400
Hi. Ed said you needed to talk to me.

361
00:17:24,540 --> 00:17:26,680
I couldn't imagine about what.

362
00:17:26,830 --> 00:17:29,190
Oh,well,come on in my office.

363
00:17:30,580 --> 00:17:33,180
You want me to put my daughter in day care?

364
00:17:33,300 --> 00:17:34,850
But I'm a stay-at-home mom.

365
00:17:35,010 --> 00:17:38,150
I'm not suggesting that you sign her up for all day.

366
00:17:38,260 --> 00:17:41,470
Maybe just a couple of hours in the afternoon.

367
00:17:41,610 --> 00:17:42,810
Wouldn't that be great?

368
00:17:42,960 --> 00:17:46,370
Have some time to yourself, relax, unwind?

369
00:17:46,500 --> 00:17:50,320
I don't need to unwind. I love taking care of little Mindy.

370
00:17:50,450 --> 00:17:53,270
Oh,of course,of course,

371
00:17:53,560 --> 00:17:57,070
but we all have days when we're starting to lose it.

372
00:17:57,240 --> 00:17:59,600
Wouldn't it be nice to have some place to take her

373
00:17:59,730 --> 00:18:02,130
before you want to strangle her?

374
00:18:04,230 --> 00:18:08,200
I cherish every moment I spend with her,truly.

375
00:18:09,010 --> 00:18:10,910
Really?

376
00:18:12,070 --> 00:18:16,060
Yeah. Look,I'm gonna level with you.

377
00:18:16,510 --> 00:18:19,050
Parcher and Murphy can't have a day care center

378
00:18:19,220 --> 00:18:21,370
unless we haveat least 16 kids

379
00:18:21,510 --> 00:18:24,480
and without little Mindy,we only have 15.

380
00:18:25,390 --> 00:18:28,690
Well,that's not my problem.

381
00:18:29,320 --> 00:18:34,540
Okay. Okay. I just thought I'd give it a shot.

382
00:18:35,030 --> 00:18:38,280
Well,I wish I could help you,but I can't.

383
00:18:38,420 --> 00:18:40,540
Okay.

384
00:18:45,200 --> 00:18:46,460
- Lynette   
- Yeah

385
00:18:46,610 --> 00:18:48,880
- Can I ask you something?  
- Yeah

386
00:18:49,190 --> 00:18:53,020
Why did you have kids if you weren't gonna raise them?

387
00:18:53,460 --> 00:18:56,370
Excuse me? Well,I just don't understand who

388
00:18:56,500 --> 00:18:58,150
say they want to be mothers,

389
00:18:58,290 --> 00:19:02,750
but then hand their kids over to glorified babysitters.

390
00:19:03,960 --> 00:19:07,050
I work because my family needs me to.

391
00:19:07,190 --> 00:19:11,330
Oh,dear,I've upset you, and that wasn't my intention.

392
00:19:11,550 --> 00:19:13,510
I bet.

393
00:19:13,900 --> 00:19:16,120
Make no mistake,I'm a good mother.

394
00:19:16,260 --> 00:19:18,790
That's the difference between us--

395
00:19:18,930 --> 00:19:21,120
I couldn't settle for being a good mother.

396
00:19:21,320 --> 00:19:24,380
I want to be a great one.

397
00:19:25,160 --> 00:19:26,450
Bye-bye.

398
00:19:26,580 --> 00:19:28,890
Bye-bye.

399
00:19:44,320 --> 00:19:46,000
Oh,hi,alberta.How are you?

400
00:19:46,200 --> 00:19:48,880
Were you the one that sent out those neighborhood watch pamphlets?

401
00:19:49,000 --> 00:19:52,130
I was wondering if maybe you had any extra copies.

402
00:19:52,480 --> 00:19:57,010
Or I'll just borrow one from somebody else. Thanks.

403
00:20:08,340 --> 00:20:10,580
Yep,looks like carol'spenmanship.

404
00:20:10,720 --> 00:20:13,150
This is ridiculous. What does she think,we're having an affair?

405
00:20:13,290 --> 00:20:15,620
Well,she probably saw you drop me off yesterday,

406
00:20:15,770 --> 00:20:17,160
and she assumed the worst.

407
00:20:17,320 --> 00:20:18,900
Well,now you're gonna have to tell her the truth.

408
00:20:19,030 --> 00:20:21,560
Oh,no,no,no. I'd catch holy hell.

409
00:20:21,690 --> 00:20:23,390
Oh,so you want me to catch it for you?

410
00:20:23,550 --> 00:20:25,280
I mean, you, yourselfs aid she's crazy.

411
00:20:25,410 --> 00:20:28,810
I don't want to wake up tomorrow morning and find my tires slashed.

412
00:20:30,420 --> 00:20:32,790
All right. I'll talk to her.

413
00:20:40,680 --> 00:20:43,670
Hello, Edie. Do you have something you'd like to say?

414
00:20:43,820 --> 00:20:48,430
No. That pretty much says it all.

415
00:21:00,620 --> 00:21:04,190
Sister Mary,what a lovely surprise.

416
00:21:04,310 --> 00:21:06,590
Well,I couldn't leave withoutsaying good-bye, Gabrielle.

417
00:21:06,710 --> 00:21:08,960
Oh,that's so sweet.

418
00:21:09,050 --> 00:21:10,460
I'm really gonna miss you.

419
00:21:10,590 --> 00:21:14,320
I'm sure not half as much as you're gonna miss your husband.

420
00:21:14,470 --> 00:21:17,280
- Huh? 
- Don't freak out.

421
00:21:17,430 --> 00:21:19,470
- I'm going to botswana.  
- What?!

422
00:21:19,610 --> 00:21:21,790
Sister Mary needs a companion.

423
00:21:22,510 --> 00:21:24,110
What happened to sister Greta?!

424
00:21:24,240 --> 00:21:27,040
I was gonna go with sister Greta,but the region is so volatile,

425
00:21:27,190 --> 00:21:30,300
I decided I'd feel much safer with a male companion.

426
00:21:30,440 --> 00:21:31,370
Carlos,you can't do this.

427
00:21:31,490 --> 00:21:34,070
You can't just goto Africa.

428
00:21:34,290 --> 00:21:37,110
Honey,I'm only gonna be gone for two months.

429
00:21:37,300 --> 00:21:39,770
This journey is important for me.

430
00:21:39,860 --> 00:21:42,730
I want to be one of god's soldiers.

431
00:21:43,580 --> 00:21:45,780
And you will be one, Carlos.

432
00:21:45,920 --> 00:21:47,130
After you see the devastation over there,

433
00:21:47,260 --> 00:21:48,640
you're never the same.

434
00:21:48,770 --> 00:21:51,190
You see how selfish your old life is

435
00:21:51,350 --> 00:21:54,710
and you just want to get rid of everything that reminds you of it.

436
00:21:55,170 --> 00:21:58,820
Oh, Gosh. I should get goingand start packing.

437
00:21:58,950 --> 00:22:00,080
We leave in less than a week.

438
00:22:00,200 --> 00:22:02,180
I should probably send a thankyou letter to my parole officer.

439
00:22:02,320 --> 00:22:04,300
He's being a real mensch about this.

440
00:22:09,220 --> 00:22:13,930
I may be a catholic,but I am so not above slapping a nun.

441
00:22:15,430 --> 00:22:17,080
Go ahead.

442
00:22:17,220 --> 00:22:19,060
Do it.

443
00:22:20,100 --> 00:22:24,390
Just make sure you hit hard enough to leave a mark.

444
00:22:26,010 --> 00:22:31,000
Yeah. I didn't think so.

445
00:22:34,370 --> 00:22:36,700
Kiss the kids good night and I'll see themin the morning

446
00:22:36,850 --> 00:22:41,210
Okay,yeah. I love you,too. Bye-bye.

447
00:22:43,190 --> 00:22:44,750
I'm sorry about the day care thing, Lynette,

448
00:22:44,960 --> 00:22:46,980
but Fran hardly ever lets me hold the kid.

449
00:22:47,090 --> 00:22:49,210
You know,since day one,all I ever got was,

450
00:22:49,340 --> 00:22:51,160
"support the head,support the head."

451
00:22:51,280 --> 00:22:54,420
I think I know how to support a damn baby head.

452
00:22:57,400 --> 00:22:59,960
Ohh,let's just--let's just do this.

453
00:23:00,080 --> 00:23:02,270
I don't want to be here all night.

454
00:23:05,320 --> 00:23:07,130
you're Mindy's father.

455
00:23:07,320 --> 00:23:09,790
You have a right to spend time with her.

456
00:23:10,170 --> 00:23:11,850
I know,but what can I do?

457
00:23:12,000 --> 00:23:13,800
You could stand up to Fran.

458
00:23:13,930 --> 00:23:16,300
If you don't,you'll just become more resentful,

459
00:23:16,440 --> 00:23:18,720
she'll get nuttier.

460
00:23:18,890 --> 00:23:20,450
And without a father figure,

461
00:23:20,590 --> 00:23:23,720
poor mindy will grow up to be a stripper.

462
00:23:23,860 --> 00:23:25,120
A stripper?

463
00:23:25,260 --> 00:23:27,920
There's science to back that up.

464
00:23:32,070 --> 00:23:33,310
You know what?

465
00:23:33,470 --> 00:23:35,690
You go ahead and push the button on this day care thing, Lynette,

466
00:23:35,830 --> 00:23:37,950
and count Mindy in.

467
00:23:38,080 --> 00:23:40,280
Yeah,I'll handle Fran.

468
00:23:40,410 --> 00:23:42,700
You're doing the right thing, Ed,

469
00:23:43,000 --> 00:23:45,090
for little Mindy.

470
00:23:52,610 --> 00:23:54,400
yeah.

471
00:23:58,430 --> 00:24:00,700
dude,what if your mom walks in?

472
00:24:00,850 --> 00:24:02,070
She won't.

473
00:24:02,210 --> 00:24:04,040
You don't know that.

474
00:24:04,580 --> 00:24:07,280
Just wait till everybody's asleep.

475
00:24:08,330 --> 00:24:09,860
Seriously.

476
00:24:09,990 --> 00:24:13,710
I'll make it worth your while.

477
00:24:15,290 --> 00:24:17,510
You better.

478
00:24:21,150 --> 00:24:23,380
I wish she would walk in on us,

479
00:24:23,520 --> 00:24:26,960
just to see the expression on her face.

480
00:24:28,230 --> 00:24:31,030
God,I hate her so much.

481
00:24:32,170 --> 00:24:34,410
Still, though,she's your mother.

482
00:24:34,550 --> 00:24:37,630
Don't you sort of have to love her?

483
00:24:38,010 --> 00:24:40,970
Last year,when she found out that I like guys,

484
00:24:41,110 --> 00:24:43,500
she freaked out.

485
00:24:43,630 --> 00:24:48,340
She said that if I didn't change, I'd be going straight to hell,

486
00:24:48,860 --> 00:24:52,040
so since I knew that I couldn't change,

487
00:24:52,170 --> 00:24:53,790
it suddenly hit me that

488
00:24:53,930 --> 00:24:57,720
one day,my own mother was gonna stop loving me,

489
00:24:58,240 --> 00:25:01,770
so I decided to stop loving her first.

490
00:25:01,900 --> 00:25:04,400
That way,it wouldn't hurt so bad.

491
00:25:04,510 --> 00:25:07,150
She didn't know what she was saying.

492
00:25:07,430 --> 00:25:09,550
Yes,she did,

493
00:25:09,970 --> 00:25:12,580
so now she's gotto be punished.

494
00:25:12,770 --> 00:25:15,190
How are you gonna punish her?

495
00:25:15,330 --> 00:25:17,940
One day,she'll slip up,

496
00:25:18,090 --> 00:25:20,740
and I'll have something against her

497
00:25:21,230 --> 00:25:23,500
and when that happens,

498
00:25:24,140 --> 00:25:27,400
I'm gonna take her down so hard,she'll never get back up.

499
00:25:27,450 --> 00:25:30,280
It may take you a while to get something on her.

500
00:25:31,010 --> 00:25:32,570
That's Okay.

501
00:25:32,800 --> 00:25:36,280
I don't mind waiting for the things that I want.

502
00:25:47,260 --> 00:25:49,830
Lynette,hey,hey.Look who's here.

503
00:25:50,000 --> 00:25:51,680
Hey!

504
00:25:51,830 --> 00:25:54,820
You know,the day care room won't be ready until next week at the earliest.

505
00:25:54,970 --> 00:25:57,190
If I had waited,I might have lost my nerve.

506
00:25:57,320 --> 00:25:58,750
I had a window.

507
00:25:58,870 --> 00:26:01,840
Fran was in the shower,so I just grabbed the baby and ran.

508
00:26:02,000 --> 00:26:04,600
You took the baby without telling Fran?

509
00:26:04,730 --> 00:26:07,470
I refuse to be bullied by that woman. You were right.

510
00:26:07,590 --> 00:26:09,990
Mindy is my daughter,I wanted to spend time with her.

511
00:26:10,140 --> 00:26:11,140
I have that right.

512
00:26:11,230 --> 00:26:15,130
Um,Ed,the lobby just called and your wife's on her way up

513
00:26:15,250 --> 00:26:17,170
and she seems pretty angry.

514
00:26:17,260 --> 00:26:18,870
Oh,man.

515
00:26:19,200 --> 00:26:22,060
- Here. Hold mindy.
- Oh.

516
00:26:22,420 --> 00:26:23,560
Let me handle this.

517
00:26:23,690 --> 00:26:25,560
Oh,I was planning to.

518
00:26:30,890 --> 00:26:32,450
I thought Mindy had been kidnapped!

519
00:26:32,570 --> 00:26:33,380
I left a sticky note.

520
00:26:33,510 --> 00:26:35,300
I wasn't looking fora sticky note,ed!

521
00:26:35,450 --> 00:26:37,040
I was looking for my missing child!

522
00:26:37,170 --> 00:26:39,270
She's my child,too,and she's staying here,

523
00:26:39,410 --> 00:26:41,030
just a few hours a day.

524
00:26:41,170 --> 00:26:44,250
- You,give her to me. 
- No,I made a decision.

525
00:26:44,380 --> 00:26:47,130
Yeah? Okay,watch me make a decision.

526
00:26:47,280 --> 00:26:48,520
I'm done with this marriage.

527
00:26:48,640 --> 00:26:50,960
I'm taking my baby and I'm getting on a plane to pittsburgh.

528
00:26:51,030 --> 00:26:53,490
- You wouldn't dare! 
- You think you miss mindy now,

529
00:26:53,630 --> 00:26:55,510
wait till we're livingwith my mother!

530
00:26:55,650 --> 00:26:56,890
- I'll fight you on this.
- Yeah? Try...

531
00:26:57,010 --> 00:27:02,290
as Lynette saw her dreams of day care about to board a plane to pittsburgh,

532
00:27:02,460 --> 00:27:04,980
- You're crazy,you know that?! 
- Yeah! I'm crazy to think...

533
00:27:05,130 --> 00:27:09,580
she decided this flight would have to be grounded.

534
00:27:09,710 --> 00:27:11,110
You don't scare me.

535
00:27:11,190 --> 00:27:12,590
Oh. Oh!

536
00:27:12,720 --> 00:27:14,350
What the hell is she doing?!

537
00:27:14,500 --> 00:27:15,780
Open up! Give me my baby!

538
00:27:15,920 --> 00:27:17,980
- Good thinking,lynette! 
- I am not on your side,ed

539
00:27:18,120 --> 00:27:20,650
- You're not? 
- No,I am on mindy's side.

540
00:27:20,760 --> 00:27:22,290
She is the one caught in the middle,

541
00:27:22,440 --> 00:27:25,470
and I'm not letting you two have her until you calm down.

542
00:27:25,610 --> 00:27:27,650
I want my damn child.

543
00:27:27,780 --> 00:27:30,310
Lynette,I have tom on line two.

544
00:27:30,450 --> 00:27:33,380
Pat, can you see here I'm holding a baby hostage?!

545
00:27:33,530 --> 00:27:35,620
I will call back!

546
00:27:35,770 --> 00:27:37,110
All right,that's it.

547
00:27:37,250 --> 00:27:39,480
- I'm calling the police. 
- Oh,for god's sakes!

548
00:27:39,610 --> 00:27:40,940
Lynette'snot going to hurt the baby!

549
00:27:41,060 --> 00:27:43,350
No,and you're gonna get herback a whole lot faster

550
00:27:43,470 --> 00:27:46,140
if you will just listen to me,okay?

551
00:27:46,270 --> 00:27:48,980
Listen,and you?All right,good.

552
00:27:49,120 --> 00:27:53,250
So first of all, Ed,stealing the baby was really stupid.

553
00:27:53,380 --> 00:27:54,640
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.

554
00:27:54,770 --> 00:27:57,960
You need to find a better way to communicate with your wife.

555
00:27:58,100 --> 00:28:01,650
And, Fran,I know what the pressure of trying to be

556
00:28:01,780 --> 00:28:03,740
a super parent does to your head.

557
00:28:03,890 --> 00:28:07,360
You can take a break and be a great mom.

558
00:28:07,500 --> 00:28:13,180
Doesn't this little sweetheart deserve a well-rested mommy?

559
00:28:15,500 --> 00:28:18,910
Well,I guess the pressure does get to me a little.

560
00:28:19,050 --> 00:28:21,280
And it's Okay to admit that.

561
00:28:21,430 --> 00:28:26,090
This is communication. This is good.

562
00:28:26,240 --> 00:28:28,550
Why don't you guys go down to the lobby,

563
00:28:28,700 --> 00:28:30,870
talk it out over some coffee?

564
00:28:31,000 --> 00:28:33,380
Uh,what about Mindy?

565
00:28:33,520 --> 00:28:36,000
We've got day care!

566
00:28:40,120 --> 00:28:43,070
We've got day care

567
00:29:03,230 --> 00:29:04,490
Hi.

568
00:29:04,630 --> 00:29:07,090
I called earlier from the spiritual outreach program?

569
00:29:07,240 --> 00:29:09,440
Hi. Piano player,right?

570
00:29:09,590 --> 00:29:11,810
This is so generous of you.

571
00:29:11,960 --> 00:29:13,340
There it is.

572
00:29:13,460 --> 00:29:16,240
It's not exactly a concert grand.

573
00:29:16,390 --> 00:29:17,710
I should warn you,

574
00:29:17,900 --> 00:29:20,730
on the whole,our patients are generally unresponsive,

575
00:29:20,850 --> 00:29:23,770
so I hope you don't expect a lot of clapping.

576
00:29:24,450 --> 00:29:29,180
Miss Delaney, I find when the spiritual rewards are this great,

577
00:29:29,320 --> 00:29:31,890
who needs applause?

578
00:29:32,220 --> 00:29:34,060
Excuse me.

579
00:30:01,330 --> 00:30:04,300
Did Addison talk to you about me?

580
00:30:04,890 --> 00:30:07,430
Oh!I guess not.

581
00:30:07,560 --> 00:30:09,140
He's a married man!

582
00:30:09,280 --> 00:30:11,210
- What's wrong with you?!
- No,wait! Wait!

583
00:30:11,340 --> 00:30:15,140
- It's not what you think! 
- He hasn't touched me for three years

584
00:30:15,260 --> 00:30:17,590
because of sluts like you!

585
00:30:17,790 --> 00:30:20,630
Carol, if you would just stop throwing things at me, I'll explain!

586
00:30:20,750 --> 00:30:23,060
How--how can you explain?!

587
00:30:23,200 --> 00:30:26,050
You're screwing my husband! No, I'm not screwing him!

588
00:30:26,180 --> 00:30:28,990
He's my father!

589
00:30:32,990 --> 00:30:34,890
I'm so sorry.

590
00:30:35,020 --> 00:30:38,180
I thought you should know, but he didn't want to tell you.

591
00:30:38,900 --> 00:30:40,660
I want to die.

592
00:30:40,800 --> 00:30:42,450
- Oh,no.
- I do.

593
00:30:42,590 --> 00:30:43,760
Oh, Carol, you don't have to clean that up.

594
00:30:43,890 --> 00:30:46,100
They have clerks for that.

595
00:30:46,930 --> 00:30:48,390
How old are you?

596
00:30:48,510 --> 00:30:50,270
38.

597
00:30:52,360 --> 00:30:54,880
We've been married 39 years.

598
00:30:55,020 --> 00:30:57,890
It's been going on from the start.

599
00:30:58,420 --> 00:31:00,660
Believe me, I didn't want to hurt anyone. I just

600
00:31:00,800 --> 00:31:03,210
wanted to find my dad.

601
00:31:04,140 --> 00:31:05,990
I'm glad you did,

602
00:31:06,120 --> 00:31:08,680
but you be careful,sweetheart.

603
00:31:09,680 --> 00:31:13,080
He's gonna break your heart.

604
00:31:22,450 --> 00:31:26,950
Andrew,I made an appointment with a therapist for you, me and Danielle.

605
00:31:27,080 --> 00:31:28,070
I don't think so.

606
00:31:28,220 --> 00:31:31,430
This pain that you're feeling is completely natural,

607
00:31:31,570 --> 00:31:34,400
but it's not gonna go away until you deal with it.

608
00:31:34,550 --> 00:31:36,250
Andrew,

609
00:31:36,440 --> 00:31:39,630
I want us to heal,I want us to be a family again.

610
00:31:39,770 --> 00:31:41,620
You know what I want?

611
00:31:41,770 --> 00:31:44,740
I want for George Williams to walk through that door

612
00:31:44,870 --> 00:31:48,960
so I can take a knife and plunge it into his heart.

613
00:31:49,090 --> 00:31:51,430
I want the pharmacist to pay for what he did to my father.

614
00:31:51,540 --> 00:31:54,850
Well,the good news is he's...he's dead.

615
00:31:54,980 --> 00:31:57,050
He committed suicide.

616
00:31:57,180 --> 00:31:58,990
His death was on his terms.

617
00:31:59,120 --> 00:32:01,480
That's not justice.

618
00:32:01,610 --> 00:32:04,230
So are you saying if he were

619
00:32:04,380 --> 00:32:08,400
executed that it would be easier for you to get past this?

620
00:32:08,560 --> 00:32:10,670
Of course.

621
00:32:20,360 --> 00:32:23,500
George...

622
00:32:23,650 --> 00:32:27,790
didn't intend to commit suicide.

623
00:32:29,930 --> 00:32:33,280
He was trying to manipulate meinto taking him back,

624
00:32:34,550 --> 00:32:39,250
and he swallowed those pills hoping that I'd feel sorry for him.

625
00:32:39,510 --> 00:32:43,630
He just assumed that I would call an ambulance.

626
00:32:43,770 --> 00:32:48,040
When I got there,he was already slipping away.

627
00:32:49,110 --> 00:32:50,800
I tried to get him to

628
00:32:50,920 --> 00:32:54,480
accept responsibility for what he'd done...

629
00:32:57,060 --> 00:32:58,590
but he wouldn't.

630
00:32:59,450 --> 00:33:02,140
So what'd you do?

631
00:33:02,630 --> 00:33:05,620
Nothing.

632
00:33:07,350 --> 00:33:12,080
I just sat there and let him die.

633
00:33:12,870 --> 00:33:15,540
Oh,my god.

634
00:33:16,200 --> 00:33:20,020
He didn't die on his terms,andrew.

635
00:33:20,650 --> 00:33:24,100
He paid for what he did to your father.

636
00:33:29,920 --> 00:33:33,070
Thank you for telling me this.

637
00:34:00,860 --> 00:34:03,490
Hey, how you doin'?

638
00:35:25,800 --> 00:35:26,770
Yeah?

639
00:35:26,900 --> 00:35:28,450
Zach's come home.

640
00:35:28,560 --> 00:35:29,930
What?

641
00:35:30,310 --> 00:35:32,560
- Is he okay? 
- He's fine.

642
00:35:32,710 --> 00:35:34,110
Is there anything I can do?

643
00:35:34,240 --> 00:35:35,560
Thanks for asking.

644
00:35:35,690 --> 00:35:38,300
You can leave us alone.

645
00:35:39,050 --> 00:35:41,210
I spent a lot of time looking for zach,

646
00:35:41,350 --> 00:35:44,360
- and you know why. 
- Maybe I'm notmaking myself clear.

647
00:35:44,510 --> 00:35:46,640
You come near my son, I'll go to the police.

648
00:35:46,780 --> 00:35:49,350
I'll tell them what happened out in that quarry.

649
00:35:49,490 --> 00:35:51,510
You do that and we'll both go down.

650
00:35:51,660 --> 00:35:52,830
Well,

651
00:35:52,990 --> 00:35:56,890
you know I'm capable of almost anything.

652
00:35:57,310 --> 00:35:58,910
Hey,I thought you'd like to know

653
00:35:59,070 --> 00:36:00,900
zach and I are moving away.

654
00:36:01,040 --> 00:36:03,640
I want to give my son a shot at a normal life.

655
00:36:03,790 --> 00:36:06,060
I'm sure you'll agree it's for the best.

656
00:36:06,210 --> 00:36:08,980
Now see, this is where you and I don't see eye-to-eye.

657
00:36:09,180 --> 00:36:12,810
For zach's sake, I'll keep quiet, for now,

658
00:36:12,960 --> 00:36:14,650
but you're not taking him away.

659
00:36:14,800 --> 00:36:16,910
If I see a "for sale" sign in front of that house,

660
00:36:17,060 --> 00:36:19,740
I'll call the police.

661
00:36:20,250 --> 00:36:24,100
I'm capable of pretty much anything myself.

662
00:36:34,280 --> 00:36:36,380
the doctor's going to give you a full work-up,

663
00:36:36,510 --> 00:36:38,120
then we'll start the inoculations.

664
00:36:38,260 --> 00:36:39,350
Make sure you fill out everything

665
00:36:39,490 --> 00:36:42,140
- and the nurse will take you back.
- Thank you.

666
00:36:43,290 --> 00:36:46,260
Boy,Sister Mary's done a number on you.

667
00:36:46,420 --> 00:36:48,810
- Right. 
- Yes,right.

668
00:36:48,940 --> 00:36:51,420
She has you flying halfway across the world to help the poor

669
00:36:51,560 --> 00:36:54,050
and there'sperfectly good poor right here.

670
00:36:54,180 --> 00:36:56,460
For god's sakes, give a buck to a homeless guy.

671
00:36:56,590 --> 00:36:58,620
- It's not the same. 
- No,it's better

672
00:36:58,740 --> 00:37:00,570
because you can do it in the comfort of your own car.

673
00:37:00,710 --> 00:37:03,150
The point is not to be comfortable,gaby.

674
00:37:03,290 --> 00:37:05,770
It's about easing pain and suffering.

675
00:37:05,930 --> 00:37:08,310
Look,I'm trying to bea better person here.

676
00:37:08,450 --> 00:37:10,850
Now you can either help meor you can get out of the way,

677
00:37:10,980 --> 00:37:13,420
but you can't stop me.

678
00:37:13,570 --> 00:37:16,020
Carlos Solis?

679
00:37:16,170 --> 00:37:18,150
Come with me,please.

680
00:37:18,260 --> 00:37:20,420
Finish that for me.

681
00:37:26,480 --> 00:37:28,040
here.

682
00:37:28,170 --> 00:37:30,340
He didn't fill out the allergy section.

683
00:37:30,480 --> 00:37:32,800
Honey,he's going to a remote village in africa.

684
00:37:33,120 --> 00:37:35,300
Does it really matter that he's allergic to eggs?

685
00:37:35,440 --> 00:37:37,580
Actually,yes.Eggs are on the list.

686
00:37:37,690 --> 00:37:40,930
He could have a severe reaction to the yellow fever vaccine,

687
00:37:41,080 --> 00:37:44,390
and he won't be getting out of bed,let alone leaving the country.

688
00:37:44,540 --> 00:37:46,510
Really?

689
00:37:47,200 --> 00:37:48,400
Oh,don't write that down.

690
00:37:48,530 --> 00:37:51,000
I wasn't being specific.

691
00:37:51,140 --> 00:37:53,330
He's allergic to fish eggs.

692
00:37:53,430 --> 00:37:54,870
Fish eggs?

693
00:37:55,030 --> 00:37:57,410
Poor baby's gone his whole life without caviar.

694
00:37:57,560 --> 00:37:59,360
Now that's suffering.

695
00:38:01,430 --> 00:38:04,730
All right, doc,give me all you got.

696
00:38:09,690 --> 00:38:11,720
It's so hot in this village.

697
00:38:11,870 --> 00:38:14,470
Baby,that's the fever talking.

698
00:38:14,600 --> 00:38:16,660
The doctor said you're having an allergic reaction,

699
00:38:16,810 --> 00:38:19,270
but you're gonna be fine,okay?

700
00:38:19,400 --> 00:38:21,330
Hold me.

701
00:38:21,480 --> 00:38:26,390
Ohh,honey. I'm so sorry.

702
00:38:27,440 --> 00:38:30,900
Ohh,maybe that stupid nun is right.

703
00:38:31,040 --> 00:38:34,720
Maybe I am trying to stop you from becoming a better person.

704
00:38:34,870 --> 00:38:38,340
It's just that I love you the way you are--

705
00:38:39,150 --> 00:38:42,840
greedy, selfish and insensitive.

706
00:38:42,990 --> 00:38:45,210
I'm just scared if you're not those things anymore,

707
00:38:45,350 --> 00:38:47,160
you're gonna wake up one day

708
00:38:47,290 --> 00:38:49,880
and realize I still am,

709
00:38:51,320 --> 00:38:53,320
and then you won't want me.

710
00:38:53,470 --> 00:38:56,250
I want you. Just hold me.

711
00:38:58,800 --> 00:39:01,200
Ohh,Carlos.

712
00:39:02,490 --> 00:39:05,470
Hold me...

713
00:39:07,490 --> 00:39:10,360
Sister Mary.

714
00:39:16,670 --> 00:39:18,510
Painting in the rain?

715
00:39:18,720 --> 00:39:19,850
Is that smart?

716
00:39:19,980 --> 00:39:21,540
Well,let me see,painting in the rain

717
00:39:21,680 --> 00:39:23,630
or letting the whole world think I'm a whore?

718
00:39:23,780 --> 00:39:25,970
I don't know.What do you think?

719
00:39:26,320 --> 00:39:28,330
Heard you ran into my wife.

720
00:39:28,460 --> 00:39:29,870
Yep.

721
00:39:30,020 --> 00:39:31,450
So?

722
00:39:31,590 --> 00:39:36,840
So you are hereby released of any further obligation to be my dad.

723
00:39:37,500 --> 00:39:38,700
Okay.

724
00:39:38,830 --> 00:39:40,730
Just so you know,

725
00:39:40,860 --> 00:39:44,540
I'm not actually proud of what I've done

726
00:39:44,680 --> 00:39:46,450
you know, my hobbies.

727
00:39:46,590 --> 00:39:48,650
Good for you.

728
00:39:48,820 --> 00:39:51,000
Bye.

729
00:39:51,390 --> 00:39:53,370
I have done things I'm proud of.

730
00:39:53,540 --> 00:39:57,010
I could give you five examples right now.

731
00:39:57,420 --> 00:39:59,830
Okay,maybe three.

732
00:40:01,100 --> 00:40:03,520
You don't have to do this.

733
00:40:04,400 --> 00:40:06,090
I was a volunteer fireman.

734
00:40:06,240 --> 00:40:10,790
I put out fires,I got kittens out of trees,the whole nine yards.

735
00:40:10,940 --> 00:40:13,260
Sweet.

736
00:40:13,570 --> 00:40:17,770
About 20 years ago,I started a foundation to

737
00:40:17,910 --> 00:40:20,680
protect wild horses. I probably saved hundreds of them.

738
00:40:20,820 --> 00:40:22,830
Really?

739
00:40:22,980 --> 00:40:25,960
I'm full of surprises.

740
00:40:27,170 --> 00:40:31,000
Okay,one more.

741
00:40:31,840 --> 00:40:36,600
I wasn't exactly thrilled when you walked back into my life.

742
00:40:36,770 --> 00:40:38,520
Now that I've met you,

743
00:40:39,790 --> 00:40:43,990
well,you gave me a third thing to be proud of.

744
00:40:44,650 --> 00:40:46,290
That was a good one.

745
00:40:47,110 --> 00:40:50,140
That's why I saved it for last.

746
00:40:53,040 --> 00:40:55,620
I have to spend some time working on my marriage.

747
00:40:55,770 --> 00:40:57,320
When that's all sorted out,

748
00:40:57,450 --> 00:41:00,400
maybe we could continue with the

749
00:41:00,570 --> 00:41:02,770
catching up?

750
00:41:05,540 --> 00:41:08,710
I'll wait for your call.

751
00:41:17,260 --> 00:41:22,200
The stories are as old as time itself...

752
00:41:22,650 --> 00:41:25,180
the prodigal son who returns home

753
00:41:25,320 --> 00:41:29,540
to the father who forgives him...

754
00:41:30,250 --> 00:41:36,610
the jealous wife who tricks the husband who trust her...

755
00:41:38,280 --> 00:41:39,900
the desperate mother

756
00:41:40,030 --> 00:41:45,030
who risks everything for the child who needs her

757
00:41:46,030 --> 00:41:48,060
and the faithless husband

758
00:41:48,190 --> 00:41:52,760
who hurts the wife who loves him so deeply.

759
00:41:54,080 --> 00:41:57,580
Why do we listen again and again?

760
00:41:57,720 --> 00:42:00,900
Because these are the stories of family,

761
00:42:01,040 --> 00:42:06,780
and once we look past the fighting, pain and the resentment,

762
00:42:07,170 --> 00:42:11,490
we occasionally like to remind ourselves...

763
00:42:11,950 --> 00:42:18,000
There is absolutely nothing more important.

764
00:42:18,150 --> 00:42:20,000
Hi, bunny, bunny. Hi.

765
00:42:20,070 --> 00:42:21,990
--------------------------  
www.ydy.com/bbs 
Proudly Presents 
--------------------------

