1
00:00:02,720 --> 00:00:04,840
Scotch.

2
00:00:04,900 --> 00:00:06,380
That's what we're missing.

3
00:00:06,500 --> 00:00:11,860
The smooth,
smoky flavor of a single barrel scotch

4
00:00:11,960 --> 00:00:14,710
with a juicy porterhouse.

5
00:00:20,370 --> 00:00:23,570
I was really hoping you'd
get your appetite back.

6
00:00:23,760 --> 00:00:25,940
You're gonna need to eat.

7
00:00:26,240 --> 00:00:28,990
You're gonna need your strength.

8
00:00:50,760 --> 00:00:52,250
What?

9
00:00:52,730 --> 00:00:54,790
We've only been here an hour.
You've made 2 calls.

10
00:00:54,810 --> 00:00:55,950
And?

11
00:00:55,970 --> 00:00:57,240
You hate the phone,elle.

12
00:00:57,330 --> 00:00:58,330
I don't hate the phone.

13
00:00:58,360 --> 00:00:59,830
Actually,you do.

14
00:00:59,860 --> 00:01:02,090
Did you know that alexander
graham bell and eli gray

15
00:01:02,140 --> 00:01:05,180
simultaneously invented
electronic sound transmission devices?

16
00:01:05,210 --> 00:01:06,760
It came down to a race betwixt the two.

17
00:01:06,790 --> 00:01:11,200
Yeah,and bell beat gray to the
patent office by a matter of hours.

18
00:01:11,400 --> 00:01:13,310
Common knowledge.

19
00:01:13,450 --> 00:01:15,220
Why are you acting so weird?

20
00:01:16,580 --> 00:01:21,080
We're sitting with a guy who knows that there
are 800 kernels of corn on the average cob...

21
00:01:21,120 --> 00:01:22,870
arranged in 16 separate rows.

22
00:01:22,910 --> 00:01:24,710
And you're calling me weird?

23
00:01:24,820 --> 00:01:27,160
(缺一句)I knew it.You got a boyfriend.

24
00:01:27,200 --> 00:01:29,720
You are basing this on what exactly,
that I don't like the phone?

25
00:01:29,740 --> 00:01:31,510
(缺一句)

26
00:01:31,540 --> 00:01:35,320
You've been a profiler for how long,
derek,and that's--that's weak.

27
00:01:35,550 --> 00:01:36,270
What's weak?

28
00:01:36,290 --> 00:01:37,960
Morgan thinks elle has a boyfriend.

29
00:01:38,080 --> 00:01:39,560
(前面还有)You just denied it.

30
00:01:39,600 --> 00:01:40,330
Do you?

31
00:01:40,370 --> 00:01:41,790
It's more fun not to answer that question.

32
00:01:41,830 --> 00:01:43,560
That right there is a yes,baby.

33
00:01:43,580 --> 00:01:45,120
I knew it. I told you.

34
00:01:45,160 --> 00:01:46,810
She doesn't want to admit to anything,man.

35
00:01:46,840 --> 00:01:49,440
Reid,trust me.You've got a lot to learn.

36
00:01:49,470 --> 00:01:51,900
Fbi tampa has been investigating
a series of murders

37
00:01:51,940 --> 00:01:54,580
over the past 2 monthsalong
florida's central golf coast.

38
00:01:54,670 --> 00:01:56,990
I consulted with the sac down there.
They had a strong lead.

39
00:01:57,000 --> 00:01:58,730
And dna evidence.

40
00:01:58,760 --> 00:02:01,130
All 4 women were killed by this man--

41
00:02:01,250 --> 00:02:02,380
mark gregory.

42
00:02:02,400 --> 00:02:06,330
If they know who he is,he's not really an unsub.
Why are they calling us?

43
00:02:06,370 --> 00:02:08,850
They weren't able to arrest him before he disappeared.

44
00:02:08,870 --> 00:02:11,040
They let a serial killer get away?

45
00:02:11,080 --> 00:02:12,190
How long has he been missing?

46
00:02:12,210 --> 00:02:15,080
About 36 hours,along with this woman--

47
00:02:15,350 --> 00:02:17,210
nicole wegener.

48
00:02:17,220 --> 00:02:18,630
What do we know about the other victims?

49
00:02:18,660 --> 00:02:21,520
They were all abducted within a 60-mile radius,

50
00:02:21,540 --> 00:02:25,480
tortured and then drowned in hotel bathtubs.

51
00:02:25,590 --> 00:02:28,900
They were all found a couple of
days after they were reported missing.

52
00:02:28,930 --> 00:02:32,720
Same geographical area, and he's killing in hotels
instead of private, controlled environments.

53
00:02:32,760 --> 00:02:35,050
He can pay for privacy in a hotel room.

54
00:02:35,060 --> 00:02:36,870
Let's just hope he's not heading for orlando.

55
00:02:36,900 --> 00:02:39,950
It's second only to las vegas
in the number of hotel rooms.

56
00:02:39,950 --> 00:02:41,960
Well,knowing who he is is
certainly part of the equation,

57
00:02:42,060 --> 00:02:44,010
but it's a long way from knowing where he is.

58
00:02:44,020 --> 00:02:47,460
A serial killer who's been sussed out
and is on the loose,he's got 2 choices.

59
00:02:47,560 --> 00:02:50,770
He's either hiding or,worse,he's on the run.

60
00:02:50,800 --> 00:02:53,170
And if gregory feels like he's got nothing to lose...

61
00:02:53,190 --> 00:02:56,240
he's got the whole country ahead of him.

62
00:02:59,320 --> 00:03:09,000
<font color=#38B0DE>-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents</font>

63
00:03:09,100 --> 00:03:15,000
<font color=#38B0DE>Sync:YTET-Wk120 Gagegao
-==www.ydy.com/bbs==-</font>

64
00:03:15,100 --> 00:03:21,000
Crimial Minds
Season 01 Episode 20

65
00:03:21,100 --> 00:03:30,580
<font color=#38B0DE>-=http://sfile.ydy.com/bbs/index.php=-</font>

1
00:03:32,730 --> 00:03:34,940
The french philosopher voltaire wrote,

2
00:03:34,940 --> 00:03:37,290
"there are some that only employ words

3
00:03:37,290 --> 00:03:39,990
for the purpose of disguising their thoughts."

4
00:03:40,400 --> 00:03:43,380
This is everything the tampa office 
has on mark gregory.

5
00:03:43,380 --> 00:03:46,500
He's a single white man,38 years old.

6
00:03:46,500 --> 00:03:48,520
Graduated from fsu.

7
00:03:48,520 --> 00:03:52,390
Started his own real estate company 
with a business partner 5 years ago.

8
00:03:52,760 --> 00:03:55,190
He frequently travels for work around the country,

9
00:03:55,190 --> 00:03:57,030
sometimes overseas.

10
00:03:57,030 --> 00:04:01,200
Just last year he purchased a very 
lavish home in sarasota.

11
00:04:01,200 --> 00:04:02,980
What was he doing before he got into real estate?

12
00:04:02,980 --> 00:04:05,930
It says he raced cars after college,

13
00:04:06,270 --> 00:04:09,800
even worked as a chef at a french restaurant.
Jack of all trades.

15
00:04:09,800 --> 00:04:11,570
Yeah,he's plenty mastered.

16
00:04:11,570 --> 00:04:13,900
He worked as a staff photographer 
for a couple of magazines

17
00:04:13,900 --> 00:04:17,750
along the central coast before 
transitioning to work with models in miami.

18
00:04:17,750 --> 00:04:21,520
It's strange so many serial killers 
make a hobby of photography.

19
00:04:21,520 --> 00:04:24,120
It must have something to do with 
the act of voyeurism.

20
00:04:24,120 --> 00:04:25,990
What about his bank accounts and credit cards?

21
00:04:25,990 --> 00:04:29,040
They seized everything after he 
disappeared 36 hours ago.

22
00:04:29,040 --> 00:04:33,640
So when he uses his credit cards or 
goes to his house or work,then they've got him.

24
00:04:33,640 --> 00:04:36,360
I heard enough about mark gregory.
I wanna hear about his victims.

25
00:04:36,360 --> 00:04:39,390
Gregory used different forms of torture with each one.

26
00:04:39,390 --> 00:04:41,780
Choking,burning,suspension,and beating.

27
00:04:41,780 --> 00:04:43,280
Drowning was the only constant.

28
00:04:43,280 --> 00:04:45,890
They were all classified as 
"wet drownings,"which means

29
00:04:45,890 --> 00:04:48,530
the victim was alive when they were submerged.

30
00:04:48,530 --> 00:04:51,530
They could feel their lungs filling up with water.

31
00:04:51,530 --> 00:04:53,330
It's an extremely painful way to die.

32
00:04:53,330 --> 00:04:57,130
Why would he take the time?
They were barely alive after all the torture.

34
00:04:57,130 --> 00:05:00,560
Drowning's a form of torture,too,
and it's all part of the signature.

35
00:05:00,980 --> 00:05:02,720
Ssa raymond mccarthy.

36
00:05:02,720 --> 00:05:04,930
Ssa jason gideon. We spoke on the phone.

37
00:05:04,930 --> 00:05:08,340
Sorry for the temporary setup.
We wanted you closer to where mark gregory lives.

39
00:05:08,940 --> 00:05:10,070
Please continue.

40
00:05:10,070 --> 00:05:12,830
We were just discussing drowning 
as a cleansing ritual.

41
00:05:12,830 --> 00:05:16,150
If we look back into gregory's childhood,
we may find what he needs to purge.

42
00:05:16,150 --> 00:05:19,990
You think that's the best use of our time?We're 
itching to find this guy.He got away on our watch.

44
00:05:20,080 --> 00:05:24,100
By studying his behavior as a child,
it helps us understand why he does what he does.

46
00:05:24,100 --> 00:05:26,510
You know everything about this 
killer except why he does it.

47
00:05:26,510 --> 00:05:29,300
So the further we go back,the further ahead of him we might get.

48
00:05:29,300 --> 00:05:31,690
Were you able to connect gregory to all 4 victims?

49
00:05:31,690 --> 00:05:34,280
He had a previous relationship 
with the first woman he killed.

50
00:05:34,280 --> 00:05:36,370
We can look into that as the possible stressor.

51
00:05:36,370 --> 00:05:40,100
The second and third were acquaintances from business deals.
The fourth worked at a restaurant the same time he did.

53
00:05:40,100 --> 00:05:42,060
What's his connection to the missing girl?

54
00:05:42,060 --> 00:05:45,160
We can't find anything.
Gregory's big news in florida.

56
00:05:45,160 --> 00:05:47,950
When do we hold a press conference 
to alert the entire country?

57
00:05:47,950 --> 00:05:50,400
Hopefully we'll find gregory before we have to.

58
00:05:50,400 --> 00:05:52,920
So if we split up,we'll cover more ground.

59
00:05:53,300 --> 00:05:55,490
Does he still have family in the area?

60
00:05:55,490 --> 00:05:57,120
His dad's close by.

61
00:05:57,120 --> 00:05:59,680
Why don't we start from the present 
and work our way backwards.

62
00:06:00,510 --> 00:06:02,290
Reid and I will go to gregory's house.

63
00:06:02,290 --> 00:06:05,090
Elle and I will talk with business partner,
hank bloomberg.

64
00:06:05,090 --> 00:06:06,970
I'll comb through some of the evidence here.

65
00:06:06,970 --> 00:06:09,060
Garcia's gonna want an update.
I'll catch up with her.

66
00:06:09,060 --> 00:06:10,390
Good. Let's meet back here in 2 hours.

67
00:06:10,390 --> 00:06:14,660
If he's following his previous pattern,we have 
less than 12 hours to find nicole wegener alive.

69
00:06:14,660 --> 00:06:16,110
Mr. Bloomberg.

70
00:06:16,110 --> 00:06:18,210
- Yes.
- Agents hotchner and greenaway,fbi.

72
00:06:18,800 --> 00:06:19,990
I've already talked to the police.

73
00:06:19,990 --> 00:06:23,650
We're from the behavioral analysis unit,
and I'm sure we'll have some different questions.

75
00:06:23,650 --> 00:06:27,310
We're looking for some insight into mark gregory's
behavior right before the killing started.

76
00:06:27,310 --> 00:06:29,910
Things you might not think are important 
could actually be helpful.

77
00:06:29,910 --> 00:06:32,690
I don't know why he disappeared. 
You sure you've got the right guy?

78
00:06:32,690 --> 00:06:36,200
Usually when someone takes off,
it gives us reason to be suspicious.

79
00:06:36,900 --> 00:06:39,440
Well,I've never noticed any odd behavior.

80
00:06:39,440 --> 00:06:42,860
We've worked together for 5 years.
I've known him for 10.

81
00:06:43,920 --> 00:06:47,920
He helped coach my son's soccer 
league this past fall.He's my best friend.

82
00:06:47,920 --> 00:06:50,020
What about his relationship with women?

83
00:06:50,790 --> 00:06:52,530
Mark's the consummate ladies man.

84
00:06:52,530 --> 00:06:55,390
He always had a different woman on his arm.
Never had a problem getting a date.

85
00:06:55,390 --> 00:06:58,990
Dating doesn't do it for him.
He likes to torture and drown them.

86
00:06:59,220 --> 00:07:01,270
What do you know about his history with women?

87
00:07:01,980 --> 00:07:04,760
He was married once in his early 20s.
Swore he'd never do it again.

88
00:07:05,050 --> 00:07:06,270
Did you know her?

89
00:07:06,890 --> 00:07:08,780
No. It was before I met him.

90
00:07:09,560 --> 00:07:11,270
Do you know if she's still in the area?

91
00:07:12,670 --> 00:07:14,900
Wait a minute.You think he 
did something to his ex-wife?

92
00:07:14,900 --> 00:07:17,260
We're looking for what we call a "stressor,"

93
00:07:17,510 --> 00:07:19,890
what could have made him lose it.

94
00:07:19,890 --> 00:07:22,300
We have to look into all the possibilities.

95
00:07:22,300 --> 00:07:24,710
If we need to ask you any more questions,
we'll find you.

96
00:07:24,710 --> 00:07:26,190
Thank you.

97
00:07:29,070 --> 00:07:32,410
I bet gregory's been killing a lot longer 
than we think,long before he disappeared.

98
00:07:35,190 --> 00:07:38,000
This is a really large house 
with hardly any furniture.

99
00:07:38,000 --> 00:07:39,910
Typical bachelor pad.

100
00:07:40,710 --> 00:07:42,950
Large sofa,big-screen tv,

101
00:07:43,340 --> 00:07:44,750
white walls.

102
00:07:44,750 --> 00:07:48,300
I noticed a luxury car in the garage,
but it's at least 10 years old.

103
00:07:48,300 --> 00:07:50,200
Where are the dogs?

104
00:07:55,250 --> 00:07:57,380
Gideon,check this out.

105
00:07:58,040 --> 00:08:01,120
This guy's got,like,20 different suits.

106
00:08:01,340 --> 00:08:05,780
Some italian. Some taylor.Some leisure suits.

107
00:08:07,280 --> 00:08:09,260
He's got a mechanic's uniform.

108
00:08:10,790 --> 00:08:13,510
Wide assortment of watches and wallets.

109
00:08:13,510 --> 00:08:16,330
Approximately 20 different pairs of shoes.

110
00:08:16,330 --> 00:08:18,550
Take a look at all these driver licenses.

111
00:08:18,550 --> 00:08:20,670
He can start his own dmv.

112
00:08:21,050 --> 00:08:22,990
Feed those to garcia.

113
00:08:24,120 --> 00:08:25,940
Travels around the country

114
00:08:26,370 --> 00:08:29,290
to buy and sell different properties.

115
00:08:29,290 --> 00:08:32,070
Probably reinvents himself with each deal he makes.

116
00:08:32,070 --> 00:08:34,520
Plays a different role.

117
00:08:34,780 --> 00:08:37,070
Dresses up to impress a rich investor

118
00:08:38,000 --> 00:08:40,360
and dresses down for a poor farmer.

119
00:08:40,360 --> 00:08:44,580
This guy's a chameleon.He can adapt 
to any situation.

120
00:08:46,690 --> 00:08:49,090
From the outside,this house seems clean and shiny.

121
00:08:49,090 --> 00:08:53,640
But it's like all for show,like it's a 
facade to hide what's really going on.

122
00:09:00,910 --> 00:09:02,950
Drawerful of catalogs.

123
00:09:03,430 --> 00:09:08,180
Uniforms for law enforcement,construction,
janitorial,military.

124
00:09:09,340 --> 00:09:11,080
What do you think he needs these for?

125
00:09:11,080 --> 00:09:13,590
Probably has something to do with this.

126
00:09:14,300 --> 00:09:17,040
Someone's trying to disguise himself.

127
00:09:45,960 --> 00:09:47,390
Room service.

128
00:09:52,350 --> 00:09:54,050
Room service.

129
00:10:01,210 --> 00:10:03,320
We received your call to pick up last 
night's dinner,mr. Gregory.

130
00:10:03,320 --> 00:10:04,810
Yes. Come in.

131
00:10:09,860 --> 00:10:11,110
Was everything ok?

132
00:10:11,110 --> 00:10:14,770
My porterhouse was juicy and rare,
just the way I like it.

133
00:10:15,120 --> 00:10:17,700
But my wife wasn't feeling very well.

134
00:10:17,970 --> 00:10:20,250
Hoping a hot bath will do the trick.

135
00:10:20,250 --> 00:10:22,680
Honey,how is everything in there?

136
00:10:23,400 --> 00:10:24,850
I guess pretty good.

137
00:10:24,850 --> 00:10:27,410
Thank you very much,oscar.

138
00:10:36,430 --> 00:10:39,340
- Angel mark gregory was such a bad boy.
- How bad?

140
00:10:39,600 --> 00:10:42,750
Well,when he was a kid,he was 
caught peeking in a neighbor's window.

141
00:10:42,750 --> 00:10:44,170
I'm sure it gets worse,right?

142
00:10:44,170 --> 00:10:47,700
At the ripe age of 18,he--
how do I put this delicately?

144
00:10:47,700 --> 00:10:50,520
Had an intense affection for ladies 
with learner's permits.

145
00:10:50,520 --> 00:10:53,790
That sounds like statutory rape.
I'm not surprised.You talk to hotch?

147
00:10:53,790 --> 00:10:56,500
Yeah. It turns out his marriage lasted only 23 days.

148
00:10:56,500 --> 00:10:58,000
Our boy's got serious commitment issues.

149
00:10:58,000 --> 00:11:01,440
And fret not,my sweet.That poor girl who 
married him is still out there somewhere.

150
00:11:01,440 --> 00:11:03,240
If she were dead,it would be easier to find her.

151
00:11:03,240 --> 00:11:05,590
Well,it's a good thing 'cause we're 
gonna want to talk to her.

152
00:11:05,590 --> 00:11:08,740
Some of his deviant behavior must've 
leaked into other parts of his life.

153
00:11:09,280 --> 00:11:11,120
At least she got out alive.

154
00:11:21,410 --> 00:11:26,500
We found evidenceat his house that he acclimates
well to different surroundings.Possible disguises.

156
00:11:26,980 --> 00:11:29,850
He's emptied his bank accounts and he's 
put his dogs in a kennel.

157
00:11:29,850 --> 00:11:32,540
We're certain he's left the area 
and he's not coming back.

158
00:11:33,030 --> 00:11:35,630
And since he's on the run,
this classifies him as a "spree killer."

159
00:11:35,630 --> 00:11:38,290
Usually this type of killer goes through 2 phases:

160
00:11:38,290 --> 00:11:39,740
Guided and random.

161
00:11:39,740 --> 00:11:43,130
"Guided" means that this killer stays 
in his particular geographic

162
00:11:43,130 --> 00:11:45,410
area or comfort zone until he breaks down.

163
00:11:45,410 --> 00:11:48,190
That's why he killed the first 
4 women in a 60-mile radius.

164
00:11:48,190 --> 00:11:50,350
That's right. And we're hoping he's still there.

165
00:11:50,350 --> 00:11:53,420
In the guided phase,they usually have 
a final destination in mind.

166
00:11:53,420 --> 00:11:57,630
Like edmund kemper and andrew cunanan,
they saved their most meaningful kills till last.

168
00:11:58,040 --> 00:12:00,210
We should find out who that would be for gregory.

169
00:12:00,210 --> 00:12:03,580
When the random phase begins,
the kills seem to be without design.

170
00:12:03,580 --> 00:12:06,850
There's less time in between them.
At that point,he's lost total control.

171
00:12:06,850 --> 00:12:11,330
And as he devolves,he's gonna take more 
victims and become less noticeable.

173
00:12:11,330 --> 00:12:12,930
What does that mean?

174
00:12:12,930 --> 00:12:15,780
In gregory's case,his M.O. Is the torture.

175
00:12:15,780 --> 00:12:19,160
That would mean he will torture less

176
00:12:19,160 --> 00:12:22,620
and spend more time on the thing 
that gives him sexual release--

177
00:12:23,660 --> 00:12:24,800
drowning.

178
00:12:24,800 --> 00:12:27,750
So it's very important that we find him 
while he's still in the comfort zone.

179
00:12:27,750 --> 00:12:29,890
After that,there's no telling where he'll be.

180
00:12:31,410 --> 00:12:33,420
We'll get a release out to all the major networks.

181
00:12:33,420 --> 00:12:36,540
His face and possible disguises  will be all over the country by dinnertime.

182
00:12:37,060 --> 00:12:38,960
They just found the missing girl's body.

183
00:12:39,310 --> 00:12:41,300
-Close by? -No. Georgia.

184
00:12:42,260 --> 00:12:45,000
come(缺一句)

185
00:12:52,520 --> 00:12:55,840
elle and morgan just landed in georgia. They'll be at the hotel in about 20 minutes.

186
00:12:55,840 --> 00:12:57,770
So florida's not his only comfort zone.

187
00:12:57,770 --> 00:13:00,340
No. Apparently,he's set up businesses  throughout the southern U.S.

188
00:13:00,340 --> 00:13:02,300
Well,we have warnings along I-95

189
00:13:02,300 --> 00:13:05,020
and I-10 in case he decides to travel  along the gulf coast.

190
00:13:05,020 --> 00:13:07,780
Well,now that he's crossed state lines, it's a nationwide search.

191
00:13:07,780 --> 00:13:11,330
He doesn't wanna get caught,so he'll  probably alter his route and drive quieter roads.

192
00:13:11,330 --> 00:13:12,270
We'll prepare for that,too.

193
00:13:12,270 --> 00:13:15,140
These records indicate that he went  to high school in 4 different states.

194
00:13:15,140 --> 00:13:18,730
So they moved around a lot. Let's talk to his father,find out why.

195
00:13:18,730 --> 00:13:21,180
Maybe he's revisiting places where he  feels comfortable.

196
00:13:21,180 --> 00:13:24,640
The latest hotel records indicate that  he checked in using his own name.

197
00:13:24,640 --> 00:13:27,620
If he doesn't want us to catch him, what's he doing,taunting us?

198
00:13:27,620 --> 00:13:30,700
No. Taunting would imply that this  is some sort of game. It isn'T.

199
00:13:30,700 --> 00:13:34,270
He's made it very clear that he has no  intention of going back to his life as it was.

200
00:13:34,270 --> 00:13:35,550
This is a one-way trip.

201
00:13:35,550 --> 00:13:37,760
There's dna proving he's the offender.

202
00:13:38,290 --> 00:13:41,010
No point in covering his tracks now. That'll only slow him down.

203
00:13:41,010 --> 00:13:43,550
And if he wanted us to catch him, he'd simply stop running.

204
00:13:43,840 --> 00:13:46,170
It's not likely.He's got 400 grand in cash.

205
00:13:46,170 --> 00:13:48,350
That type of money he can charter a plane

206
00:13:48,350 --> 00:13:50,800
or buy a ticket to virtually  anywhere in the world.

207
00:13:50,800 --> 00:13:52,730
Well,he's not hiding.He's hunting.

208
00:13:52,730 --> 00:13:56,290
Besides,driving works for him.It's anonymous, and he can cover a lot of territory.

209
00:13:56,330 --> 00:13:59,600
We should notify the mexican and canadian  border patrols.He might try to leave the U.S.

210
00:13:59,600 --> 00:14:02,380
Let them know most spree kills  end with suicide by cop.

211
00:14:02,380 --> 00:14:04,850
It could be how he plans on getting out of his mess.

212
00:14:13,040 --> 00:14:15,910
Wow. Mark gregory splurges on hotel rooms, doesn't he?

213
00:14:15,910 --> 00:14:17,610
Yeah. Great guy.

214
00:14:17,610 --> 00:14:21,770
He offers them a nice,warm robe  right before he drowns them.

215
00:14:22,280 --> 00:14:24,320
He spent a lot of time with nicole wegener.

216
00:14:24,320 --> 00:14:26,040
Picked her up in tampa

217
00:14:26,410 --> 00:14:28,530
and drove her all the way to georgia.

218
00:14:29,060 --> 00:14:32,260
But unlike his other victims,there's  no type of relationship to link the two of them.

219
00:14:32,260 --> 00:14:35,290
A random victim with a whole life ahead of her.

220
00:14:35,720 --> 00:14:38,170
- She was beautiful. 
- She was also a stranger.

221
00:14:38,170 --> 00:14:40,330
So it means he had to lure her somehow.

222
00:14:42,180 --> 00:14:44,450
"Mark gregory,photographer."

223
00:14:46,520 --> 00:14:48,960
So what if he preyed on this woman's vanity?

224
00:14:48,960 --> 00:14:52,360
He's a photographer.He offers her  a professional modeling career.

225
00:14:52,990 --> 00:14:56,930
Well,if he has a legitimate web site and portfolio,

226
00:14:56,930 --> 00:14:59,430
the right credentials, why wouldn't she trust him?

227
00:14:59,430 --> 00:15:01,920
And a perfected ruse would explain  how he was able to get her through the lobby

228
00:15:01,920 --> 00:15:04,250
of a 5-star hotel with no one looking.

229
00:15:04,400 --> 00:15:07,670
It's just a matter of time before  he finds himself another victim.

230
00:15:36,050 --> 00:15:39,320
- Hotchner. 
- Who is your daddy?

231
00:15:39,320 --> 00:15:40,180
I'm sorry?

232
00:15:40,180 --> 00:15:43,200
This has not been easy. This woman seriously covered her tracks.

233
00:15:43,200 --> 00:15:44,380
Do you have the right number?

234
00:15:44,380 --> 00:15:46,110
Are you looking for gregory's ex-wife?

235
00:15:46,110 --> 00:15:46,920
- You found her.  
- Yeh.

236
00:15:46,920 --> 00:15:49,920
Still in the sunshine state. Settled down in bradenton.

237
00:15:49,920 --> 00:15:51,380
We'll have her picked up.

238
00:15:51,380 --> 00:15:53,590
- I'm still in shock.  
- Well,it's understandable.

239
00:15:53,590 --> 00:15:57,910
I'm more surprised that you found me. I paid a lot to have my past erased.

240
00:15:59,160 --> 00:16:01,390
Are you saying you're not  surprised that mark is a serial killer?

241
00:16:01,390 --> 00:16:05,100
I knew something was wrong. That's why we were only married for 3 weeks.

242
00:16:05,100 --> 00:16:07,490
Have you been in hiding because  you were afraid he would come after you?

243
00:16:07,490 --> 00:16:10,620
He stalked me for a few years after the annulment.

244
00:16:10,620 --> 00:16:13,430
I had to disappear if I wanted to survive.

245
00:16:14,710 --> 00:16:17,710
I know it was a long time ago, but what was life with him like?

246
00:16:18,140 --> 00:16:21,120
Terrible. He was controlling,didn't trust me,

247
00:16:21,120 --> 00:16:26,690
insisted I was cheating on him with anyone, with everyone.I couldn't leave the house.

248
00:16:27,930 --> 00:16:30,610
I'm sorry to dredge all this up, but you've definitely helped us understand him.

249
00:16:30,610 --> 00:16:32,280
He dated his first victim.

250
00:16:32,280 --> 00:16:36,230
And if she cheated on him,it may have  been the thing that started him killing.

251
00:16:37,950 --> 00:16:42,330
I still can't understand how my son  could be responsible for this.

252
00:16:43,590 --> 00:16:46,410
Your son's a narcissist with a split personality.

253
00:16:46,410 --> 00:16:48,610
He's able to gain his victim's  trust before inflicting pain upon them.

254
00:16:48,610 --> 00:16:52,800
This is most likely derived from an  incredible amount of self-awareness.

255
00:16:52,800 --> 00:16:57,360
Mark has mastered the art of manipulation. It only allows you to see his good side.

256
00:16:57,360 --> 00:17:01,190
-This is a nightmare. -Why won't you sit down,mr. Gregory.

257
00:17:11,820 --> 00:17:14,290
You moved around a lot when mark was growing up?

258
00:17:14,880 --> 00:17:19,410
Mark never complained.I guess it's because  he was always good at making friends.

259
00:17:19,410 --> 00:17:21,520
He fit in wherever we went.

260
00:17:21,520 --> 00:17:25,900
We know he's been to georgia.Do you know where else he night go? Anyplace he loved to visit,anywhere he'd call home?

261
00:17:25,900 --> 00:17:30,310
Well,we've lived here the longest. He would consider florida home.

262
00:17:36,470 --> 00:17:39,150
Mark's mother isn't in any photos.

263
00:17:41,320 --> 00:17:44,690
Elizabeth died in a car accident.

264
00:17:44,690 --> 00:17:47,170
I'm sorry.

265
00:17:47,170 --> 00:17:48,930
How old was mark when that happened?

266
00:17:48,930 --> 00:17:51,540
-10. -Were they close?

267
00:17:51,540 --> 00:17:53,130
She was his mother.

268
00:17:53,130 --> 00:17:56,700
Typically,when a child loses a mother, he sees her as a victim,

269
00:17:56,700 --> 00:17:59,370
which,theoretically,he'd wanna protect women.

270
00:17:59,370 --> 00:18:01,240
More likely to lash out against the father,

271
00:18:01,240 --> 00:18:05,280
blaming men for needing punishment, but mark didn't do that.

272
00:18:05,280 --> 00:18:07,380
-'Cause you and mark were close? -Yes.

273
00:18:07,380 --> 00:18:09,390
Any reason he would have blamed  his mother for her death?

274
00:18:09,390 --> 00:18:12,800
Was she drinking and driving, fell asleep at the wheel?Anything?

275
00:18:12,800 --> 00:18:15,090
No. No,no.Nothing like that.

276
00:18:15,090 --> 00:18:19,390
Maybe he blames her because he  thinks she abandoned him.

277
00:18:19,390 --> 00:18:24,750
Lost of a female figure could explain why  he was a peeping tom in adolescence.

278
00:18:26,010 --> 00:18:29,400
Are you telling me that young  boys aren't curious?

279
00:18:29,400 --> 00:18:31,970
Sure they're curious,but not all  of 'em peek into windows.

280
00:18:31,970 --> 00:18:34,540
What about the statutory rape charge?

281
00:18:34,540 --> 00:18:38,730
Aw,nah. Mark had just turned 18,

282
00:18:39,020 --> 00:18:41,590
and his girlfriend was 15.

283
00:18:41,590 --> 00:18:44,050
They were kids,for god sake.

284
00:18:44,050 --> 00:18:47,270
It was her parents that pressed charges.

285
00:18:48,560 --> 00:18:50,400
Mark ever have to take responsibility for anything?

286
00:18:50,400 --> 00:18:52,360
What are you saying?

287
00:18:53,300 --> 00:18:57,790
That being a protective parent has  turned my child into a killer?

288
00:18:57,790 --> 00:19:01,530
No. I'm saying you're making excuses. I'm not sure it did him any favors.

289
00:19:16,070 --> 00:19:17,750
You're gonna be ok.

290
00:19:54,980 --> 00:19:56,350
wake up.

291
00:20:13,390 --> 00:20:16,310
It looks like the first victim  wasn't being unfaithful.

292
00:20:16,310 --> 00:20:18,560
She had a husband and was trying  to keep it a secret.

293
00:20:18,560 --> 00:20:19,930
Sounds like he found out.

294
00:20:19,930 --> 00:20:23,470
There must have been something major  in his past to trigger such an extreme reaction.

295
00:20:23,470 --> 00:20:27,360
Maybe something with his parents'  relationship had scarred him during childhood.

296
00:20:27,360 --> 00:20:31,100
Hey,guys,I found mark gregory's car  at atlanta international airport.

297
00:20:31,580 --> 00:20:33,820
Pretty smart.There's a sea of cars at the airport.

298
00:20:33,820 --> 00:20:35,940
But he parked in short term and he got a ticket.

299
00:20:35,940 --> 00:20:38,120
There must have been another reason  for him to dump it there.

300
00:20:38,120 --> 00:20:39,740
Guys,I know we ruled out flying,

301
00:20:39,740 --> 00:20:42,820
but it's hard to ignore the fact  that his last known location was a place

302
00:20:42,820 --> 00:20:45,960
that literally had thousands of  international flights a day.

303
00:20:45,960 --> 00:20:48,110
Thousands of people.All possible victims.

304
00:20:48,110 --> 00:20:50,960
Garcia,is it possible to run the  face recognition software at the airport?

305
00:20:50,960 --> 00:20:53,370
I'm already on it.I went ahead  and started with the security footage

306
00:20:53,370 --> 00:20:55,730
at the parking garage since we  know he was in there.

307
00:20:55,730 --> 00:20:57,950
Knowing what he looks like's  got to be some advantage to us.

308
00:20:57,950 --> 00:20:59,200
And...

309
00:21:01,860 --> 00:21:04,340
it is. I'm uploading to you right now.

310
00:21:04,340 --> 00:21:05,740
Thanks.

311
00:21:18,200 --> 00:21:19,840
She seemed like his type.

312
00:21:20,630 --> 00:21:23,630
He's looking for the easiest target. He doesn't have time to waste.

313
00:21:24,750 --> 00:21:27,280
Who doesn't trust a man in uniform?

314
00:21:28,900 --> 00:21:30,590
He helps her.

315
00:21:32,180 --> 00:21:34,960
She returns the favor and gives him a ride.

316
00:21:35,990 --> 00:21:37,900
Fatal mistake.

317
00:21:40,480 --> 00:21:43,700
As you can see in the footage, he's been able to access uniforms.

318
00:21:43,700 --> 00:21:47,910
Most likely,he'll use those of authority  to try and invoke a feeling of safety.

319
00:21:48,250 --> 00:21:50,470
He may also be using disguises.

320
00:21:50,470 --> 00:21:54,700
He's suspected of having approached  a woman with a photography ruse.

321
00:21:54,700 --> 00:21:56,420
Gregory has credentials.

322
00:21:56,420 --> 00:21:59,280
He was a photographer in miami for years.

323
00:22:00,660 --> 00:22:04,640
He's well traveled and conducts business  throughout the southern united states.

324
00:22:06,260 --> 00:22:09,640
There's no chance of predicting  where he'll strike next.

325
00:22:10,050 --> 00:22:12,260
That's why we are asking you to be aware

326
00:22:12,260 --> 00:22:15,710
and on the lookout for this  38-year-old white male.

327
00:22:17,660 --> 00:22:21,750
He appears to be very confident, trustworthy,and charming.

328
00:22:35,780 --> 00:22:38,780
Let's review what we know. Gregory will continue to drown.

329
00:22:39,170 --> 00:22:41,040
The question is why does he have to.

330
00:22:41,860 --> 00:22:45,160
We know someone who murders by drowning wants to invoke fear.

331
00:22:45,610 --> 00:22:48,230
If water symbolizes emotion that says they're overwhelmed

332
00:22:48,230 --> 00:22:52,470
by their own unresolved issues or facing some sort of major life crisis,

333
00:22:52,900 --> 00:22:57,660
it suggests a release of the old is necessary to emerge and begin anew.

334
00:22:58,350 --> 00:23:02,480
So there's something he's trying to purge or cleanse by killing these women?

335
00:23:02,720 --> 00:23:04,210
I think it's exactly right.

336
00:23:04,210 --> 00:23:06,330
That's the key to unlock why he kills.

337
00:23:06,330 --> 00:23:07,570
Excuse me,gentlemen.

338
00:23:07,570 --> 00:23:09,330
Sorry to interrupt.

339
00:23:10,830 --> 00:23:13,560
You really don't know someone until you take a road trip with them.

340
00:23:15,530 --> 00:23:17,020
What are you trying to say?

341
00:23:17,020 --> 00:23:18,520
Look at this car,man.

342
00:23:18,520 --> 00:23:22,120
There's empty soda cans and fast-food wrappers everywhere.

343
00:23:22,120 --> 00:23:25,300
You're a slob. Back at quantico your desk is all neat.

344
00:23:25,300 --> 00:23:27,690
But I bet if you looked in those drawers, you'll find a mess.

345
00:23:27,690 --> 00:23:30,070
Ok,we have been on the road way too long.

346
00:23:31,980 --> 00:23:34,000
Aw. That must be the boyfriend.

347
00:23:34,000 --> 00:23:35,700
Yes,it is.

348
00:23:36,070 --> 00:23:37,500
Hey,gideon.

349
00:23:39,830 --> 00:23:40,940
Ok.

350
00:23:44,870 --> 00:23:46,260
Yeah. Got it.Yeah.

351
00:23:47,480 --> 00:23:50,610
They found the woman from the atlanta airport in south carolina.

352
00:23:50,610 --> 00:23:52,590
It feels like we're driving from body to body.

353
00:23:52,590 --> 00:23:55,540
Well,we know that south carolina's part of his business route.

354
00:23:55,540 --> 00:23:57,860
So he's probably going back to what he knows.

355
00:24:11,900 --> 00:24:13,170
You see something?

356
00:24:14,040 --> 00:24:18,240
No. I was just thinking about the information you released about mark gregory at the press conference.

357
00:24:18,240 --> 00:24:19,200
What about it?

358
00:24:19,200 --> 00:24:23,160
Well,we described him as someone who's engaging, confident,poses as people with authority.

359
00:24:23,160 --> 00:24:25,240
But this is a guy who's flying under the radar.

360
00:24:25,240 --> 00:24:26,770
So we made a mistake?

361
00:24:26,770 --> 00:24:28,240
No,not at all.

362
00:24:28,240 --> 00:24:31,950
We're dealing with a killer who's highly intelligent and incredibly resourceful.

363
00:24:31,950 --> 00:24:35,410
You would think that we've pushed him to change what he's doing.

364
00:24:35,960 --> 00:24:37,180
To what?

365
00:24:37,180 --> 00:24:39,500
Maybe he's not using a simple ruse anymore.

366
00:24:39,500 --> 00:24:43,570
He could alter his appearance so he's barely recognizable,just like in the sketch book.

367
00:24:43,820 --> 00:24:47,040
If he does that, we'd have no idea what we're looking for.

368
00:24:54,850 --> 00:24:57,030
Fbi.Morgan and greenaway.

369
00:25:01,390 --> 00:25:02,480
This place is...

370
00:25:02,480 --> 00:25:04,420
is a hole in the wall.

371
00:25:04,730 --> 00:25:08,090
I don't know why he's checking into a fleabag motel.Gregory's got cash.

372
00:25:08,090 --> 00:25:10,720
And he's obviously devolved into the random phase of his kills.

373
00:25:11,460 --> 00:25:13,320
Must have something to do with how he views his victims.

374
00:25:13,320 --> 00:25:17,650
Well,if he doesn't know these women, maybe he thinks that they're not worthy or dirty.

375
00:25:17,650 --> 00:25:18,920
Are you the manager?

376
00:25:18,920 --> 00:25:20,520
Yes. You wanted to see me?

377
00:25:20,520 --> 00:25:22,650
Do you recognize this man?

378
00:25:23,160 --> 00:25:25,140
Yeah. Kind of looks like the guy.

379
00:25:25,140 --> 00:25:27,560
He paid his bill in cash about 3 hours ago.

380
00:25:27,560 --> 00:25:28,860
You sure about the time?

381
00:25:28,870 --> 00:25:31,110
Absolutely. My stories were on.

382
00:25:32,250 --> 00:25:34,930
Well,given the lividity,I'd say she died right before that.

383
00:25:34,930 --> 00:25:36,820
Did you happen to see what he was driving?

384
00:25:36,820 --> 00:25:38,660
Yeah. One of those black suvs.

385
00:25:38,660 --> 00:25:40,590
That's the victim's car from the atlanta airport.

386
00:25:40,590 --> 00:25:42,200
Did you notice if it had georgia plates?

387
00:25:42,200 --> 00:25:44,630
No. They definitely had south carolina plates.

388
00:25:44,630 --> 00:25:46,640
When he was filling out the forms for the motel,

389
00:25:46,640 --> 00:25:49,250
he couldn't remember the number. So I went outside to write it down.

390
00:25:49,250 --> 00:25:51,770
That's why we can't track him. He's switching plates.

391
00:25:52,130 --> 00:25:53,400
Can you get us those numbers,please?

392
00:25:53,400 --> 00:25:56,490
-Sure. I'll be right back. -Thank you.

393
00:25:58,440 --> 00:25:59,760
There goes the pilot uniform.

394
00:25:59,760 --> 00:26:00,940
Well,we know his identity.

395
00:26:00,940 --> 00:26:04,240
We know he likes to use disguises, and he doesn't care about leaving them.

396
00:26:05,020 --> 00:26:07,050
Look at the level of torture here.

397
00:26:07,050 --> 00:26:10,400
He spent the least amount of time with her,but he still shocked her enough to turn her feet black.

398
00:26:10,400 --> 00:26:13,620
No normal human being can sustain this kind of torture.

399
00:26:15,530 --> 00:26:18,500
If he shocked her over and over again, then she must've died.

400
00:26:18,500 --> 00:26:21,240
But the cause of death was a wet drowning. The only way he could've done that--

401
00:26:21,240 --> 00:26:23,750
resuscitate her every time just so he can drown her again.

402
00:26:23,750 --> 00:26:26,200
We know that he was spending 2 days with these women.

403
00:26:27,220 --> 00:26:29,260
But he picked her up at the airport yesterday.

404
00:26:29,260 --> 00:26:31,420
So he's spending hf as much time with them now.

405
00:26:31,420 --> 00:26:33,510
And now he's probably got himself another one.

406
00:26:35,230 --> 00:26:36,360
Hotchner.

407
00:26:36,360 --> 00:26:37,620
Who's the answer to all your dreams?

408
00:26:37,620 --> 00:26:40,080
- I'm gonna put you on speaker. 
- Oh,you completely suck.

409
00:26:40,460 --> 00:26:44,140
Hospital records show mark gregory fractured a vertebrae when he was 10.

410
00:26:44,140 --> 00:26:46,960
He suffered damage to his spine,ligaments, and neck.

411
00:26:46,960 --> 00:26:49,690
-What caused that type of injury? -Whiplash.

412
00:26:49,840 --> 00:26:54,000
Behold the wonderful genius of dr. Spencer reid. Honey,that's exactly what the rest of the hospital record says.

413
00:26:54,000 --> 00:26:58,330
I did some more digging.I found an article in the polk county paper describing the crash.

414
00:26:58,330 --> 00:26:59,460
What did it say?

415
00:26:59,460 --> 00:27:04,910
The headline reads that elizabeth gregory died in a crash.But her 10-year-old son was only injured.

416
00:27:05,680 --> 00:27:07,420
Mark gregory was in the car with her.

417
00:27:07,420 --> 00:27:09,000
Apparently.

418
00:27:09,010 --> 00:27:12,680
We need to talk to gregory's father, find out what else he's keeping from us.

419
00:27:26,100 --> 00:27:27,410
Do you need some help with your bags,sir?

420
00:27:27,410 --> 00:27:29,630
No. I'm good.Thank you very much.

421
00:27:33,880 --> 00:27:35,600
-Thank you. -No problem.

422
00:27:36,130 --> 00:27:40,070
You know,actually i would like a little help.Thank you.

423
00:27:41,080 --> 00:27:43,350
Perfect. That's what I'm here for.

424
00:27:50,210 --> 00:27:54,280
Well,I know you guys didn't come here to look at pictures of my son.

425
00:27:54,740 --> 00:27:56,300
Did something happen?

426
00:27:56,300 --> 00:27:58,350
Why are there no memories of your wife here?

427
00:27:59,320 --> 00:28:02,110
Why would I want to remind my son

428
00:28:02,110 --> 00:28:05,010
of the most horrible thing that  ever happened to him?

429
00:28:05,010 --> 00:28:08,980
Normally when a parent dies, the other parent tends to overcompensate

430
00:28:08,980 --> 00:28:11,300
by building a shrine of pictures,

431
00:28:11,300 --> 00:28:14,410
leaving their personal effects untouched sometimes for years.

432
00:28:15,120 --> 00:28:16,790
You didn't happen to do that.

433
00:28:16,790 --> 00:28:19,850
Why didn't you tell us your son was in the car when your wife died?

434
00:28:20,700 --> 00:28:22,910
I didn't think it was important.

435
00:28:25,960 --> 00:28:27,450
You didn't think it was important.

436
00:28:27,450 --> 00:28:30,710
You didn't think it was important to tell us your son witnessed his mother dying?

437
00:28:31,100 --> 00:28:32,080
No.

438
00:28:32,080 --> 00:28:37,170
The fact that he witnessed his mother die at such a young age clearly affected how he regards women.

439
00:28:37,170 --> 00:28:39,740
Do you know why your son was married for such a short period of time?

440
00:28:39,740 --> 00:28:43,080
Yes. It was a mistake.He was young.

441
00:28:43,080 --> 00:28:47,520
Well,we talked to his ex-wife.Mark was obsessed with thinking she was unfaithful.

442
00:28:48,370 --> 00:28:51,010
-It could happen. -But she never was.

443
00:28:51,010 --> 00:28:53,530
But he made life unbearable for her. She couldn't leave the house.

444
00:28:53,530 --> 00:28:55,590
She couldn't take a breath without  worrying about it.

445
00:28:55,590 --> 00:29:01,790
Something must have happened to feed that distrust, to give him such a distorted view of relationships.

446
00:29:01,790 --> 00:29:03,980
How were things with your wife,mr. Gregory?

447
00:29:04,170 --> 00:29:06,880
Normal and uneventful.

448
00:29:07,410 --> 00:29:08,900
Was she being unfaithful?

449
00:29:08,900 --> 00:29:09,870
What?

450
00:29:09,870 --> 00:29:11,730
Did she pick men up?XXXXXXXX No.

451
00:29:11,730 --> 00:29:14,320
All right,all right. Enough. Stop.

452
00:29:19,430 --> 00:29:21,850
when she couldn't find a baby-sitter,she would

453
00:29:22,690 --> 00:29:26,970
take him with her to the motel, let him play by the pool.

454
00:29:27,940 --> 00:29:30,690
This went on for over a year.

455
00:29:30,960 --> 00:29:33,480
What kind of mother would do that?

456
00:29:33,480 --> 00:29:35,590
Did you ever take him to therapy,mr. Gregory?

457
00:29:35,980 --> 00:29:37,330
- No. 
- Why?

458
00:29:37,330 --> 00:29:39,240
I didn't think he needed it.

459
00:29:39,240 --> 00:29:40,880
- Didn't think he needed it? 
- No.

460
00:29:40,880 --> 00:29:44,040
Boy watches his mother die.He lives,she dies.

461
00:29:44,040 --> 00:29:46,120
You don't think that's confusing  to a 10-year-old?

462
00:29:46,120 --> 00:29:48,080
- I didn't say that. - You did say that.

463
00:29:48,080 --> 00:29:49,710
Mark was smart enough to know what was going on.

464
00:29:49,710 --> 00:29:52,740
That explains his issues with infidelity, his hatred towards women,

465
00:29:52,740 --> 00:29:55,630
and now why he tortures and drowns them.

466
00:29:55,990 --> 00:29:58,140
His first victim was married.

467
00:29:58,140 --> 00:30:01,220
She was having an affair with him,which--

468
00:30:01,710 --> 00:30:04,660
it clearly reminded him of what  his mother did to you.

469
00:30:04,660 --> 00:30:06,700
You think your wife's death was an accident?

470
00:30:07,480 --> 00:30:09,180
I honestly don't know.

471
00:30:09,180 --> 00:30:12,440
Well,what do you know?What do you think? Do you even know what I'm talking about?

472
00:30:12,440 --> 00:30:14,900
I--ok. I had my suspicions.

473
00:30:14,900 --> 00:30:17,550
Your son did what you thought about doing a hundred times.

474
00:30:18,130 --> 00:30:20,630
These are innocent women.Innocent women, mr. Gregory.

475
00:30:20,860 --> 00:30:23,880
Ever occur to you your son might be trying to stand up for you in his own sick,

476
00:30:23,880 --> 00:30:26,520
demented way because you weren't there? You weren't there,mr. Gregory.

477
00:30:26,520 --> 00:30:27,790
I--

478
00:30:29,170 --> 00:30:32,560
help us before he kills again and again and again.

479
00:30:32,560 --> 00:30:35,340
Help us,mr. Gregory.Help us.

480
00:30:50,610 --> 00:30:52,040
Gideon. Gideon.

481
00:30:52,430 --> 00:30:55,060
You do know that doug gregory isn't the killer, right?

482
00:30:55,870 --> 00:30:57,460
Yes,I know that.

483
00:30:57,460 --> 00:30:59,400
But he protected one,

484
00:30:59,400 --> 00:31:01,950
and now at least 6 women are  dead because of it.

485
00:31:06,690 --> 00:31:08,800
Come!Move it.

486
00:31:12,460 --> 00:31:14,420
No!

487
00:31:32,070 --> 00:31:34,400
Can't be in the pool with your clothes on.

488
00:31:37,170 --> 00:31:38,960
- Are you ok? 
- Help me.

489
00:31:38,960 --> 00:31:42,040
It's my wife.She fell in the pool. She can't swim.

490
00:31:42,040 --> 00:31:44,650
-Bring her over to the side. -I know cpr.

491
00:31:47,510 --> 00:31:48,900
Please help me.

492
00:31:49,760 --> 00:31:51,410
All right. All right.

493
00:31:51,410 --> 00:31:53,230
Well,she's not breathing.

494
00:31:55,390 --> 00:31:58,670
Look,man,I'm doing the best that I can. Why don't you go call 911.

495
00:32:00,660 --> 00:32:02,510
Go call 911,man.

496
00:32:08,700 --> 00:32:12,970
Oh,there you go.There you go. Get it out. Get it out. All right.There you go,honey.

497
00:32:14,830 --> 00:32:15,410
No! No!

498
00:32:15,410 --> 00:32:20,170
It's ok. It's ok.It's all right. You're breathing.There you go,honey.

499
00:32:20,540 --> 00:32:23,980
You're all right.You're all right. Your husband's gonna be right back.

500
00:32:26,430 --> 00:32:28,910
have you found any other suspicious drownings the last couple of days?

501
00:32:28,910 --> 00:32:31,350
Do you have any idea how many people drown every day?

502
00:32:31,350 --> 00:32:33,760
Yes,but they're more in the summer for obvious reasons.

503
00:32:33,760 --> 00:32:37,610
But I think it averages around 6,500 a year, which is 17 a day.

504
00:32:37,610 --> 00:32:39,230
-Is this reid? -Why,you're impressed?

505
00:32:39,230 --> 00:32:41,770
I am,slick. I am.

506
00:32:41,770 --> 00:32:43,800
You've been doing your research, haven't you?

507
00:32:44,610 --> 00:32:45,810
Hey,

508
00:32:45,810 --> 00:32:48,150
this one sounds particularly creepy.

509
00:32:48,800 --> 00:32:50,410
Garcia found a lead in tennessee.

510
00:32:50,410 --> 00:32:53,100
Allyson glennon was snatched from a grocery store a couple of hours ago

511
00:32:53,100 --> 00:32:55,440
and survived an attempted drowning in a motel pool.

512
00:32:55,440 --> 00:32:57,500
Motel pool?Doesn't sound like our guy.

513
00:32:57,500 --> 00:32:59,690
Yeah,I know,except that she's identified gregory as her attacker

514
00:32:59,690 --> 00:33:02,100
and the place is less than an hour from the last killing.

515
00:33:02,100 --> 00:33:04,660
Garcia's giving elle and morgan details right now.

516
00:33:05,500 --> 00:33:09,110
Reid and I had another talk with mark's father. We need to get everybody on the phone.

517
00:33:12,490 --> 00:33:13,720
Hey,gideon.

518
00:33:13,720 --> 00:33:15,990
We think mark's first victim was his mother.

519
00:33:16,170 --> 00:33:17,320
What?

520
00:33:17,320 --> 00:33:20,890
I'm sorry. You're saying a 10-year-old killed his own mom?

521
00:33:20,890 --> 00:33:25,600
Well,it's a common theory that sons can fixate on their mothers since their mothers are their introducon to love.

522
00:33:25,600 --> 00:33:29,180
And if that mother had a negative influence-- in this case she was an adulteress--

523
00:33:29,180 --> 00:33:32,410
it invalidated not only the father but reflected poorly onto the son.

524
00:33:32,410 --> 00:33:35,900
Mark gregory was a child,but he was old enough to understand what his mother was doing.

525
00:33:35,900 --> 00:33:39,620
He was protecting a weak,impotent, passive-aggressive father who wanted his wife dead.

526
00:33:39,620 --> 00:33:41,920
He read the old man like a book and lived the life he couldn'T.

527
00:33:41,920 --> 00:33:46,470
Because she was his mother,he saw her as a saint. But because she was a cheater,he also saw her as a sinner.

528
00:33:47,460 --> 00:33:49,500
There's a good chance he caused the car to crash.

529
00:33:49,500 --> 00:33:51,570
Do you think the father knew his son was a murderer?

530
00:33:51,570 --> 00:33:53,600
-Yes. -That's why he's so overprotective of him.

531
00:33:53,600 --> 00:33:57,150
We need to go through all the evidence from the car accident.Absolutely everything.

532
00:33:57,850 --> 00:34:00,430
News articles,medical records,police reports. I'm on it.

533
00:34:00,430 --> 00:34:04,520
We need to do it as quickly as possible.There's a killer on the run and he's grabbing women as he sees them.

534
00:34:05,090 --> 00:34:09,030
I got done sooner than I thought, so I'll be able to pick up the kids after the bell.

535
00:34:09,560 --> 00:34:11,930
Ok. See you then.

536
00:34:20,330 --> 00:34:23,000
Do exactly as I say or you'll die.

537
00:34:28,800 --> 00:34:32,470
When I got to the pool,he said he was gonna call for help,but he just disappeared.

538
00:34:32,470 --> 00:34:34,600
So you're thinking,"why wouldn't  I trust this guy?

539
00:34:34,600 --> 00:34:36,560
What kind of psycho would kill somebody in front of witnesses?"

540
00:34:36,560 --> 00:34:38,610
Yeah. Yeah. I'd seen the news.

541
00:34:38,610 --> 00:34:41,610
But this man didn't look like the one you're looking for.

542
00:34:41,610 --> 00:34:43,720
He left his glasses in the pool.

543
00:34:43,720 --> 00:34:45,690
And when he left,he walked with a limp.

544
00:34:45,690 --> 00:34:49,550
And nobody said anything about glasses or a limp,so...

545
00:34:50,370 --> 00:34:52,740
he might be in a hurry, but he's not looking to get caught.

546
00:34:53,070 --> 00:34:54,640
'Cause he's not done killing yet.

547
00:34:54,640 --> 00:34:57,320
Here's a police photo of the car gregory's mother was killed in.

548
00:34:57,320 --> 00:34:59,460
Right there. See the water dripping from under the car?

549
00:34:59,460 --> 00:35:04,230
It doesn't look like a fatal car crash. All the damage was done on the passenger side.

550
00:35:04,740 --> 00:35:06,500
What was her official cause of death?

551
00:35:06,500 --> 00:35:07,710
I'll ask garcia.

552
00:35:07,710 --> 00:35:09,700
We've got a possible abduction.

553
00:35:10,590 --> 00:35:12,000
Kelly dalton,28.

554
00:35:12,000 --> 00:35:15,290
Eyewitness saw her leaving a parking lot with a man resembling gregory.

555
00:35:15,490 --> 00:35:18,350
She was supposed to pick up her son. Never made it.

556
00:35:21,770 --> 00:35:23,180
Thanks,hotch.

557
00:35:23,860 --> 00:35:25,390
He's picked up a new victim.

558
00:35:25,390 --> 00:35:27,410
Hey,we got to get to the mall.

559
00:35:27,410 --> 00:35:29,960
Jump on 113.It'll take you 10 minutes.

560
00:35:30,920 --> 00:35:34,120
It was better when he had a ruse. At least that required a little planning.

561
00:35:34,120 --> 00:35:36,450
...Believed to have left the parking lot and headed south--

562
00:35:36,450 --> 00:35:38,410
..hey were driving a green jeep with tennessee plates--

563
00:35:38,410 --> 00:35:42,650
...if you see this vehicle or the passengers meeting the descriptions...

564
00:35:42,650 --> 00:35:46,870
do you want money or something?I've got a rich husband, and I know he'll pay a lot to get me back.

565
00:35:49,110 --> 00:35:51,770
So he's got a victim and a car. Now all he needs is the location.

566
00:35:51,770 --> 00:35:54,730
There are 5 sources of water nearby.

567
00:35:54,730 --> 00:35:57,940
Closest to the accident is rock creek in...

568
00:35:57,940 --> 00:36:02,820
copperhill,tennessee.There's where kelly dalton was abducted.Morgan and elle are there right now.

569
00:36:03,210 --> 00:36:04,590
Reid,one more thing.

570
00:36:04,590 --> 00:36:09,490
Elizabeth gregory's official cause of death was asphyxia caused by immersion in fluid.

571
00:36:10,610 --> 00:36:11,960
She drowned?

572
00:36:12,890 --> 00:36:16,430
With no discernible damage done by keeping her trapped in the car,

573
00:36:16,430 --> 00:36:20,850
what would cause a taller mother to drown and a smaller child to survive?

574
00:36:21,680 --> 00:36:23,350
There's only one way.

575
00:36:24,810 --> 00:36:28,510
Mark gregory held his mother's head under whatever water was in the car.

576
00:36:30,000 --> 00:36:32,040
His first kill was his most powerful.

577
00:36:35,580 --> 00:36:37,300
Well,at least we know where he's going.

578
00:36:40,250 --> 00:36:42,450
Back to where it all started.

579
00:36:52,830 --> 00:36:55,080
please,I have 2 boys.XXXXXXX

580
00:36:55,450 --> 00:36:56,820
Shut up.

581
00:36:56,820 --> 00:37:00,340
The article said the accident was on route 60 near east west highway.

582
00:37:01,010 --> 00:37:05,590
We're on route 60 about a quarter of a mile from rock creek.We're pulling over to check it out.

583
00:37:15,210 --> 00:37:17,310
-This is all your fault. 
-What is?

584
00:37:17,800 --> 00:37:19,950
I saw you every week with that man.

585
00:37:19,950 --> 00:37:21,990
You think I don't know what was going on?

586
00:37:21,990 --> 00:37:23,950
- I've never met you before. 
- Shut up!

587
00:37:24,120 --> 00:37:25,480
You're a liar!

588
00:37:26,310 --> 00:37:27,820
Turn here.

589
00:37:35,880 --> 00:37:37,820
Gideon,he's not here.

590
00:37:45,330 --> 00:37:46,740
Slow down!

591
00:37:47,870 --> 00:37:48,990
Stop!

592
00:37:50,410 --> 00:37:52,150
Stop! Stop!

593
00:37:59,260 --> 00:38:01,120
-You hear that?Did you guys hear that? 
-Yeah,I heard it.

594
00:38:01,120 --> 00:38:03,110
It's over there. Let's go.

595
00:38:50,790 --> 00:38:52,550
No!

596
00:38:53,010 --> 00:38:54,600
Please!

597
00:38:54,940 --> 00:38:56,900
Somebody help me!

598
00:38:56,900 --> 00:38:59,390
It's just the two of us out here.

599
00:39:17,110 --> 00:39:19,180
It's clear.Nobody in the car.

600
00:39:19,310 --> 00:39:23,330
We found the car off the road,but it's empty.

601
00:39:23,750 --> 00:39:25,770
-Which way is the water? -Over there

602
00:39:32,130 --> 00:39:34,590
Help me!

603
00:39:34,900 --> 00:39:36,530
Somebody help!

604
00:39:37,140 --> 00:39:38,640
That's coming from over there.

605
00:39:49,300 --> 00:39:50,290
No!

606
00:39:50,290 --> 00:39:51,700
How does that feel?

607
00:40:28,600 --> 00:40:31,180
Mark gregory,fbi!Put it down!

608
00:40:31,650 --> 00:40:32,750
Put it down!

609
00:40:39,360 --> 00:40:41,480
Come here. I got you.

610
00:40:43,850 --> 00:40:46,140
I got you.You're ok.

611
00:40:54,350 --> 00:40:56,050
Ok.it's okay.

612
00:41:04,410 --> 00:41:06,170
Hey. It's morgan.

613
00:41:06,590 --> 00:41:08,310
Kelly dalton's gonna be ok.

614
00:41:09,120 --> 00:41:12,160
Gregory's dead. We're coming home.

615
00:41:37,780 --> 00:41:40,420
The author francois de la rochefoucauld wrote,

616
00:41:41,190 --> 00:41:44,490
"we are so accustomed to disguise ourselves to others

617
00:41:44,490 --> 00:41:48,450
that in the end we become disguised to ourselves."

618
00:41:48,450 --> 00:41:51,460
<font color="#ffff00">-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- proudly presents sync:gagegao wk120</font>

619
00:41:51,460 --> 00:41:52,590
<font color="#ffff00">Criminal Minds Season 01 Episode 20</font>


