1
00:00:13,200 --> 00:00:15,210
His name's jack.

2
00:00:15,250 --> 00:00:18,970
He's a soldier,and he protects me.

3
00:00:19,710 --> 00:00:22,350
I didn't mean to get you mad.

4
00:00:22,400 --> 00:00:23,680
Please?

5
00:00:23,740 --> 00:00:26,260
I'll be a good boy.

6
00:00:26,350 --> 00:00:29,410
Please let me out.

7
00:00:44,170 --> 00:00:46,760
Peter.

8
00:00:58,140 --> 00:00:59,320
Katie.

9
00:00:59,380 --> 00:01:01,630
I think peter's back.

10
00:01:02,930 --> 00:01:04,480
Peter?
Are you sure?

12
00:01:04,540 --> 00:01:06,330
I just got a new image.

13
00:01:07,130 --> 00:01:08,640
The screen name onthe sender is hugz.

14
00:01:08,720 --> 00:01:09,990
He just uploadedthis to me.

15
00:01:10,030 --> 00:01:11,240
We're sure it'sa new image?

16
00:01:11,290 --> 00:01:12,150
New image,same boy.

17
00:01:12,180 --> 00:01:13,690
Time and datestamped an hour ago.

18
00:01:13,730 --> 00:01:15,910
- Are communicatingdirectly with this hugz?
- No.

20
00:01:15,970 --> 00:01:17,650
I'm in a chat room.
I was just fishing.

22
00:01:17,700 --> 00:01:18,750
Put him up.

23
00:01:18,810 --> 00:01:21,090
Carl,I need to know wherethis chat room originated.

24
00:01:21,150 --> 00:01:22,240
People,listen up.

25
00:01:22,270 --> 00:01:24,460
We have a boy we namedpeter a year ago.

26
00:01:24,500 --> 00:01:27,530
At the time,he was listedbetween 5 and 6 years old.

27
00:01:27,530 --> 00:01:32,090
I.M. Hugz "vn-ho."

28
00:01:33,740 --> 00:01:36,770
Very nice.How old.

29
00:01:40,030 --> 00:01:42,330
Very.

30
00:01:48,780 --> 00:01:51,050
Go to the site.

31
00:01:56,700 --> 00:01:58,000
That clock iscounting down.

32
00:01:58,070 --> 00:01:59,290
It's an auction clock.

33
00:01:59,370 --> 00:02:00,990
He's gonna sell peter.

34
00:02:01,060 --> 00:02:03,630
Give me aaron hotchnerat the B.A.U.

35
00:02:09,400 --> 00:02:12,660
40,000 imagesof child pornare posted every weekon the internet,

36
00:02:12,720 --> 00:02:15,280
along with the appearanceof 20 new children.

37
00:02:15,350 --> 00:02:18,480
The appetite for babies as youngas 4 months old has soared.

38
00:02:18,530 --> 00:02:22,070
Many of these childrenhave been kidnappedand sold into pedophile rings.

39
00:02:22,120 --> 00:02:26,820
One year ago,the same boy appearedon several web sitesused by pedophiles.

40
00:02:26,900 --> 00:02:28,830
He was a new face then.

41
00:02:28,830 --> 00:02:34,030
After a massive huntled by our crimesagainst children unit,the boy disappeared.

42
00:02:34,100 --> 00:02:36,590
Until tonight whenS.S.A.Cole telephoned us.

43
00:02:36,670 --> 00:02:37,650
Katie cole?

44
00:02:37,710 --> 00:02:39,080
She was inthe B.A.U.,Right?

45
00:02:39,130 --> 00:02:42,290
One of the firstprofilers,clinical psychologist,brilliant.

46
00:02:42,320 --> 00:02:45,230
She runs the crimesagainst childrenunit in maryland.

47
00:02:45,300 --> 00:02:46,680
I always wantedto meet her.

48
00:02:46,730 --> 00:02:48,210
Really?
I heardshe's a bitch.

50
00:02:48,240 --> 00:02:50,200
Nobody ever calledyou that,katie.

51
00:02:50,230 --> 00:02:52,550
Well,not to my face.

52
00:02:54,430 --> 00:02:58,810
The first timeI ever saw him,he appeared in aseries of photos.

53
00:02:58,860 --> 00:03:01,210
I named him peteR.

54
00:03:01,260 --> 00:03:05,320
Now he's beingauctioned offwhen that clockruns to zero.

55
00:03:05,390 --> 00:03:06,690
Auctioned.

56
00:03:06,720 --> 00:03:08,400
His face isn't pixilated.

57
00:03:08,460 --> 00:03:11,410
'Cause the unsubis confidentthat we're notgoing to be ableto identify himin time.

58
00:03:11,470 --> 00:03:12,320
What aboutthe site itself?

59
00:03:12,390 --> 00:03:13,730
Can't we justtrack its origin?

60
00:03:13,800 --> 00:03:16,410
It's routed through aproxy server in belarus.

61
00:03:16,460 --> 00:03:20,550
Even if that governmentwas friendly,peter'd be gonebefore we finishedthe paperwork.

62
00:03:20,610 --> 00:03:22,480
We don't need to worryabout the paperwork.

63
00:03:22,570 --> 00:03:24,000
We have garcia.

64
00:03:24,070 --> 00:03:26,860
- Better get on that,will you?
- Yes,sir.

66
00:03:27,260 --> 00:03:28,730
So,what happeneda year ago,katie?

67
00:03:28,820 --> 00:03:31,280
We cross-referencedthe images of the boy.

68
00:03:31,360 --> 00:03:33,440
We talked to knownoffenders nationwide.

69
00:03:33,540 --> 00:03:36,470
We narrowed the locationdown to the easternunited states.

70
00:03:36,530 --> 00:03:39,160
We had some suspects in,but the trail went cold.

71
00:03:39,240 --> 00:03:40,080
Until today.

72
00:03:40,150 --> 00:03:43,350
With all due respect,miss cole,how is this time goingto be any different?

73
00:03:43,460 --> 00:03:45,210
We havea starting point.

74
00:03:45,300 --> 00:03:47,420
The location where the imagewas first discovered.

75
00:03:47,480 --> 00:03:52,610
A chat room--hosted by an independentweb companyin cleveland,ohio.

76
00:03:52,700 --> 00:03:57,480
And this time,I am bringing youall in with me.

77
00:04:09,850 --> 00:04:14,240
<font color=#38B0DE>-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents</font>

78
00:04:14,270 --> 00:04:19,320
<font color=#38B0DE>Sync: YTET-colleen3684
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-</font>

79
00:04:19,360 --> 00:04:25,080
<font color=#38B0DE>Criminal Minds
Season 2 Episode 02</font>

80
00:04:41,760 --> 00:04:51,330
Theologiandietrich bonhoeffer said,"the test of the moralityof a societyis what it doesfor its children."

81
00:05:02,060 --> 00:05:04,120
Well,if it isn'tdr.Reid.

82
00:05:04,190 --> 00:05:06,730
Elle.
Wow.

84
00:05:07,360 --> 00:05:11,960
- Nice haircut.
- Thanks.Yeah...

86
00:05:12,030 --> 00:05:13,570
I likeyour haircut,too.

87
00:05:13,630 --> 00:05:14,600
Is that a boys' regular?

88
00:05:14,660 --> 00:05:16,400
Yeah,it is.

89
00:05:16,440 --> 00:05:18,460
Wa--do you not like it?

90
00:05:18,520 --> 00:05:20,830
It's totally you.

91
00:05:20,890 --> 00:05:25,620
So,you're,uh...
ok?

93
00:05:25,650 --> 00:05:27,190
I didn't think youwere back till next week.

94
00:05:27,230 --> 00:05:29,660
Oh,um,I gota text message,so...

95
00:05:29,720 --> 00:05:31,410
then it was a mistake.

96
00:05:31,470 --> 00:05:32,340
Is there a case?

97
00:05:32,390 --> 00:05:34,770
Not untilyou're healthy.

98
00:05:34,830 --> 00:05:37,550
Yesterday I found myselflooking forward towatching a soap opera.

99
00:05:37,610 --> 00:05:38,510
Which one?

100
00:05:38,570 --> 00:05:40,540
Please,can you put meback to work,hotch?

101
00:05:40,610 --> 00:05:41,950
The doctor hasn'tcleared you forthe field.

102
00:05:42,010 --> 00:05:43,760
- Please,hotch.
- You need more time.

104
00:05:43,810 --> 00:05:45,180
I've been outfor 4 months.

105
00:05:45,220 --> 00:05:48,970
What I need is togo back to work.

106
00:05:50,430 --> 00:05:51,630
We're goingto cleveland.

107
00:05:51,700 --> 00:05:54,040
Reid's going tothe crimes againstchildren division.
Go with him.

109
00:05:54,110 --> 00:05:56,270
- But I can--
- or go home.

111
00:05:59,310 --> 00:06:02,310
I'm all yours,dr.Reid.

112
00:06:11,420 --> 00:06:16,990
The image was uploaded toone of our C.A.C.Undercoversfishing in a chat room.

113
00:06:17,010 --> 00:06:18,820
We try to monitoras many of them as we can,

114
00:06:18,880 --> 00:06:22,260
pretending tobe children,pedophiles,whatever works on that site.

115
00:06:22,310 --> 00:06:24,360
Did you run forensiclinguisticson the chat log?

116
00:06:24,440 --> 00:06:26,570
There might besomething to hugz'speech patterns.

117
00:06:26,620 --> 00:06:31,080
It doesn't really work thatway with internet talk.

118
00:06:34,870 --> 00:06:36,870
Fear of flying?

119
00:06:37,390 --> 00:06:40,930
Lengthy,deep-rootedissues of control?

120
00:06:41,980 --> 00:06:44,990
I--think better on my feet.

121
00:06:46,370 --> 00:06:48,170
Most of the talkis abbreviated text--

122
00:06:48,230 --> 00:06:52,380
L.O.L.,Laughing out loud. I.M.H.O.,,In my humble opinion.F.T.F.--

123
00:06:52,440 --> 00:06:54,030
- face to face.
- Right.

125
00:06:54,060 --> 00:06:58,460
Uh,pedophilescan be dividedinto two categories...

126
00:07:02,830 --> 00:07:05,180
situationaland preferential.

127
00:07:05,230 --> 00:07:07,480
Situational offendersrarely seek out children,

128
00:07:07,530 --> 00:07:09,940
but they'll take advantageof a situation whenpresented with it,

129
00:07:09,990 --> 00:07:17,340
whereas preferential offendersactively target childrenby age group,hair color...

130
00:07:17,400 --> 00:07:20,520
they'll seek out jobs whichgive them as much accessto children as possible.

131
00:07:20,600 --> 00:07:25,460
The often trawl aroundresidential neighborhoods,hijacking homewireless systems

132
00:07:25,520 --> 00:07:30,530
and communicatingwith childrenoften outside the veryhouse the child is in.

133
00:07:30,590 --> 00:07:35,830
Or they'll simply usea wireless coffee shopto find,locate,and arrange a meeting.

134
00:07:35,890 --> 00:07:37,110
And it's growing.

135
00:07:37,180 --> 00:07:39,970
It's growing as fastas the internet.

136
00:07:40,050 --> 00:07:42,400
They're gettingsmarter and smarter,

137
00:07:42,480 --> 00:07:47,120
and all the securityin the worldcan't stop them fromcoming through our doors.

138
00:07:47,180 --> 00:07:50,320
Hell,the monsters arealready in our homes.

139
00:07:50,400 --> 00:07:52,890
If he's had this kidfor a year,it makeshim preferential.

140
00:07:52,970 --> 00:07:54,320
Definitely.

141
00:07:54,410 --> 00:07:57,410
So,then why ishe selling him?

142
00:07:59,880 --> 00:08:02,380
Maybe,uh...
maybehe's losing interest.

144
00:08:02,430 --> 00:08:04,790
Peter's maybe gettingtoo old,too tall.

145
00:08:04,840 --> 00:08:08,290
Preferential offendersare very specificabout their preferences.

146
00:08:08,350 --> 00:08:11,430
And if he can't sell him?

147
00:08:11,470 --> 00:08:13,540
He isn't going tojust let him go.

148
00:08:13,590 --> 00:08:15,910
Hotch?

149
00:08:16,560 --> 00:08:17,260
Yeah?

150
00:08:17,310 --> 00:08:19,880
Yeah,I was thinking,shouldn't we releasepeter's picture to the media?

151
00:08:19,930 --> 00:08:21,150
No.No,no.

152
00:08:21,200 --> 00:08:25,440
If this unsub thinksthat we're on to him,he may make a run for itand dispose of the boy.

153
00:08:25,500 --> 00:08:26,870
Shouldn't we assumehe does know?

154
00:08:26,930 --> 00:08:30,600
As I said,we interceptedthis image as part ofan undercover operation.

155
00:08:30,660 --> 00:08:33,260
These predators havea fairly closed society.

156
00:08:33,320 --> 00:08:37,430
The way they run thesesites gives them theexpectation of anonymity.

157
00:08:37,490 --> 00:08:38,370
Right.

158
00:08:38,420 --> 00:08:41,200
Have reid and ellecheck the live feed.

159
00:08:41,270 --> 00:08:44,170
Not just the boy,but everythingaround him--the room.

160
00:08:44,250 --> 00:08:45,470
See if wemissed anything.

161
00:08:45,530 --> 00:08:47,160
- Ok.
- Yeah.

163
00:08:47,210 --> 00:08:48,020
Amanda gilroy.

164
00:08:48,070 --> 00:08:48,840
You're the B.A.U.?

165
00:08:48,840 --> 00:08:51,100
I'm spender reedand this isagent greenaway.

166
00:08:51,160 --> 00:08:53,050
You're the agentwho had contact withthe image of peter.

167
00:08:53,110 --> 00:08:57,010
This time.
A year ago,it was katie who firstidentified him.

169
00:08:57,040 --> 00:08:58,780
- You call her katie?
- Everyone does.

171
00:08:58,850 --> 00:09:00,570
She hatesto be called agent cole.

172
00:09:00,620 --> 00:09:01,730
Make yourselves at home.

173
00:09:01,800 --> 00:09:03,090
We just got yourwarrants approved.

174
00:09:03,160 --> 00:09:06,510
Katie and your team areabout to pay a visit tothe chat room vendor.

175
00:09:06,580 --> 00:09:09,930
Yeah.
Well,yeah.

177
00:09:09,980 --> 00:09:12,290
We went overthe probability.

178
00:09:12,380 --> 00:09:14,160
That's fine.

179
00:09:14,220 --> 00:09:16,300
Yeah.

180
00:09:16,350 --> 00:09:20,770
Yeah,one of our main onlinelisting sites is down,but we should beback online--fbi.

181
00:09:20,840 --> 00:09:22,480
We have a warrantto search these premises.

182
00:09:22,540 --> 00:09:24,530
Stop what you're doingright now.

183
00:09:24,570 --> 00:09:26,180
I'm sorry.
I gotta go.

185
00:09:26,230 --> 00:09:29,260
Can somebody tell mewho owns this place?
Ahem.

187
00:09:31,720 --> 00:09:32,980
That'd be me.

188
00:09:33,040 --> 00:09:36,740
I want access to yourchat room database.

189
00:09:42,790 --> 00:09:44,760
It looks like thewalls are padded.

190
00:09:44,830 --> 00:09:47,520
- And the dimensionsare strange.
- Strange?

192
00:09:47,580 --> 00:09:50,500
- It looks like a hall,but smaller.
- A basement?

194
00:09:50,570 --> 00:09:51,550
I don'tthink so.

195
00:09:51,620 --> 00:09:54,910
Katie just got us accessto the originalchat room's database.

196
00:09:54,970 --> 00:09:57,030
It's coming through now.

197
00:10:02,630 --> 00:10:04,680
Must be thousandsof screen names there.

198
00:10:04,740 --> 00:10:06,170
All encrypted.

199
00:10:06,180 --> 00:10:09,630
Yeah,but we're onlyconcerned about one.

200
00:10:10,260 --> 00:10:12,300
Hugz.

201
00:10:13,080 --> 00:10:15,280
This is so typical.

202
00:10:15,350 --> 00:10:16,930
You feds just can'thelp yourselves.

203
00:10:17,020 --> 00:10:19,920
You gotta pollutethe truest form of freeexpression ever invented.

204
00:10:20,010 --> 00:10:22,370
Agent find a chatroomof your choice.

205
00:10:22,450 --> 00:10:24,780
Your name is susie.
You're 12 years old.

207
00:10:24,820 --> 00:10:26,260
- What are you doing?
- Fishing.

209
00:10:26,320 --> 00:10:30,150
You know,I've got rights,and so do my clients.

210
00:10:42,570 --> 00:10:46,930
That's the soundof pedophiles lookingto hook up witha 12 year old girlnamed suzy.

211
00:10:47,000 --> 00:10:51,290
You let them runeverything throughssl connectionsfrom proxy serversin offshore countries.

212
00:10:51,360 --> 00:10:53,280
So they can't be identified?

213
00:10:53,330 --> 00:10:54,640
Not in 12 1/2 hours.

214
00:10:54,690 --> 00:10:57,280
Hey,I'm justa middleman here,ok?

215
00:10:57,330 --> 00:10:58,770
What can I do?

216
00:10:58,830 --> 00:11:02,730
There's a little boy forsale on one of your sites.

217
00:11:02,770 --> 00:11:06,100
"What can I do"just isn't good enough.

218
00:11:06,170 --> 00:11:07,340
Cole was right.

219
00:11:07,420 --> 00:11:09,800
Hugz routed throughan offshore proxy.

220
00:11:09,830 --> 00:11:11,040
So we have no wayof tracking him?

221
00:11:11,110 --> 00:11:13,400
Not if you only track himwith his address.

222
00:11:13,470 --> 00:11:15,750
What else do we have?

223
00:11:15,810 --> 00:11:21,270
He used a basicencryption programto hide hispayment method.

224
00:11:21,320 --> 00:11:25,200
And as you know,I'm anything but basic.

225
00:11:25,250 --> 00:11:28,220
Ah,gotta lovethe money traila credit card leaves.

226
00:11:28,320 --> 00:11:31,740
Well,well,well.
Graham rose,15 hauser lane,rimond,va.

228
00:11:31,800 --> 00:11:33,260
Check this out,jj.

229
00:11:33,310 --> 00:11:37,590
He used the same cardto pay for a web domain.

230
00:11:37,640 --> 00:11:40,180
Oh,my god.

231
00:11:45,170 --> 00:11:48,900
Gideon,we just foundanother child being held.

232
00:12:00,760 --> 00:12:02,620
Fbi!

233
00:12:04,320 --> 00:12:06,700
You're a bad boy.

234
00:12:08,340 --> 00:12:11,430
You needed to be tied up,didn't you?

235
00:12:13,670 --> 00:12:16,690
Let me see you struggle.

236
00:12:16,740 --> 00:12:18,860
Clear! ********

237
00:12:19,850 --> 00:12:23,980
**********

238
00:12:30,180 --> 00:12:32,060
Fbi!

239
00:12:40,910 --> 00:12:42,200
What are you doing?

240
00:12:42,250 --> 00:12:43,170
Where is he?

241
00:12:43,230 --> 00:12:45,140
Where is who?

242
00:12:49,710 --> 00:12:51,710
- It's ok.
- You're safe now.

244
00:12:51,740 --> 00:12:53,040
Safe?

245
00:12:55,330 --> 00:12:57,710
- What's your name?
- Kevin.

247
00:12:57,760 --> 00:12:59,740
The man who didthis to you.
Is he still here?

249
00:12:59,790 --> 00:13:00,900
It's my house.

250
00:13:00,930 --> 00:13:04,140
Graham rose is theowner of this house.
Where is he?

252
00:13:04,550 --> 00:13:05,920
No,no!
Don't touch that.

254
00:13:05,960 --> 00:13:06,900
Back up.

255
00:13:06,960 --> 00:13:08,900
- Where is he?
- He's gone.

257
00:13:08,960 --> 00:13:12,140
What do you mean,gone?
He's just gone,ok?

259
00:13:12,160 --> 00:13:15,430
- Graham roseis your father?
- Yeah,sure.

261
00:13:15,490 --> 00:13:17,220
You can call him that.

262
00:13:17,270 --> 00:13:19,840
I just call him a bastard.

263
00:13:35,860 --> 00:13:39,010
You scared?

264
00:13:39,060 --> 00:13:42,120
You think dad'smad at us?

265
00:13:43,350 --> 00:13:45,590
The father's been in jailfor the last 8 months.

266
00:13:45,700 --> 00:13:48,890
In that time,kevin'sbeen selling the onlything he's got,which is himself.

267
00:13:48,930 --> 00:13:51,000
Just likea street hustler.

268
00:13:51,140 --> 00:13:53,080
Only now the streetis the internet.

269
00:13:53,180 --> 00:13:55,000
And his client basespans the globe.

270
00:13:55,080 --> 00:13:58,360
Well,this kid definitelyuploaded peter's videoto the chat room,'cause it's stillon his computer.

271
00:13:58,410 --> 00:13:59,640
Yeah,but notthe live feed.

272
00:13:59,700 --> 00:14:01,260
He say how he gothold of the video?

273
00:14:01,330 --> 00:14:03,500
He said it came fromone of his clients.

274
00:14:03,540 --> 00:14:04,390
It was a shared file.

275
00:14:04,430 --> 00:14:06,020
They'd gone aroundthese chat groups.

276
00:14:06,090 --> 00:14:07,400
It's possible.

277
00:14:07,500 --> 00:14:08,480
Buyers and sellers routine.

278
00:14:08,550 --> 00:14:14,040
They trade files becausethe act in itselfis an illegal act,which proves they'renot the police.

279
00:14:14,110 --> 00:14:16,640
I'll see what elsewe can find out.

280
00:14:19,950 --> 00:14:23,950
Kid,the boy whose videoyou've been sending aroundto all the chat rooms,

281
00:14:24,010 --> 00:14:26,840
he's gonna be sold fromone pedophile to another.

282
00:14:26,900 --> 00:14:30,430
Boo-hoo.

283
00:14:32,180 --> 00:14:33,320
These are dummy logs.

284
00:14:33,390 --> 00:14:36,750
What's the passwordto get me intothe real transcriptsof your sessions?

285
00:14:36,810 --> 00:14:38,200
You're the fbi.
You figure it out.

287
00:14:38,270 --> 00:14:41,180
I know you don'tthink so,kevin,but we are tryingto help you here.

288
00:14:41,260 --> 00:14:42,820
Help me?
What I dois consensual.

290
00:14:42,880 --> 00:14:44,030
No one's getting hurt.

291
00:14:44,090 --> 00:14:45,240
Come on,kevin,what's the password?

292
00:14:45,300 --> 00:14:48,280
Your birthday?
Your favorite band?

294
00:14:48,310 --> 00:14:50,880
Kevin,this is prostitution.

295
00:14:50,950 --> 00:14:52,390
But I'm a minor.

296
00:14:52,450 --> 00:14:54,330
I don't even reallyknow what I'm doing.

297
00:14:54,390 --> 00:15:00,670
Plus I never leavethis room,so no one,no one ever touches me.

298
00:15:00,710 --> 00:15:02,710
Anymore.

299
00:15:02,760 --> 00:15:05,790
Your father's been beatingyou since you can remember.

300
00:15:05,830 --> 00:15:09,800
First it was when he wasdrunk on the weekend,then he was always drunk.

301
00:15:09,890 --> 00:15:13,050
You never knew whyhe was hurting you...

302
00:15:13,550 --> 00:15:16,620
why he was so angry.

303
00:15:16,720 --> 00:15:20,840
At night you'd cryyourself to sleep,hoping someone wouldcome and save you.

304
00:15:20,900 --> 00:15:23,200
No one ever came.

305
00:15:23,260 --> 00:15:26,460
You have the chanceto be the one whosaves someone,kevin.

306
00:15:26,530 --> 00:15:30,460
You can be the onewho answers him,the one who stopshis pain.

307
00:15:30,530 --> 00:15:35,980
You can't getto your father,but you can getto the guy who'shurting this boy.

308
00:15:42,450 --> 00:15:45,050
Move.

309
00:15:48,100 --> 00:15:51,390
This backs upall my transcripts.

310
00:15:51,440 --> 00:15:56,080
The screen name of the guy whosent me the file is mehtevas.

311
00:15:57,810 --> 00:16:00,350
Can you hear me?

312
00:16:00,400 --> 00:16:05,010
Can I get out anytime soon?
Please?

314
00:16:07,190 --> 00:16:10,500
He's got food and water,a toilet and some toys.

315
00:16:10,550 --> 00:16:12,620
He never has toleave the room.

316
00:16:13,640 --> 00:16:15,960
That's it!
It's not a room.

318
00:16:16,040 --> 00:16:17,160
A room has a door.

319
00:16:17,220 --> 00:16:18,910
Even a prisoncell has a door.

320
00:16:18,990 --> 00:16:22,290
There are no windows,so he can't be seen,and the walls are paddedso he can't be heard.

321
00:16:22,350 --> 00:16:24,250
The unsub's anticipatingbecoming a suspect.

322
00:16:24,320 --> 00:16:25,420
So he's hidden the boy.

323
00:16:25,480 --> 00:16:28,480
If there are no doors,how did he get the boyin the room?

324
00:16:28,540 --> 00:16:30,680
It's like a shipin a bottle.

325
00:16:30,770 --> 00:16:34,280
He's built the roomaround the boy.

326
00:16:35,320 --> 00:16:38,480
How long has mehtevasbeen a client of yours?

327
00:16:38,550 --> 00:16:39,980
Like,6 months.

328
00:16:40,050 --> 00:16:42,500
Where is he located?
He's a local.

330
00:16:42,550 --> 00:16:44,720
He's always askingto meet with me,but I don't do that.

331
00:16:44,780 --> 00:16:46,730
- Does he knowwhere you are?
- Just the city.

333
00:16:46,780 --> 00:16:49,280
- How do you contact him?
- He contacts me.

335
00:16:49,340 --> 00:16:50,630
Come on,kevin.

336
00:16:50,680 --> 00:16:53,480
You don't just sitaround here waitingfor these guysto look you up.

337
00:16:53,540 --> 00:16:54,810
That's no wayto run a business.

338
00:16:54,880 --> 00:16:58,860
Right now you'rethe only person whocan help us find peter.

339
00:16:58,920 --> 00:17:00,970
What do youwant me to do?

340
00:17:01,040 --> 00:17:04,240
Ask him fora face to face.

341
00:17:04,260 --> 00:17:06,330
No.
No way.I don't do that.

343
00:17:06,380 --> 00:17:08,490
- I've never beenout of this room.
- It'll be fine.

345
00:17:08,540 --> 00:17:10,060
He won'tlay a finger on you.

346
00:17:10,120 --> 00:17:12,520
We'll right there,kevin,the whole time.

347
00:17:12,600 --> 00:17:15,240
I promise you.

348
00:17:15,340 --> 00:17:17,850
Won't he be suspiciousif I suddenly wantto meet with him?

349
00:17:17,890 --> 00:17:20,440
He's a need drivenoffender,kevin.

350
00:17:20,520 --> 00:17:22,410
What does that mean?

351
00:17:22,460 --> 00:17:26,340
if you offer tomeet with him,he won't be ableto resist.

352
00:17:26,410 --> 00:17:29,060
He can't help himself.

353
00:17:48,710 --> 00:17:51,670
You said that he firstappeared a year ago,right?

354
00:17:51,730 --> 00:17:53,120
But he wasin a normal room.

355
00:17:53,150 --> 00:17:54,680
The pictures didn'tlook like that.

356
00:17:54,760 --> 00:17:57,090
Here.

357
00:18:03,470 --> 00:18:04,710
So,something changed.

358
00:18:04,760 --> 00:18:07,170
A stressor for himto lock him away.

359
00:18:07,240 --> 00:18:09,500
Hey,guys.

360
00:18:09,540 --> 00:18:11,080
What is it?

361
00:18:11,160 --> 00:18:13,420
I'm not sure.

362
00:18:14,910 --> 00:18:16,930
Wait,do you see howhe's looking off camera?

363
00:18:17,000 --> 00:18:19,200
Someone's telling himto do what he's doing.

364
00:18:19,260 --> 00:18:22,390
A bidder who must wantto see him wearing...

365
00:18:22,450 --> 00:18:25,490
wait a minute.

366
00:18:25,540 --> 00:18:27,700
That's a tadpole shirt.

367
00:18:27,740 --> 00:18:30,450
That's a tadpole shirt.
It's a wilderness group.

369
00:18:30,590 --> 00:18:34,180
Knot tying.
Compass wielding.Boy stuff.

371
00:18:34,240 --> 00:18:35,000
Are you sure?

372
00:18:35,050 --> 00:18:38,670
I have 4 brothers,jj.
They all hadthat shirt.

374
00:18:40,400 --> 00:18:43,330
Is that numberson his sleeve?

375
00:18:43,390 --> 00:18:44,970
Wait,wait,enhance it.

376
00:18:45,000 --> 00:18:48,410
Capture that imagewhen he turns.

377
00:18:48,470 --> 00:18:50,990
The badge is torn.

378
00:18:51,020 --> 00:18:53,010
It's like,4 numbers.
What is that?

380
00:18:53,070 --> 00:18:56,800
3,something,something,6?

381
00:18:56,860 --> 00:18:59,650
That's a unit number.
4 digits endingwith a 6.

383
00:18:59,670 --> 00:19:02,400
999 possiblecombinations.

384
00:19:02,430 --> 00:19:04,490
But a unit number wouldbe registered,right?

385
00:19:04,530 --> 00:19:06,000
Already on it,kid.

386
00:19:06,050 --> 00:19:08,000
- Of course you are.
- I rule.

388
00:19:09,810 --> 00:19:11,040
They're headingto alexandria.

389
00:19:11,100 --> 00:19:14,170
They want us to lookup this addressand tell themwhat's there.

390
00:19:17,560 --> 00:19:21,210
- Plowright.
- Alexandria.

392
00:19:22,150 --> 00:19:26,580
That location,it's right outside ofan elementary school.

393
00:19:26,630 --> 00:19:27,430
Where are you going?

394
00:19:27,490 --> 00:19:28,600
We can be therein 30 minutes.

395
00:19:28,650 --> 00:19:31,580
- You're not allowedto go anywhere.
- Don't even try it,reid.

397
00:19:52,590 --> 00:19:56,120
Don't you lovethat sound?

398
00:19:56,190 --> 00:19:58,820
Excuse me?

399
00:19:59,670 --> 00:20:03,790
- Children.
- Mehtevas?

401
00:20:03,870 --> 00:20:05,440
You seem nervous.

402
00:20:05,470 --> 00:20:08,940
Well,you aremehtevas,right?

403
00:20:09,650 --> 00:20:12,290
My friends call me hayden.

404
00:20:12,350 --> 00:20:16,350
Hey,you're tallerin person.

405
00:20:16,450 --> 00:20:18,230
What's the matter?
Did I say something wrong?

407
00:20:18,250 --> 00:20:21,700
Hugz?
Kevin?

409
00:20:23,630 --> 00:20:26,000
Fbi!
Turn around!

411
00:20:27,410 --> 00:20:29,430
- Agent morgan.
- I didn't do anything.

413
00:20:29,450 --> 00:20:31,960
Agent morgan,take it easy.
Take it easy.

415
00:20:32,020 --> 00:20:32,830
We need his cooperation.

416
00:20:32,880 --> 00:20:34,750
We just want to ask youa few questions.

417
00:20:34,790 --> 00:20:40,590
Here's a question.What's the principalof a schooldoing hooking up witha 14 year old boy?

418
00:20:42,240 --> 00:20:45,000
Let's go.********

419
00:20:47,260 --> 00:20:51,480
Katie,social servicesis picking up kevinat the alexandriafield office.

420
00:20:51,540 --> 00:20:52,750
I'm going to gowith him.

421
00:20:52,840 --> 00:20:55,310
I'll be backas soon as I can.

422
00:20:58,380 --> 00:21:02,080
- Are you ok?
- Yeah.I,uh...

424
00:21:02,980 --> 00:21:04,150
yeah.

425
00:21:06,230 --> 00:21:08,840
Hotch.
You already got him?

427
00:21:08,900 --> 00:21:10,160
I told you to stayout of the field.

428
00:21:10,210 --> 00:21:12,120
Yeah,I know.
But reid said thatyou wanted us here.

430
00:21:12,160 --> 00:21:13,400
- No,I didn'T.
- Yes,you did.

432
00:21:13,440 --> 00:21:16,140
- I'm sure you didn't,reid.
- Thanks.

434
00:21:16,190 --> 00:21:18,770
The school district hasgiven us permission tosearch rawlings' office.

435
00:21:18,800 --> 00:21:22,070
I'm on it.*********

436
00:21:33,840 --> 00:21:35,800
Principal of a school.

437
00:21:35,870 --> 00:21:39,020
As much access tochildren as possible.

438
00:21:39,040 --> 00:21:42,440
Growing up guidefor parents.

439
00:21:44,400 --> 00:21:47,880
He's got a library ofchild psychology.

440
00:21:49,570 --> 00:21:52,000
He's got adoctorate in it.

441
00:21:52,070 --> 00:21:54,490
Well prepared pedophile.

442
00:21:55,710 --> 00:21:58,660
- Elle,you noticeanything missing?
- Computer.

444
00:22:03,310 --> 00:22:08,200
Family man,so,if he does have peter,he's not keeping him at home.

445
00:22:11,310 --> 00:22:13,470
Elle,this one's locked.

446
00:22:16,560 --> 00:22:18,300
Hey,move.

447
00:22:19,550 --> 00:22:22,550
Did they teach youthat in fbi school?

448
00:22:23,420 --> 00:22:26,160
No,they taught methat in brooklyn.

449
00:22:30,180 --> 00:22:33,440
I wish you would informme what exactly I'mbeing charged with.

450
00:22:33,500 --> 00:22:35,210
Anything I canpossibly stick to you.

451
00:22:35,330 --> 00:22:36,560
I haven't done anything.

452
00:22:36,630 --> 00:22:38,550
You're an educatedman,mr.Rawlings.

453
00:22:38,610 --> 00:22:39,910
You know you'rein trouble here.

454
00:22:39,980 --> 00:22:41,760
I believe I just walkedoutside my school.

455
00:22:41,820 --> 00:22:43,280
Is that a crime now?

456
00:22:43,320 --> 00:22:45,500
You knowwhere he is?

457
00:22:48,880 --> 00:22:51,770
How could anyonehurt something so...

458
00:22:52,280 --> 00:22:54,430
pure?

459
00:22:55,660 --> 00:22:58,360
You sent thisimage to kevin.

460
00:22:59,160 --> 00:23:02,980
Well,that was wrongof me,I know,but I was so shocked.

461
00:23:03,070 --> 00:23:05,500
I wanted to try to savethis poor boy.

462
00:23:05,560 --> 00:23:09,980
I thought hugz--kevin--might know him.

463
00:23:10,050 --> 00:23:12,470
That's why I sent himthe link to the website,see if he knew.

464
00:23:12,510 --> 00:23:14,910
Please.
You weretrying to save him?

466
00:23:14,930 --> 00:23:17,140
Help search his office.

467
00:23:18,160 --> 00:23:20,090
I got this.

468
00:23:31,360 --> 00:23:34,230
How were you goingto save peter?

469
00:23:34,280 --> 00:23:38,650
Peter?
Is that his name?Peter?

471
00:23:38,700 --> 00:23:40,780
I wanted to save themboth.

472
00:23:40,820 --> 00:23:43,330
Kevin,too.

473
00:23:45,260 --> 00:23:47,090
Sit down.

474
00:23:57,720 --> 00:23:59,940
Tell me we gotsomething we can nailthe son of a bitch on.

475
00:24:00,000 --> 00:24:02,700
Not unless we canbreak the passwordon this guy'scomputer.

476
00:24:02,760 --> 00:24:04,810
- Call garcia.
- Take too long.

478
00:24:04,850 --> 00:24:06,290
Come on,genius.

479
00:24:06,360 --> 00:24:08,480
Do somethinggenius-like.

480
00:24:08,520 --> 00:24:14,810
If this guy doeshave child pornographyon his computerand we type inthe wrong password,it could triggera virus that wipesthe entire hard drive.

481
00:24:14,870 --> 00:24:16,240
What's he saying out there?

482
00:24:16,290 --> 00:24:19,370
He's a preferentialpedophilewho claims he'strying to save theM.

483
00:24:20,450 --> 00:24:23,290
Save them.
Save--

485
00:24:41,630 --> 00:24:43,490
Mehtevas.

486
00:24:48,690 --> 00:24:50,460
Can you getany closer?

487
00:24:50,510 --> 00:24:53,260
I can,but it'll distortthe image even more.

488
00:24:53,340 --> 00:24:58,760
There,see,the edgeof his badge,it looks like itsays "mount" something.

489
00:24:58,830 --> 00:25:00,300
Ok.

490
00:25:00,360 --> 00:25:05,910
There are 4 unitdesignations,allstarting with mount.

491
00:25:05,950 --> 00:25:09,270
Mount clements,minnesota,2346.

492
00:25:09,340 --> 00:25:11,700
Mount vernon,new york,2436.

493
00:25:11,750 --> 00:25:14,580
Mount pleasant,virginia,3446.
That's it,right?

495
00:25:14,620 --> 00:25:16,360
Yeah.
Yeah,yeah,good one.

497
00:25:25,860 --> 00:25:30,040
Mr.Rawlings,have a seat.

498
00:25:32,380 --> 00:25:34,190
Your laptop.

499
00:25:37,460 --> 00:25:39,350
Yeah,it's morgan.

500
00:25:39,390 --> 00:25:41,940
Ok,hold on,garcia.
Hold on.

502
00:25:43,850 --> 00:25:47,740
It's,uh,research.
I'm writing a book.

504
00:25:47,790 --> 00:25:49,340
Sit down.

505
00:25:56,970 --> 00:25:59,150
I swear to you thisis all just research.

506
00:25:59,200 --> 00:26:00,350
It's not research.

507
00:26:00,400 --> 00:26:04,070
It's 100 years in afederal penitentiary.

508
00:26:08,110 --> 00:26:10,300
I'd like to make a deal.

509
00:26:11,070 --> 00:26:13,210
No deals.

510
00:26:13,260 --> 00:26:16,820
All you have is a very,verysmall amount of good will.

511
00:26:16,900 --> 00:26:19,530
Tell me about peter.

512
00:26:20,720 --> 00:26:23,780
I was contacted by theman who was holding him.

513
00:26:23,860 --> 00:26:25,720
I didn't search outthis boy.

514
00:26:25,780 --> 00:26:28,340
- I didn't go lookingfor this.
- Give me a name.

516
00:26:28,390 --> 00:26:30,570
Well,I only knowthe screen name.

517
00:26:30,590 --> 00:26:32,630
It's manchild.

518
00:26:32,660 --> 00:26:35,530
Did you bid on peter?

519
00:26:36,010 --> 00:26:38,860
How much?

520
00:26:38,920 --> 00:26:41,460
$8,000.

521
00:26:41,510 --> 00:26:43,720
But it was onlyin order to save him.

522
00:26:43,770 --> 00:26:44,900
You the high bidder?

523
00:26:44,950 --> 00:26:47,280
I--I think so,yes.

524
00:26:47,340 --> 00:26:48,640
I was,anyway.

525
00:26:48,710 --> 00:26:53,660
I was supposed to goback onlineand contact himon his web siteand get the address.

526
00:26:53,690 --> 00:26:56,200
So you can inspectthe merchandise?

527
00:26:56,260 --> 00:27:00,620
Look,this child isbeing auctioned off,and I am tryingto save him.

528
00:27:00,680 --> 00:27:02,530
Trying to save him.

529
00:27:02,570 --> 00:27:04,540
He'd have given you a code.
What is it?

531
00:27:04,590 --> 00:27:07,240
Come on.

532
00:27:07,290 --> 00:27:09,900
I have a family.
I have childrenof my own.

534
00:27:09,960 --> 00:27:13,190
I love children.I would never harm them.

535
00:27:13,240 --> 00:27:20,170
In your pursuitto save them,you think you could haveavoided having sex with them?

536
00:27:21,090 --> 00:27:23,480
Mr.Rawlings.

537
00:27:24,170 --> 00:27:27,650
The code.

538
00:27:34,930 --> 00:27:37,470
Butterfly.

539
00:27:46,020 --> 00:27:48,430
Dad?

540
00:27:50,410 --> 00:27:53,720
Dad?
When can I come out?

542
00:27:53,760 --> 00:27:55,620
I'm being a good boy.

543
00:27:55,670 --> 00:27:56,930
- In live breaking news...
- shut up...

545
00:27:56,930 --> 00:28:02,440
The fbi's crimescontrol unit and localauthorities have arrestedmark twain elementary schoolprincipal

546
00:28:02,500 --> 00:28:07,520
hayden rawlings today in what sources sayis a sting operationtargeting what may be

547
00:28:07,590 --> 00:28:10,820
oneof the largest pedophile ringsthis country has ever seen.

548
00:28:10,890 --> 00:28:15,670
Both agencies have declinedto comment on the arrestat this time,or give any details of the case,

549
00:28:15,730 --> 00:28:19,980
but it is rumored to beconnected to the investigationof a child pornography ring.

550
00:28:20,040 --> 00:28:24,490
Experts in law enforcementknow that the explosionof social networking sites

551
00:28:24,540 --> 00:28:27,190
- on the internetare a favorite huntinggrounds...
- Hello,agent cole.

553
00:28:33,280 --> 00:28:35,140
- What happened?
- I don't know.

555
00:28:35,170 --> 00:28:37,480
He broke contact.

556
00:28:42,080 --> 00:28:44,770
- What happened?
- The entire feedjust went dark.

558
00:28:44,820 --> 00:28:47,010
Get Hotch on the phone.

559
00:28:47,090 --> 00:28:48,700
We got reporters outsideof the schools.

560
00:28:48,760 --> 00:28:50,490
This thing isall over the news.

561
00:28:50,530 --> 00:28:53,690
My god,that's why the sitewent down.
He knows.

563
00:29:07,730 --> 00:29:09,390
She's sure aboutthis,right?

564
00:29:09,460 --> 00:29:13,210
If garcia says thattadpoles shirt camefrom a unit inmount pleasant,then I gotta believe her.

565
00:29:13,260 --> 00:29:17,360
She better be.Mount pleasantis 60 miles awayand there's onlytwo hours left onthe auction clock.

566
00:29:17,410 --> 00:29:18,910
Maybe.

567
00:29:18,940 --> 00:29:22,960
If the unsubknows we're on to him,he may movethat clock up.

568
00:29:25,880 --> 00:29:28,060
Think this guy'sgonna panic?

569
00:29:28,130 --> 00:29:30,280
I don't know.
Depends on hiscomfort level.

571
00:29:30,340 --> 00:29:33,560
Maybe getting closeto auction time,he can wait it out.

572
00:29:33,630 --> 00:29:36,380
I know one thing: Ican't lose peter again.

573
00:29:36,420 --> 00:29:38,360
Well,let's justhope jj bought ussome time.

574
00:29:38,410 --> 00:29:39,990
Mary,I need a favor.

575
00:29:40,040 --> 00:29:44,170
It's absolutelyall right that youbroadcast this.

576
00:29:44,230 --> 00:29:47,690
We have to bluffthis kid's captorinto believing we arein another locale.

577
00:29:47,730 --> 00:29:48,690
It will buy us time.

578
00:29:48,740 --> 00:29:51,780
This kid's lifedepends on it.
Ok,this is a lie.

580
00:29:51,820 --> 00:29:56,960
Say the crimesagainst children unitis searching fora boy being heldcaptive in virginia.

581
00:29:57,020 --> 00:30:01,850
He's approximately4 feet tall,he has brown hair.

582
00:30:01,910 --> 00:30:04,970
We need you to get thison the air immediately.

583
00:30:05,020 --> 00:30:06,130
Thank you.

584
00:30:06,170 --> 00:30:10,310
The fbi has informed usthat they are looking fora missing 7 year old child.

585
00:30:10,340 --> 00:30:14,510
This child is believedto be somewhere withinalexandria right now.

586
00:30:14,560 --> 00:30:19,070
A door to door searchis being coordinatedby the members of the crimesagainst children unit.

587
00:30:19,150 --> 00:30:24,250
The boy is described asapproximately 3 feet tallwith sandy brown hair.

588
00:30:26,770 --> 00:30:28,540
Jj,it's back.

589
00:30:28,610 --> 00:30:30,840
Uh,we got itback up,hotch.

590
00:30:30,920 --> 00:30:34,860
We got an hour tillthe auction closes.

591
00:30:39,040 --> 00:30:41,600
The site went dark fora few minutes and thencame back online.

592
00:30:41,680 --> 00:30:44,160
So he believes the storyjj fed to the media.

593
00:30:44,250 --> 00:30:45,710
But we've only gotan hour left.

594
00:30:45,750 --> 00:30:46,840
RighT.

595
00:30:46,900 --> 00:30:49,000
Tadpoles areaffiliated with a church.

596
00:30:49,050 --> 00:30:51,220
When we getto mount pleasant,elle and morganshould go to the church.

597
00:30:51,270 --> 00:30:52,860
We'll take the school.

598
00:30:52,910 --> 00:30:54,210
Peter may beregistered there.

599
00:30:54,230 --> 00:30:55,610
That sounds good.

600
00:30:55,680 --> 00:30:57,580
I gave up on him.

601
00:30:58,260 --> 00:31:00,120
A year ago,I gave upon looking for him.

602
00:31:00,190 --> 00:31:01,590
There were so manyother kids.

603
00:31:01,660 --> 00:31:04,010
Katie,I'm sure youdid what you could.

604
00:31:05,010 --> 00:31:08,630
You ever ask yourselfhow you make a decisionlike that?

605
00:31:08,690 --> 00:31:12,280
How we come tothe conclusionthat it's time to moveon to the next kid.

606
00:31:12,350 --> 00:31:15,270
How do you give yourselfthat kind of permission?

607
00:31:15,770 --> 00:31:19,790
What's happened tothat boy in the year istopped looking for him?

608
00:31:32,490 --> 00:31:34,310
Recognize him?

609
00:31:34,340 --> 00:31:35,870
Can't say that I do.

610
00:31:35,940 --> 00:31:39,760
But you're certainthat the shirt camefrom this unit ofthe tadpoles,right?

611
00:31:39,780 --> 00:31:43,920
It disbanded6 months ago,before i took overthe congregation.

612
00:31:43,970 --> 00:31:45,460
Why?

613
00:31:45,550 --> 00:31:47,470
I was told therewasn't enough interest.

614
00:31:47,540 --> 00:31:49,800
Only a few boysparticipated.

615
00:31:53,040 --> 00:31:55,740
Do you have the recordsof those who did participate?

616
00:31:55,800 --> 00:31:57,760
How could anyonedo this to a child?

617
00:31:59,830 --> 00:32:02,400
We need to find this boy.

618
00:32:02,440 --> 00:32:03,810
The records.

619
00:32:03,860 --> 00:32:05,500
I'm sorry.

620
00:32:05,540 --> 00:32:07,760
I don't think so.

621
00:32:08,190 --> 00:32:09,980
Wait.

622
00:32:10,020 --> 00:32:13,530
There may be a photoof the tadpoles.

623
00:32:19,040 --> 00:32:21,010
This boy's ina terrible state.

624
00:32:21,050 --> 00:32:23,380
But do yourecognize him?
Please look carefully.

626
00:32:23,410 --> 00:32:25,190
You said his appearancemay have been altered?

627
00:32:25,210 --> 00:32:27,710
First or secondgrade student.

628
00:32:28,060 --> 00:32:30,530
Let me check my records.

629
00:32:33,180 --> 00:32:35,920
This may be whatyou're looking for.

630
00:32:39,380 --> 00:32:41,980
Yeah,that's himright there.

631
00:32:42,470 --> 00:32:44,350
Is there a name,address,anything?

632
00:32:44,380 --> 00:32:46,370
As I said,there areno records left.

633
00:32:46,410 --> 00:32:49,100
The church was run prettysloppily until I took over.

634
00:32:49,130 --> 00:32:51,540
Let me see that.

635
00:32:56,040 --> 00:32:58,780
His name's charlie.

636
00:32:59,200 --> 00:33:01,590
This is everyonewho registered forthe second grade.

637
00:33:01,660 --> 00:33:02,600
That's a lotof names.

638
00:33:02,640 --> 00:33:04,290
What about the kidswho didn't register?

639
00:33:04,350 --> 00:33:04,920
Excuse me?

640
00:33:05,000 --> 00:33:07,910
Were there anyfirst graderswho didn't registerfor second grade?

641
00:33:07,970 --> 00:33:10,900
I imagine therewere some transfers.

642
00:33:16,390 --> 00:33:19,490
Yes.
Yes,therewere two transfers.

644
00:33:19,730 --> 00:33:23,120
Ashley watersand charlie sparks.

645
00:33:23,180 --> 00:33:24,110
Charlie sparks.

646
00:33:24,150 --> 00:33:25,930
Does it say wherecharlie's records went?

647
00:33:25,970 --> 00:33:27,450
His father pickedthem up himself.

648
00:33:27,490 --> 00:33:28,620
Can you describethe father?

649
00:33:28,670 --> 00:33:30,830
Oh,dear,no.
I'd have no idea.

651
00:33:30,880 --> 00:33:33,840
- Thank you.
- The end of the school yearhere is so very hectic.

653
00:33:33,910 --> 00:33:36,730
We have children from--

654
00:33:47,850 --> 00:33:50,050
the name the schoolhas is charlie sparks.

655
00:33:50,110 --> 00:33:51,900
No sparks in any ofthe phone directories.

656
00:33:51,940 --> 00:33:55,330
Garcia can't even finda sparks within 100 milesfor the last 10 years.

657
00:33:55,400 --> 00:33:56,850
Probably not hisreal name anyway.

658
00:33:56,890 --> 00:33:58,970
The school said hemay have moved away.

659
00:33:59,050 --> 00:34:00,550
Then we startover again.

660
00:34:00,590 --> 00:34:02,300
We don't havea lot of time left.

661
00:34:02,350 --> 00:34:04,870
Guys,maybe we're lookingat this the wrong way.

662
00:34:04,930 --> 00:34:05,590
What do you mean?

663
00:34:05,640 --> 00:34:07,250
The behavior,it's odd,right?

664
00:34:07,300 --> 00:34:11,610
The unsub apparentlylisted this kid in schooland the tadpolesuntil about a year ago.

665
00:34:11,650 --> 00:34:15,150
At that point he hadpictures of him onlinein a regular looking room.

666
00:34:15,210 --> 00:34:19,860
But now he's ina prison-like roomwith no windows,no doors,completely hidden.

667
00:34:19,920 --> 00:34:21,790
Preferential pedophilesdon't change overnight.

668
00:34:21,830 --> 00:34:24,880
So,what happened a yearago to make him changehis behavior so much?

669
00:34:24,960 --> 00:34:26,630
Fear.

670
00:34:27,450 --> 00:34:29,490
Katie almost caught him.

671
00:34:29,520 --> 00:34:30,520
You probablytalked to him.

672
00:34:30,590 --> 00:34:32,710
The unsub'sin your records.

673
00:34:43,970 --> 00:34:47,490
Guys,we justran out of time.
oh,sorry.
I used all of his change...
for the new 99?
kfc ultimate cheese snacker!
Kfc snackers now comewith cheese?
!
And they're still only 99?
Alright!
Looks like we gota snacker backer here!
Introducing the newultimate cheese snackerfrom kfc.
100% chicken breastsmothered in a blendof cheddar and swiss,topped with crisp lettuce,freshly preparedon a sesame seed bun.
And like the originalkfc snacker,it's only 99?
Now your dollar goes furtherat kfc.
Ky touch...
warming body massage...
and personal lubricant.
K-y touch massage,the only body massageand personal lubricant...
that warms on contact.
Ky touch massage.
[ Woman giggles ](Girl) what's that?
New glade light show.
Mom got it for me.
it's a glade air freshener,and mom got it for youbecause your room stinks.
Really?
Yeah.
She got one for you too.
(Female announcer)new glade light show.
See it,smell it,love it.
Sc johnson,a family company.

703
00:35:15,830 --> 00:35:17,890
Dad!

704
00:35:17,940 --> 00:35:19,920
Dad!

705
00:35:32,400 --> 00:35:34,200
Dad?

706
00:35:38,260 --> 00:35:39,520
I never reallyhad a good suspect.

707
00:35:39,570 --> 00:35:42,640
I only did somegeneral interviewswith child offenderson the east coast.

708
00:35:42,720 --> 00:35:44,190
One of them wasthe right guy.

709
00:35:44,260 --> 00:35:45,300
Amanda,hey.

710
00:35:45,360 --> 00:35:49,620
Uh,I need youto pull all ofthe original fileson peter's case.

711
00:35:49,670 --> 00:35:52,130
Somewherein my office.
Try my desk.

713
00:35:52,180 --> 00:35:54,880
I need the names ofeveryone I interviewed.

714
00:35:54,910 --> 00:35:56,530
Have her callpenelope garciaat the B.A.U.

715
00:35:56,590 --> 00:35:58,620
She'll be able to tell usif we can cross any off.

716
00:35:58,660 --> 00:36:00,420
You got it?
Thanks.

718
00:36:07,310 --> 00:36:09,130
- You still there?
- Yeah.

720
00:36:18,880 --> 00:36:20,840
Oh,oh,oh,
Got it,got it,got it.

722
00:36:21,690 --> 00:36:27,040
Ok,uh,frank portwell,dob 11 april 1962.

723
00:36:27,840 --> 00:36:29,640
He's doing 12 yearsin westover prison.

724
00:36:29,680 --> 00:36:32,920
Martin devries,dob 20 november '70.

725
00:36:32,980 --> 00:36:36,250
Got a death certificatefor him.
Shot on the streetlast january.

727
00:36:36,310 --> 00:36:37,870
All righT.

728
00:36:38,370 --> 00:36:42,090
Michael earlson,dob...

729
00:36:58,690 --> 00:37:01,400
garcia,you're sure?

730
00:37:01,430 --> 00:37:03,740
Ok,no.No,no.
I got it all.I got it all.

732
00:37:03,790 --> 00:37:06,780
All right,thanks,baby.
You're the best.

734
00:37:06,840 --> 00:37:08,950
All right,guys.Listen up.
We might have something.

736
00:37:08,990 --> 00:37:10,310
12 men were interviewed.

737
00:37:10,370 --> 00:37:12,790
8 are back in prison,one is dead.

738
00:37:12,840 --> 00:37:20,130
One lives in california,and two have lastknown addresses within10 minutes of us--a patrick forestand a michael earlson.

739
00:37:20,170 --> 00:37:22,530
Patrick forest isn'tsmart enough to putthis all together.

740
00:37:22,570 --> 00:37:25,210
- What aboutmichael earlson?
- Definitely.

742
00:38:19,540 --> 00:38:24,620
Where are you going?********. don't move!

743
00:38:54,390 --> 00:38:55,960
Daddy!

744
00:38:56,270 --> 00:38:58,430
it's okay,it's okay.

745
00:38:58,480 --> 00:39:00,170
daddy!

746
00:39:00,990 --> 00:39:03,370
you're save now. i got you,i got you.

747
00:39:03,410 --> 00:39:05,370
where's daddy?

748
00:39:05,670 --> 00:39:07,340
I know.

749
00:39:26,560 --> 00:39:29,360
Peter's real name is *********.

750
00:39:29,430 --> 00:39:34,370
*** adopted him in north new jersy when he was****

751
00:39:35,620 --> 00:39:40,100
sometimes it's the same as ****** punishment enough.

752
00:39:40,190 --> 00:39:43,170
jj chases his mother.

753
00:39:43,220 --> 00:39:45,710
- she's on her way.
- okay.

755
00:39:48,360 --> 00:39:52,820
you know katie,no one has ever done the job you are doing as long as you are doing it.

756
00:39:56,110 --> 00:39:57,790
I know.

757
00:39:59,590 --> 00:40:03,340
maybe it's time to get out.

758
00:40:03,390 --> 00:40:07,440
I don't know if I can anymore.

759
00:40:16,060 --> 00:40:18,340
I just can't thank you all enough.

760
00:40:18,380 --> 00:40:20,210
remember what I told you.

761
00:40:20,250 --> 00:40:23,930
here's ****** say hello but,

762
00:40:24,000 --> 00:40:27,210
does anything about being his mother that'll just scare and confuse him.

763
00:40:27,260 --> 00:40:28,150
okay.

764
00:40:28,210 --> 00:40:29,750
It's gonna be a long process.

765
00:40:29,790 --> 00:40:30,650
I'll have to ******

766
00:40:30,670 --> 00:40:32,960
****** this way.

767
00:41:11,960 --> 00:41:14,390
What's his name?

768
00:41:14,800 --> 00:41:17,150
His name's jack.

769
00:41:17,220 --> 00:41:20,730
He's a soldier.
He protects me.

771
00:41:23,800 --> 00:41:26,730
It's nice tomeet you,jack.

772
00:41:26,790 --> 00:41:29,190
My name is jackie.

773
00:41:29,780 --> 00:41:33,920
- Really?
- Really.

775
00:41:35,390 --> 00:41:37,820
Can I see jack?

776
00:41:39,760 --> 00:41:42,500
be Careful.

777
00:41:43,000 --> 00:41:45,550
<font color=#38B0DE>-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents</font>

778
00:41:45,610 --> 00:41:48,740
<font color=#38B0DE>Sync: YTET-colleen3684
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-</font>

779
00:41:48,820 --> 00:41:51,570
<font color=#38B0DE>Criminal Minds
Season 2 Episode 02</font>
