1
00:00:04,040 --> 00:00:05,780
*Don't you even think about it!

2
00:00:07,080 --> 00:00:08,180
Back it up.

3
00:00:17,300 --> 00:00:18,350
Everybody,down!

4
00:00:18,800 --> 00:00:20,020
Everybody,down!

5
00:00:34,300 --> 00:00:35,420
I said watch it.

6
00:00:39,990 --> 00:00:41,270
I said watch it!

7
00:00:51,690 --> 00:00:54,630
Please,don'T.

8
00:00:59,060 --> 00:01:00,120
Over the past 2 months,

9
00:01:00,120 --> 00:01:04,680
the L.A. Field office has been tracking a series 
of 4 bank robberies in the L.A. Metro area.

10
00:01:04,950 --> 00:01:06,680
It's one individual wearing a black ski mask.

11
00:01:06,680 --> 00:01:07,280
He's highly skilled.

12
00:01:07,280 --> 00:01:08,350
It's his unique M.O.

13
00:01:08,660 --> 00:01:12,150
That put him squarely in our court.

14
00:01:12,400 --> 00:01:13,450
This happened 2 days ago.

15
00:01:17,730 --> 00:01:18,860
He's making them undress?

16
00:01:19,240 --> 00:01:21,200
He takes their clothes and locks them in the vault,

17
00:01:21,410 --> 00:01:22,600
then he goes for the cash.

18
00:01:22,970 --> 00:01:23,660
Smart.

19
00:01:24,080 --> 00:01:25,560
Nobody's going to run after him buck-naked.

20
00:01:25,850 --> 00:01:27,990
It's also a psychological advantage.

21
00:01:28,310 --> 00:01:30,510
Make the captives feel exposed,intimidated,

22
00:01:30,770 --> 00:01:32,200
and much less likely to fight back.

23
00:01:32,390 --> 00:01:34,100
That,and the mac-10 he's waving around.

24
00:01:34,570 --> 00:01:35,800
Boy's got a lot of firepower.

25
00:01:36,090 --> 00:01:37,460
But why is this case for us?

26
00:01:37,550 --> 00:01:39,710
Because in the last robbery,2 things changed.

27
00:01:39,880 --> 00:01:42,420
1,he beat the security guard nearly senseless,

28
00:01:43,940 --> 00:01:45,690
and 2,after he made everyone undress,

29
00:01:45,860 --> 00:01:48,620
he forced 2 pairs of victims together at gunpoint,

30
00:01:48,880 --> 00:01:50,990
then he made them simulate sex with each other.

31
00:01:54,880 --> 00:01:55,700
Whoa.

32
00:01:55,780 --> 00:01:57,060
It's remarkable.

33
00:01:57,190 --> 00:01:58,790
By utilizing your practical M.O.

34
00:01:58,790 --> 00:02:00,800
The subject has stumbled on to a psychological signature.

35
00:02:00,900 --> 00:02:01,700
It's fascinating.

36
00:02:01,970 --> 00:02:03,340
He's a sex offender now.

37
00:02:03,430 --> 00:02:04,970
Fueled by violent rage.

38
00:02:06,350 --> 00:02:07,800
Only our unsub doesn't know it yet.

39
00:02:07,970 --> 00:02:10,030
If he did,he wouldn't be robbing banks anymore.

40
00:02:20,080 --> 00:02:22,020
So,he's a violent sex offender in denial.

41
00:02:22,210 --> 00:02:23,340
And a sexual predator.

42
00:02:23,340 --> 00:02:24,950
Who's just escalated his crimes.

43
00:02:25,380 --> 00:02:27,080
He's a serial killer in the making.

44
00:02:31,700 --> 00:02:36,620
criminal minds Season 02 Episode 04

45
00:02:38,160 --> 00:02:43,850
SYNC:YTET-cauorr -=bbs.ydy.com=-

46
00:02:45,550 --> 00:02:52,350
--------------------------  bbs.ydy.com Proudly Presents  --------------------------

47
00:03:07,650 --> 00:03:09,140
Hey,what are you doing here?

48
00:03:09,750 --> 00:03:12,200
Your cell phone kept going straight to voicemail.

49
00:03:12,200 --> 00:03:13,420
Yeah,no,I was in a meeting.

50
00:03:14,570 --> 00:03:15,610
Is everything all right?

51
00:03:16,450 --> 00:03:17,390
Going out of town?

52
00:03:17,620 --> 00:03:18,500
Yeah,we're going to L.A.

53
00:03:18,840 --> 00:03:20,010
I was going to call you from the car.

54
00:03:22,950 --> 00:03:23,760
What is it?

55
00:03:24,200 --> 00:03:25,520
You really don't know why I'm here?

56
00:03:26,850 --> 00:03:27,810
Honey,I'm sorry,

57
00:03:28,030 --> 00:03:29,070
we're running late.

58
00:03:31,440 --> 00:03:33,190
I just got back from the hospital.

59
00:03:34,010 --> 00:03:35,030
Jack?

60
00:03:35,130 --> 00:03:36,460
Oh,my god,the tests.

61
00:03:40,250 --> 00:03:41,970
What happened?

62
00:03:41,970 --> 00:03:43,250
He's got a condition.

63
00:03:44,260 --> 00:03:46,470
It's treatable and he's going to be ok.

64
00:03:47,780 --> 00:03:48,800
Honey,I'm sorry.

65
00:03:51,500 --> 00:03:52,370
How was he?

66
00:03:52,890 --> 00:03:54,110
Scared.

67
00:03:54,890 --> 00:03:56,220
You know,they put those electrodes all over him

68
00:03:56,220 --> 00:03:57,870
and he was wondering where his daddy was.

69
00:04:01,770 --> 00:04:03,590
-Babe,you promised you'd be there. -I know.

70
00:04:03,610 --> 00:04:04,730
I'm sorry.

71
00:04:08,940 --> 00:04:10,010
Where is he now?

72
00:04:10,240 --> 00:04:12,010
At home with my mom 

73
00:04:12,850 --> 00:04:14,750
I didn't want him here while we were talking.

74
00:04:15,670 --> 00:04:17,840
Look,I know this job is important to you,

75
00:04:18,680 --> 00:04:20,500
but we're important,too.

76
00:04:20,500 --> 00:04:21,480
You don't have to tell me that.

77
00:04:23,210 --> 00:04:26,910
I don't want you to wake up some day in some random city

78
00:04:27,110 --> 00:04:29,110
and realize that you don't know your own son.

79
00:04:32,960 --> 00:04:34,490
They can go without me.

80
00:04:35,970 --> 00:04:37,520
No,they can'T.

81
00:04:38,480 --> 00:04:39,730
It's ok.

82
00:04:40,330 --> 00:04:41,480
Go.

83
00:04:41,780 --> 00:04:42,970
We'll talk about it when you get home.

84
00:04:45,170 --> 00:04:46,530
I'm so sorry.

85
00:04:54,870 --> 00:04:55,850
sorry

86
00:05:03,410 --> 00:05:06,020
"Man is least himself when he talks in his own person.

87
00:05:06,900 --> 00:05:09,570
Give him a mask and he will tell you the truth."

88
00:05:09,670 --> 00:05:11,230
Oscar wilde.

89
00:05:12,100 --> 00:05:13,820
"Stripping bandiT."

90
00:05:14,270 --> 00:05:17,230
That's terrible.That makes it sound like the bandit's doing the stripping.

91
00:05:17,560 --> 00:05:18,410
What would you call him?

92
00:05:18,580 --> 00:05:19,430
Pervert.

93
00:05:19,430 --> 00:05:20,370
Scumbag.

94
00:05:20,370 --> 00:05:22,010
-I'd call him an ass -hey,focus,please.

95
00:05:22,360 --> 00:05:25,030
We have the details of the 4 bank robberies to learn before we get to los angeles.

96
00:05:25,320 --> 00:05:28,390
At this point is he more a bank robber or a sex offender?

97
00:05:28,390 --> 00:05:30,620
Seriously.What's he going to do next,rob a bank or rape somebody?

98
00:05:30,830 --> 00:05:31,910
I'd say we need to know more about 

99
00:05:31,910 --> 00:05:34,730
how he robs the banks and who he chooses to victimize.

100
00:05:34,730 --> 00:05:36,240
Why these banks and why these victims?

101
00:05:36,430 --> 00:05:39,190
Pairing these specific people together is a fantasy.

102
00:05:40,220 --> 00:05:41,780
If we can figure out the nature of that fantasy,

103
00:05:41,780 --> 00:05:43,720
we may be able to predict his targets.

104
00:05:45,090 --> 00:05:45,980
Hmm.

105
00:05:45,980 --> 00:05:49,320
In the last robbery I don't see any photos of what he made the victims actually do.

106
00:05:49,460 --> 00:05:51,090
There is a problem with this surveillance system.

107
00:05:51,090 --> 00:05:52,210
We're working on it.

108
00:05:52,320 --> 00:05:54,300
We should hit the ground running.How should we break it down?

109
00:05:54,300 --> 00:05:55,460
There's got to be a pattern to the banks.

110
00:05:55,460 --> 00:05:57,750
We should run a geographical profile.

111
00:05:57,870 --> 00:05:58,570
It's yours.

112
00:05:58,960 --> 00:05:59,780
And for the sexual aspects,

113
00:05:59,780 --> 00:06:02,050
we need to look at the specific victimology.

114
00:06:02,050 --> 00:06:03,520
You and I can go with the victim reports,

115
00:06:03,520 --> 00:06:05,320
see whatever surveillance footage they got.

116
00:06:05,320 --> 00:06:06,750
We'll need the unsub himself.

117
00:06:06,750 --> 00:06:08,420
We'll need his perspective.

118
00:06:09,970 --> 00:06:11,030
Crime scene.

119
00:06:41,470 --> 00:06:43,340
The suspect entered around 2:00 P.M.

120
00:06:43,590 --> 00:06:45,470
And a witness said he saw a man on a motorcycle

121
00:06:45,680 --> 00:06:48,770
with a backpack speed by a few minutes after the robbery.

122
00:06:49,330 --> 00:06:50,710
Freeway's just a few blocks that way,right?

123
00:06:50,930 --> 00:06:53,040
Actually,we're in a half-mile of 3 freeways.

124
00:06:53,220 --> 00:06:54,350
This is a perfect location.

125
00:06:54,790 --> 00:06:56,450
If he's on a bike,he's got no trouble getting out of here.

126
00:06:56,670 --> 00:06:58,320
Well,first he's got to get to his bike.

127
00:06:59,490 --> 00:07:00,470
Where's it parked?

128
00:07:00,800 --> 00:07:01,710
-Not hidden anywhere. -No.

129
00:07:02,050 --> 00:07:04,610
No. No.A guy this good wouldn't risk his bike not being near when he comes out.

130
00:07:04,870 --> 00:07:05,680
He'd park illegally.

131
00:07:05,680 --> 00:07:07,300
Probably not in the parking lot,

132
00:07:07,670 --> 00:07:08,800
but further down the block,maybe,

133
00:07:09,940 --> 00:07:10,900
or right across the street here.

134
00:07:11,700 --> 00:07:14,910
We need to know if any of these places have security cameras that might have caught the bike.

135
00:07:15,520 --> 00:07:16,340
Ready?

136
00:07:17,300 --> 00:07:19,830
Let's go rob a bank. 

137
00:07:21,680 --> 00:07:22,760
Basically,

138
00:07:22,940 --> 00:07:25,530
we assume the suspects will hunt close to where they live,

139
00:07:25,530 --> 00:07:27,260
but far enough to remain anonymous.

140
00:07:27,630 --> 00:07:29,810
Each one of these data points represents a bank that he hit,

141
00:07:29,810 --> 00:07:35,000
and this area where the lines intersect give us the best estimate of the unsub's home.

142
00:07:35,600 --> 00:07:37,370
So,how many does that narrow it down to?

143
00:07:38,070 --> 00:07:40,370
Uh,couple hundred thousand.

144
00:07:41,420 --> 00:07:42,420
Oh.

145
00:07:42,940 --> 00:07:44,060
Witness statements.

146
00:07:46,100 --> 00:07:48,600
Not planning on seeing any of the sights this afternoon,were you?

147
00:07:49,180 --> 00:07:50,740
I've already seen the hollywood sign,

148
00:07:50,740 --> 00:07:51,850
been to the getty center,

149
00:07:51,850 --> 00:07:53,960
I'm not really interested in john wayne's footprints,

150
00:07:53,960 --> 00:07:56,090
so I guess that covers the sights of los angeles.

151
00:07:57,090 --> 00:07:57,920
Oh. Let me guess,new york?

152
00:07:58,500 --> 00:07:59,580
Now,what would make you say that?

153
00:08:00,100 --> 00:08:01,950
Is this all the video equipment you've got?

154
00:08:02,620 --> 00:08:03,640
It ain't quanico.

155
00:08:03,860 --> 00:08:05,880
I need to set up a link with our tech back there.

156
00:08:05,880 --> 00:08:08,030
We got another bay as crappy as this one down the hall.

157
00:08:08,730 --> 00:08:09,440
You all right?

158
00:08:09,670 --> 00:08:10,870
I just need some popcorn.

159
00:08:11,320 --> 00:08:11,950
Have fun.

160
00:08:15,010 --> 00:08:19,500
So,he enters and he walks right to this spot.

161
00:08:22,390 --> 00:08:24,640
Pulls his weapon and shoots into the ceiling right there.

162
00:08:26,520 --> 00:08:27,410
That gets everyone's attention,

163
00:08:27,410 --> 00:08:29,090
let's them all know he's dead serious.

164
00:08:29,090 --> 00:08:29,930
Efficient.

165
00:08:30,530 --> 00:08:31,620
This is the best spot in the bank.

166
00:08:32,220 --> 00:08:34,390
I can see all the tellers,the front door,

167
00:08:35,550 --> 00:08:37,270
and that's the back office over there.

168
00:08:38,920 --> 00:08:40,320
So,he knew exactly where to go.

169
00:08:40,440 --> 00:08:41,360
He had been here before.

170
00:08:42,830 --> 00:08:43,640
Next.

171
00:08:44,200 --> 00:08:48,980
Next,he turns,aims the gun at the guard.

172
00:08:49,240 --> 00:08:50,870
Don't you even think about it!

173
00:08:51,310 --> 00:08:52,110
Back it up.

174
00:08:52,110 --> 00:08:54,640
Disarms the guard and handcuffs him to the base.

175
00:08:57,260 --> 00:08:58,220
So,where's the threat?

176
00:08:58,220 --> 00:08:59,740
The guard's disarmed and chained.

177
00:08:59,740 --> 00:09:00,830
How's he a threat to the unsub?

178
00:09:01,540 --> 00:09:02,290
He isn'T.

179
00:09:02,810 --> 00:09:04,190
Then why did he take the time to assault?

180
00:09:05,490 --> 00:09:06,320
He's got control,

181
00:09:06,750 --> 00:09:07,840
he's obviously got skills,

182
00:09:08,660 --> 00:09:10,250
the very thing that he doesn't have is time.

183
00:09:10,430 --> 00:09:12,460
He didn't assault the guards in the previous banks,why?

184
00:09:12,460 --> 00:09:14,160
What's changed? What's different about this guard?

185
00:09:16,030 --> 00:09:17,610
Maybe this guard reminded him of somebody.

186
00:09:17,790 --> 00:09:19,600
What were the other guards in the previous robberies wearing?

187
00:09:20,690 --> 00:09:21,600
Uniforms?

188
00:09:22,380 --> 00:09:23,300
Black suits.

189
00:09:24,360 --> 00:09:24,950
That's it.

190
00:09:25,720 --> 00:09:26,820
That's all.

191
00:09:29,730 --> 00:09:30,770
Our boy's efficient,

192
00:09:31,140 --> 00:09:32,110
he's determined.

193
00:09:32,690 --> 00:09:33,830
This ain't his first baby.

194
00:09:34,340 --> 00:09:35,700
He's got his trade down cold.

195
00:09:36,070 --> 00:09:38,670
Something about a guy in uniform triggers an emotional response.

196
00:09:39,950 --> 00:09:40,730
Army?

197
00:09:40,730 --> 00:09:42,470
Army,you're conditioned to work with people.

198
00:09:42,530 --> 00:09:44,340
This guy,he don't trust anybody.

199
00:09:44,690 --> 00:09:45,560
Prison.

200
00:09:46,020 --> 00:09:47,600
Best trade school in the country.

201
00:09:49,380 --> 00:09:51,810
I got access to 4 bank robberies with security footage.

202
00:09:51,810 --> 00:09:52,720
What do I get to do with them?

203
00:09:52,890 --> 00:09:56,250
You know your digital perspective whatever software?

204
00:09:56,770 --> 00:09:58,640
Digital perspective analysis rendering?

205
00:09:58,690 --> 00:09:59,090
Yeah.

206
00:09:59,090 --> 00:10:01,000
Honey,not only do I know it,I helped develop it.

207
00:10:01,390 --> 00:10:04,190
Good,'cause I want every physical dimension of the unsub:

208
00:10:04,190 --> 00:10:06,850
Height,waist size,inseam,everything that you can give me.

209
00:10:06,850 --> 00:10:08,440
Honey,if he opens his mouth,

210
00:10:08,440 --> 00:10:09,810
I'll give you the length of his teeth.

211
00:10:09,810 --> 00:10:12,370
Just keep it clean and don't call me honey.

212
00:10:16,130 --> 00:10:17,150
See anything interesting?

213
00:10:18,050 --> 00:10:18,850
Maybe.

214
00:10:20,280 --> 00:10:21,280
He took his time,

215
00:10:21,780 --> 00:10:22,790
he looked at me,

216
00:10:23,820 --> 00:10:25,340
then he pointed his gun at me.

217
00:10:25,670 --> 00:10:27,110
And you were all naked at this point?

218
00:10:28,870 --> 00:10:29,760
Yes.

219
00:10:31,010 --> 00:10:32,280
Bank manager's wife.

220
00:10:32,280 --> 00:10:33,620
She stopped by to pick him up.

221
00:10:33,620 --> 00:10:36,010
They were going to celebrate their son's 16th birthday.

222
00:10:36,010 --> 00:10:37,470
The son was with them?

223
00:10:37,470 --> 00:10:39,280
Daughter,too.

224
00:10:46,690 --> 00:10:47,760
He knows the kids are theirs?

225
00:10:48,100 --> 00:10:50,080
Well,witnesses said he checked their wallets first.

226
00:10:50,320 --> 00:10:51,390
He would have seen their names.

227
00:10:52,180 --> 00:10:53,150
So,of all 13 people,

228
00:10:53,150 --> 00:10:56,180
he puts together woman in her 60's,guy in his 30's,

229
00:10:56,180 --> 00:10:57,590
married couple in front of their kids.

230
00:10:58,990 --> 00:10:59,790
Why?

231
00:10:59,790 --> 00:11:02,140
Maybe they were the most inappropriate couples he could think of.

232
00:11:03,880 --> 00:11:04,850
He's sadistic.

233
00:11:04,850 --> 00:11:06,920
Would explains why he brings them herE.

234
00:11:07,660 --> 00:11:09,160
He could have taken them behind the teller windows,

235
00:11:09,160 --> 00:11:10,660
he could have taken them back into the vault,

236
00:11:10,660 --> 00:11:11,550
but he chooses here.

237
00:11:12,270 --> 00:11:13,580
It's the most exposed place in the bank.

238
00:11:16,320 --> 00:11:17,510
Like a stage.

239
00:11:18,590 --> 00:11:21,520
Like,it was as important for them to see what was going on as it was for him.

240
00:11:22,240 --> 00:11:24,690
Public humiliation. 

241
00:11:28,530 --> 00:11:29,590
I said,watch it!

242
00:11:34,560 --> 00:11:35,870
Robbery wasn't about the money;

243
00:11:35,870 --> 00:11:39,400
it was about getting off on what he made these people do on this spot.

244
00:11:40,800 --> 00:11:42,710
Forcing others to squirm and watch.

245
00:11:43,220 --> 00:11:45,020
We got to know what exactly they were forced to do.

246
00:11:46,280 --> 00:11:47,580
We need to see the fantasy.

247
00:11:48,310 --> 00:11:49,950
Did you ever get a hold of the security videos?

248
00:11:49,950 --> 00:11:52,330
Yes,but they were mostly erased.

249
00:11:56,060 --> 00:11:57,490
That's henderson,the bank manager.

250
00:11:57,490 --> 00:12:00,100
Said he was so flustered after what he had been through,

251
00:12:00,460 --> 00:12:01,940
that when he was gathering the tapes for us,

252
00:12:02,550 --> 00:12:04,170
he hit the wrong buttons and erased part of them.

253
00:12:05,080 --> 00:12:05,980
You believe him?

254
00:12:06,050 --> 00:12:07,770
No. I told him I thought he was embarrassed 

255
00:12:07,770 --> 00:12:09,810
about the tapes getting out and he erased them on purpose.

256
00:12:10,160 --> 00:12:10,910
He denied it.

257
00:12:10,960 --> 00:12:12,720
You rule out the possibility he was in on it?

258
00:12:13,440 --> 00:12:16,180
Why would he be involved in a robbery when he had to go through something like that?

259
00:12:16,180 --> 00:12:17,900
Well,maybe he didn't know what was going to happen.

260
00:12:18,090 --> 00:12:19,890
Maybe he was betrayed by the unsub.

261
00:12:19,890 --> 00:12:21,510
Or perhaps he was coerced.

262
00:12:21,510 --> 00:12:23,460
There's been many documented cases of robbers 

263
00:12:23,460 --> 00:12:25,730
forcing bank managers to assist them with their crimes.

264
00:12:26,660 --> 00:12:29,180
Yeah,none of that is consistent with the M.O.'S of the other robberies.

265
00:12:29,180 --> 00:12:31,190
Maybe there's a reason this last one was different from the others.

266
00:12:31,190 --> 00:12:32,680
Call from quanico on one.

267
00:12:32,680 --> 00:12:33,730
Thanks.

268
00:12:33,730 --> 00:12:34,840
Garcia,it's hotch.

269
00:12:34,840 --> 00:12:36,930
Are we ready for something completely weird?

270
00:12:36,930 --> 00:12:38,750
How weird are we talking,garcia?

271
00:12:38,750 --> 00:12:40,200
The security footage hotch gave me,

272
00:12:40,200 --> 00:12:42,320
I ran it through my software 3 times...

273
00:12:42,520 --> 00:12:43,240
and?

274
00:12:43,240 --> 00:12:45,690
And there are weird height issues.

275
00:12:45,690 --> 00:12:49,270
I.E.,The unsub in the first 3 robberies is 6 foot 1 

276
00:12:49,270 --> 00:12:52,190
and the unsub in the last robbery,he's 5'10".

277
00:12:52,740 --> 00:12:54,980
So what?The last robbery we're dealing with a different unsub?

278
00:12:55,170 --> 00:12:57,300
An unsub who is somehow able to erase tapes 

279
00:12:57,300 --> 00:12:59,560
that show exactly what happened at that bank.

280
00:13:00,010 --> 00:13:02,370
An unsub who may have possibly had inside help.

281
00:13:03,570 --> 00:13:05,670
I think it's time we sat down with the bank manager.

282
00:13:08,750 --> 00:13:12,050
Look,I already told the other agent that I was nervous.

283
00:13:12,810 --> 00:13:13,690
I screwed up.

284
00:13:13,980 --> 00:13:16,380
I--what else do you want me to say?

285
00:13:16,380 --> 00:13:19,880
It took you 9 minutes to call 911 after the robber left.

286
00:13:19,880 --> 00:13:21,440
I was collecting the tapes.

287
00:13:21,790 --> 00:13:23,020
Before you called 911?

288
00:13:24,930 --> 00:13:26,320
You think I had something to do with this?

289
00:13:27,260 --> 00:13:29,290
You think I'd put my family through this?

290
00:13:29,330 --> 00:13:30,030
No.

291
00:13:34,550 --> 00:13:37,530
I don't think you'd put your family through letting those tapes get out either.

292
00:13:39,950 --> 00:13:42,900
You were the only one who had access to those tapes,mr. Henderson.

293
00:13:42,900 --> 00:13:45,910
Now,at best,you erased them because you were embarrassed,and at rst,

294
00:13:45,910 --> 00:13:47,480
because you had something to do with the robbery.

295
00:13:47,480 --> 00:13:49,030
Now,which one would you rather have us think?

296
00:13:50,800 --> 00:13:51,970
You got to understand.

297
00:13:51,970 --> 00:13:53,930
We were raised baptists.

298
00:13:54,350 --> 00:13:56,770
It's hard for us to talk about this kind of thing.

299
00:13:58,370 --> 00:13:59,480
It's hard for all of us.

300
00:14:07,720 --> 00:14:09,700
The thought about anybody seeing those tapes,

301
00:14:09,940 --> 00:14:10,990
even the police...

302
00:14:14,570 --> 00:14:15,420
no.

303
00:14:17,100 --> 00:14:18,040
I'm sorry.

304
00:14:19,680 --> 00:14:20,950
I'm sorry.

305
00:14:22,490 --> 00:14:23,740
I didn't think it would matter.

306
00:14:31,290 --> 00:14:32,810
I think it's pretty clear what this is about.

307
00:14:34,320 --> 00:14:35,880
Shame and humiliation.

308
00:14:39,230 --> 00:14:40,270
Everybody,down!

309
00:14:41,300 --> 00:14:42,490
I said,watch it!

310
00:14:42,650 --> 00:14:43,850
Watch it!

311
00:14:46,530 --> 00:14:48,530
there is nothing wrong with my software.

312
00:14:49,260 --> 00:14:51,160
My software is perfect,

313
00:14:52,240 --> 00:14:52,920
isn't it?

314
00:14:53,320 --> 00:14:55,440
No,it isn'T.It is.

315
00:14:59,580 --> 00:15:02,720
Why must your beauty be so painful?

316
00:15:10,660 --> 00:15:11,300
Yeah?

317
00:15:11,300 --> 00:15:12,020
Uh,pals,

318
00:15:12,020 --> 00:15:12,730
don't be ticked,

319
00:15:12,730 --> 00:15:15,850
but I think I may have missed the sort of  glaringly obvious here.

320
00:15:16,110 --> 00:15:19,590
How would you make yourself taller without being a different person entirely or

321
00:15:19,590 --> 00:15:21,630
having some sort of weird chinese surgery?

322
00:15:21,630 --> 00:15:22,430
Heels.

323
00:15:22,650 --> 00:15:24,830
Right,sunshine,but would have seen heels,

324
00:15:24,830 --> 00:15:28,080
unless the unsub had them hidden inside his shoe.

325
00:15:28,080 --> 00:15:29,440
The point is,lifts.

326
00:15:29,440 --> 00:15:30,160
Lifts.

327
00:15:30,160 --> 00:15:31,780
Lifts,all hidden up inside his boot.

328
00:15:32,280 --> 00:15:33,790
With a little fancy footwork,

329
00:15:33,790 --> 00:15:35,920
pun emphatically intended,

330
00:15:35,920 --> 00:15:37,600
garcia here managed to dig him out.

331
00:15:37,600 --> 00:15:38,520
Thanks,girl.

332
00:15:40,040 --> 00:15:40,790
He's trying to throw us off,

333
00:15:40,790 --> 00:15:41,730
hide his real height.

334
00:15:41,730 --> 00:15:44,190
But why would he take the lifts out just for the last robbery?

335
00:15:44,200 --> 00:15:45,480
Maybe he's getting careless.

336
00:15:45,630 --> 00:15:47,260
Which means he's also getting more dangerous.

337
00:15:47,260 --> 00:15:49,280
At least we know we're only dealing with one unsub.

338
00:15:59,160 --> 00:16:00,170
Aah!

339
00:16:01,760 --> 00:16:03,940
Based on the knowledge that spending a significant time

340
00:16:03,940 --> 00:16:07,670
in prison stunts emotional growth while increasing professional skills,

341
00:16:07,670 --> 00:16:09,670
we can estimate this unsub went to jail

342
00:16:09,670 --> 00:16:11,780
between the ages of 18 and 22 and spent 

343
00:16:11,780 --> 00:16:13,600
between5 and 10 years inside.

344
00:16:19,210 --> 00:16:23,570
That puts him at the approximate age between 23 and 35.

345
00:16:23,820 --> 00:16:25,720
This guy's much more than just a bank robber though.

346
00:16:26,040 --> 00:16:27,860
What started out as a practical M.O.,

347
00:16:27,860 --> 00:16:29,070
Stripping his hostages,

348
00:16:29,800 --> 00:16:31,980
triggered a deep psycho-sexual response.

349
00:16:31,980 --> 00:16:33,050
In other words,

350
00:16:33,050 --> 00:16:35,720
when he found himself in front of a bunch of naked people under his control,

351
00:16:35,720 --> 00:16:38,790
he snapped,then he decided to manipulate them.

352
00:16:38,790 --> 00:16:40,340
Better,or just getting worse?

353
00:16:40,340 --> 00:16:42,250
He's attacking banks earlier in the day 

354
00:16:42,250 --> 00:16:44,020
when more and more people are present.

355
00:16:44,020 --> 00:16:47,270
This sounds like he's sacrificing the safety of having just a few hostages to contain,

356
00:16:47,270 --> 00:16:49,540
for the satisfaction of having more subjects to control.

357
00:16:49,910 --> 00:16:51,340
He'll be less interested in money 

358
00:16:51,340 --> 00:16:54,190
and more interested in sadistically  anipulating his captives.

359
00:16:54,720 --> 00:16:56,570
In all likelihood,he's high on drugs.

360
00:17:01,450 --> 00:17:03,490
It'd be wrong,however,to write this guy off as crazy.

361
00:17:04,190 --> 00:17:05,540
Bank robbing is an ambitious crime and 

362
00:17:05,540 --> 00:17:07,440
it takes time and planning to pull it off.

363
00:17:07,440 --> 00:17:11,670
What makes this unsub unique is his fractured psyche.

364
00:17:12,740 --> 00:17:13,960
On the one hand,

365
00:17:14,790 --> 00:17:16,580
a cold,organized bank robber.

366
00:17:17,230 --> 00:17:17,900
On the other,

367
00:17:19,250 --> 00:17:23,010
a disorganized sexual sadist full of bottled up rage.

368
00:17:27,010 --> 00:17:27,860
Freeze!

369
00:17:27,860 --> 00:17:30,130
Drop it!

370
00:17:30,130 --> 00:17:30,850
No.

371
00:17:30,850 --> 00:17:33,250
Come on now,just put it down.

372
00:17:36,330 --> 00:17:37,700
I got a mac-10.

373
00:17:37,970 --> 00:17:38,640
One shot. 

374
00:17:38,640 --> 00:17:39,990
You got one shot to kill me.

375
00:17:42,250 --> 00:17:44,750
Even if you kill me,I'm going down shooting.

376
00:18:00,830 --> 00:18:05,090
The 2 parts of his psyche have just begun to bleed though,

377
00:18:05,570 --> 00:18:07,090
and when they finally converge,

378
00:18:08,140 --> 00:18:09,400
we're talking about a criminal 

379
00:18:10,250 --> 00:18:13,560
with the skills and efficiency of a master bank robber

380
00:18:14,250 --> 00:18:16,590
and the rage of a suicide bomber.

381
00:18:17,500 --> 00:18:18,570
He will explode.

382
00:18:40,780 --> 00:18:41,850
Take them off.

383
00:18:47,190 --> 00:18:50,620
-I said take them off. -No.

384
00:18:51,410 --> 00:18:54,180
Take...them...off!

385
00:18:58,270 --> 00:19:00,000
Sir,bank robbery in progress.

386
00:19:00,000 --> 00:19:01,660
Corner of washington and sepulveda.

387
00:19:01,660 --> 00:19:03,220
Kid in the back called 911 on his cell.

388
00:19:03,220 --> 00:19:05,130
Said the suspect's started making people undress.

389
00:19:32,950 --> 00:19:34,000
How far are we from the bank?

390
00:19:34,000 --> 00:19:35,810
Without traffic,10 minutes.

391
00:19:35,960 --> 00:19:37,240
Let's avoid traffic.

392
00:19:51,500 --> 00:19:53,310
Do I have everybody's attention?

393
00:20:04,720 --> 00:20:05,510
How we doing?

394
00:20:05,510 --> 00:20:06,100
5 minutes.

395
00:20:06,100 --> 00:20:07,110
Make it 3.

396
00:20:21,780 --> 00:20:22,870
Please?

397
00:20:22,870 --> 00:20:24,850
Less than a mile.

398
00:20:26,600 --> 00:20:27,640
Just around the corner.

399
00:20:32,660 --> 00:20:33,620
Is this your bike?

400
00:20:52,720 --> 00:20:53,390
Call E.M.S.!

401
00:20:53,540 --> 00:20:54,910
F.B.I.He took off.Where?

402
00:20:54,910 --> 00:20:55,640
I don't know.

403
00:20:55,910 --> 00:20:57,420
Ma'am. Ma'am,can you hear me?

404
00:20:58,390 --> 00:20:59,330
She's unconscious.

405
00:20:59,430 --> 00:21:00,240
Medics are on their way.

406
00:21:00,240 --> 00:21:01,820
Gideon,he may be headed your way.

407
00:21:02,440 --> 00:21:04,580
You know what the odds are of catching a motorcycle with a car in L.A.?

408
00:21:04,580 --> 00:21:05,740
Right now,I'm trying not to think about it.

409
00:21:10,020 --> 00:21:10,680
There.

410
00:21:13,900 --> 00:21:14,950
Damn it.Go.

411
00:22:36,470 --> 00:22:37,980
It's the first time he's made so many mistakes.

412
00:22:38,960 --> 00:22:39,900
Hit the bank in the morning,

413
00:22:39,900 --> 00:22:40,930
more people around.

414
00:22:41,890 --> 00:22:42,580
Didn't clear the back room,

415
00:22:42,580 --> 00:22:43,780
parked his bike right out front.

416
00:22:43,780 --> 00:22:44,960
Didn't bother taking any money.

417
00:22:45,060 --> 00:22:46,700
Did almost everything you predicted.

418
00:22:48,930 --> 00:22:50,300
Sometimes it sucks to be right.

419
00:22:50,780 --> 00:22:52,670
Witnesses said he refused to take off his clothes.

420
00:22:55,280 --> 00:22:55,810
Damn.

421
00:22:55,810 --> 00:22:56,790
That's enough.

422
00:23:01,860 --> 00:23:03,550
It's not the kind of rage you bottle back up.

423
00:23:04,680 --> 00:23:05,970
This could be the beginning of a spree.

424
00:23:08,180 --> 00:23:09,700
How's jj doing on that suspect list?

425
00:23:12,080 --> 00:23:12,770
I'll call her.

426
00:23:12,770 --> 00:23:14,500
I'll call reid and elle and get them on it,too.

427
00:23:18,620 --> 00:23:19,860
You don't think he's going to rob another bank?

428
00:23:20,960 --> 00:23:22,550
No.

429
00:23:22,550 --> 00:23:24,090
He doesn't care about money anymore.

430
00:23:24,720 --> 00:23:25,830
Whatever he's after,

431
00:23:27,620 --> 00:23:29,190
he'll hurt anyone who gets in his way.

432
00:23:49,870 --> 00:23:50,490
Hey.

433
00:23:50,490 --> 00:23:51,640
You call elle and reid?

434
00:23:51,640 --> 00:23:52,410
Yeah.

435
00:23:54,130 --> 00:23:54,790
What's that?

436
00:23:54,790 --> 00:23:56,300
My son's first steps.

437
00:23:56,630 --> 00:23:58,880
I was out of town and haley sent me the file.

438
00:23:58,880 --> 00:23:59,950
It's nice.

439
00:24:00,800 --> 00:24:01,840
It's 5 months ago.

440
00:24:01,840 --> 00:24:03,730
I haven't loaded anything on here since.

441
00:24:04,920 --> 00:24:06,770
Ok.So you film a new one when you get home.

442
00:24:12,160 --> 00:24:13,600
So,you're sure this is it?

443
00:24:13,600 --> 00:24:15,490
Yeah. Based on all the parameters,

444
00:24:15,970 --> 00:24:17,890
age,armed robbery charge,

445
00:24:17,890 --> 00:24:18,600
time spent in prison,

446
00:24:19,220 --> 00:24:22,270
approximate location of home address based on geographical profile.

447
00:24:23,080 --> 00:24:24,320
It's about 360 names 

448
00:24:25,110 --> 00:24:26,180
these guys aren't sweethearts,

449
00:24:26,180 --> 00:24:28,310
but there's only a handful with sex crimes on their rap sheets 

450
00:24:28,310 --> 00:24:30,050
and none are sexual sadists.

451
00:24:30,050 --> 00:24:31,350
That's not surprising.

452
00:24:31,350 --> 00:24:34,410
Bank robbers and gun nuts aren't typically sex offenders.

453
00:24:34,640 --> 00:24:36,100
That's what makes this one so unique.

454
00:24:36,240 --> 00:24:37,020
What about a pimp?

455
00:24:38,720 --> 00:24:40,720
Roland lynch,32 years old.

456
00:24:41,650 --> 00:24:43,280
Pimps are characteristically sociopath and,

457
00:24:43,500 --> 00:24:45,690
in many cases,sadistic.

458
00:24:45,760 --> 00:24:47,010
Helps control their employees.

459
00:24:47,820 --> 00:24:49,950
Well,this one started out robbing convenience stores 

460
00:24:50,210 --> 00:24:51,430
before working his way into pimping.

461
00:24:52,020 --> 00:24:52,960
That's unusual.

462
00:24:53,230 --> 00:24:54,670
Pimps typically violate by proxy,

463
00:24:54,960 --> 00:24:56,390
forcing others to do the work for them,whereas,

464
00:24:56,390 --> 00:24:59,180
bank robbers usually operate in pairs or alone.

465
00:24:59,420 --> 00:25:02,900
So,he's sexually sadistic and has experience with armed robbery.

466
00:25:03,260 --> 00:25:04,810
Along with fitting all other parameters of the profile.

467
00:25:05,490 --> 00:25:07,470
All right.I'll get in touch with his parole officer.

468
00:25:09,350 --> 00:25:10,760
You're lynch's parole officer.

469
00:25:10,760 --> 00:25:12,060
When was the last time you talked to him?

470
00:25:13,230 --> 00:25:14,360
Haven't talked to lynch in a month.

471
00:25:14,970 --> 00:25:16,210
What can you tell us about him?

472
00:25:16,210 --> 00:25:16,990
Roland?

473
00:25:17,750 --> 00:25:18,630
A real peach.

474
00:25:19,450 --> 00:25:21,970
He used to punish his girls by raping them in front of their little sisters.

475
00:25:24,760 --> 00:25:25,630
He got a habit?

476
00:25:25,790 --> 00:25:26,800
Which one of mine doesn't?

477
00:25:27,330 --> 00:25:27,980
If I'm not mistaken,

478
00:25:27,980 --> 00:25:29,680
he probably has about a 10 rock a day monkey.

479
00:25:30,270 --> 00:25:31,080
If lynch is our guy,

480
00:25:31,080 --> 00:25:32,090
he's going downhill fast,

481
00:25:32,090 --> 00:25:33,750
but if he's tweaked,he's going down even faster.

482
00:25:34,580 --> 00:25:36,230
His latest drug test isn't back yet,

483
00:25:36,890 --> 00:25:38,280
but I'm betting it isn't going to be clean.

484
00:25:38,920 --> 00:25:39,710
You got a line on him?

485
00:25:40,730 --> 00:25:42,810
Give me a break.You know what my case load is like?

486
00:25:43,290 --> 00:25:44,120
Hey,come on,maN.

487
00:25:44,510 --> 00:25:46,500
He might have beaten a civilian to death with a mac-10,

488
00:25:46,500 --> 00:25:48,460
caved in a meter maid's face,and that's just the beginning.

489
00:25:49,370 --> 00:25:50,350
That make the top of your list?

490
00:25:51,660 --> 00:25:52,610
I'll make some calls.

491
00:26:01,460 --> 00:26:02,840
F.B.I. I need roland lynch.

492
00:26:02,870 --> 00:26:04,090
I need to talk to roland lynch.

493
00:26:04,090 --> 00:26:04,790
Roland lynch?

494
00:26:06,220 --> 00:26:07,380
Hey! Roland lynch?

495
00:26:08,170 --> 00:26:08,930
Don't even think about it.

496
00:26:08,930 --> 00:26:09,840
Don't move!

497
00:26:09,840 --> 00:26:10,590
Give it to me.

498
00:26:10,590 --> 00:26:11,690
Give it to me.

499
00:26:15,860 --> 00:26:18,750
Roland,I can count about 16 different ways you've just violated your parole.

500
00:26:18,750 --> 00:26:20,760
They send in feds for busting parole?

501
00:26:20,760 --> 00:26:23,510
We're here for the bank robberies and the delivery man you killed.

502
00:26:24,780 --> 00:26:25,940
I don't rob banks.

503
00:26:25,940 --> 00:26:27,010
You violated parole,

504
00:26:27,010 --> 00:26:28,350
we've got you on possession,

505
00:26:28,350 --> 00:26:29,190
you're going down.

506
00:26:29,860 --> 00:26:31,870
You think I'm gonna roll over 'cause you're waving 3 to 5 at me?

507
00:26:32,570 --> 00:26:34,100
I took beating's that lasted longer than that.

508
00:26:34,100 --> 00:26:37,340
If i were you,I wouldn't even worry about the murder charge.

509
00:26:37,810 --> 00:26:40,720
I'd worry what happens to you when word gets around you're a pervert.

510
00:26:41,050 --> 00:26:42,720
Yeah,well,I made my living being a pervert.

511
00:26:42,720 --> 00:26:43,650
You can tell them that.

512
00:26:43,650 --> 00:26:44,790
Oh,this is different.

513
00:26:44,790 --> 00:26:47,780
Went after little old ladies,kids.

514
00:26:48,200 --> 00:26:51,130
Witnesses say you got off when the old lady took her shirt off.

515
00:26:53,080 --> 00:26:55,160
Old ladies,kids,inside,think about it.

516
00:26:57,220 --> 00:26:57,970
Hey,roland,

517
00:26:58,540 --> 00:27:00,240
you're high out of your mind right now,aren't ya?

518
00:27:01,250 --> 00:27:02,010
Get him in the car.

519
00:27:02,010 --> 00:27:02,930
Take him back to the field office,

520
00:27:03,170 --> 00:27:04,870
spend a few hours with him,he'll sober up.

521
00:27:04,870 --> 00:27:07,000
Give me a pot of coffee and I'll go all night with this fool.

522
00:27:07,000 --> 00:27:07,800
Get him out of here.

523
00:27:28,540 --> 00:27:29,560
Hey,morgan.

524
00:27:29,560 --> 00:27:30,120
We got him.

525
00:27:30,600 --> 00:27:31,800
This guy's a hardcore prison rat.

526
00:27:32,300 --> 00:27:32,970
Hey.

527
00:27:32,970 --> 00:27:33,580
Hang on.

528
00:27:33,580 --> 00:27:35,890
We just got another call,restaurant in the south bay.

529
00:27:35,890 --> 00:27:38,480
Guy came in in a ski-mask,started making people undress.

530
00:27:38,770 --> 00:27:40,030
He just shot a 14-year-old kid.

531
00:27:40,030 --> 00:27:40,700
When?

532
00:27:40,700 --> 00:27:41,700
10 minutes ago.

533
00:27:41,700 --> 00:27:42,650
What'd she say?

534
00:27:42,650 --> 00:27:45,620
Hardcore or not,you've got the wrong scumbag.

535
00:27:49,540 --> 00:27:50,340
According to witnesses,

536
00:27:50,340 --> 00:27:52,380
he came in and fired at the ceiling.

537
00:27:56,180 --> 00:27:58,360
Then he separated all the kids from their parents.

538
00:28:08,840 --> 00:28:09,550
Then?

539
00:28:12,810 --> 00:28:14,710
He's forcing the sons to hit their mothers.

540
00:28:14,710 --> 00:28:15,840
He started to.

541
00:28:15,840 --> 00:28:18,990
When he tried to get the first one to hit his mother harder,

542
00:28:20,310 --> 00:28:21,510
he refused,

543
00:28:22,330 --> 00:28:23,540
and when he refused...

544
00:28:28,240 --> 00:28:30,220
it doesn't make sense.They're children.

545
00:28:32,490 --> 00:28:33,750
He's playing out a fantasy.

546
00:28:33,750 --> 00:28:35,970
Yeah,but it's his fantasy and someone else's children.

547
00:28:36,990 --> 00:28:38,280
They're surrogates of some kind.

548
00:28:39,250 --> 00:28:42,360
No. You don't do this to someone else's kids to get off.

549
00:28:42,360 --> 00:28:43,240
You just don't do it.

550
00:28:54,920 --> 00:28:56,010
It just doesn't make sense to me.

551
00:28:57,420 --> 00:28:58,090
You internalize violence.

552
00:28:58,090 --> 00:28:59,530
You take it out on other people.

553
00:28:59,530 --> 00:29:00,640
Why force somebody else to do it?

554
00:29:01,050 --> 00:29:03,470
Why force children to act out your rage?

555
00:29:04,850 --> 00:29:06,780
He didn't make the children do anything at the bank.

556
00:29:08,380 --> 00:29:10,210
Manager said he put the parents together.

557
00:29:11,030 --> 00:29:13,510
So,why is he so focused on the kids now?

558
00:29:14,340 --> 00:29:16,070
I want to talk to the bank manager again.

559
00:29:21,660 --> 00:29:22,690
I don't know what else I can tell you.

560
00:29:22,910 --> 00:29:24,220
I've already gone over it 3 times.

561
00:29:25,700 --> 00:29:26,400
What we need to know is 

562
00:29:26,670 --> 00:29:29,150
if there's something in that tape that you don't want us to know about?

563
00:29:31,940 --> 00:29:34,570
There were 12 other people in that bank who were forced to watch.

564
00:29:34,740 --> 00:29:36,340
What could I possibly be hiding?

565
00:29:43,730 --> 00:29:45,660
This is about your children,isn't it?

566
00:29:51,470 --> 00:29:52,430
We're sorry.

567
00:30:00,590 --> 00:30:03,280
Mr. Henderson,this is very important.

568
00:30:04,120 --> 00:30:06,380
He's already killed 2 people and he's not going to stop.

569
00:30:10,100 --> 00:30:11,840
God! Go ahead.

570
00:30:12,470 --> 00:30:14,470
Why don't you tell them what he did to us,

571
00:30:14,470 --> 00:30:16,200
what you let him do?

572
00:30:17,250 --> 00:30:18,040
He had a gun.

573
00:30:20,490 --> 00:30:21,570
He was going to kill me.

574
00:30:32,530 --> 00:30:33,730
Come on.

575
00:30:46,170 --> 00:30:47,550
They took my family from me.

576
00:30:51,730 --> 00:30:53,300
We can't even look at each other anymore.

577
00:31:03,710 --> 00:31:05,320
I don't know how a family gets over something like that.

578
00:31:06,150 --> 00:31:07,070
They don'T.

579
00:31:07,680 --> 00:31:08,770
Excuse me.

580
00:31:12,010 --> 00:31:14,470
Is it true he would have killed my father if he tried to stand up to him?

581
00:31:15,270 --> 00:31:16,230
There's no way to know,darren,

582
00:31:16,230 --> 00:31:17,840
but your father did the right thing.

583
00:31:20,210 --> 00:31:21,570
Is there some reason you doubt that?

584
00:31:23,110 --> 00:31:23,930
It's just...

585
00:31:25,230 --> 00:31:26,820
the robber said something afterwards.

586
00:31:29,550 --> 00:31:30,830
He said he was sorry.

587
00:31:36,960 --> 00:31:38,110
He apologized.

588
00:31:38,910 --> 00:31:39,830
Sadists don't apologize.

589
00:31:39,830 --> 00:31:40,880
They gloat,maybe,

590
00:31:41,140 --> 00:31:42,210
but they don't apologize.

591
00:31:42,210 --> 00:31:43,580
Our guy's not a sadist.

592
00:31:43,950 --> 00:31:45,630
We got that part of the profile wrong.

593
00:31:46,460 --> 00:31:49,600
He doesn't derive any sadistic pleasure from these fantasies,

594
00:31:51,130 --> 00:31:52,390
they're--they're more like a compulsion.

595
00:31:52,490 --> 00:31:54,400
Compulsion that's literally life or death?

596
00:31:54,400 --> 00:31:56,260
I mean,if anyone interferes,he kills them.

597
00:31:56,690 --> 00:32:00,470
It's like he's compelled to direct these fantasies using these people as actors.

598
00:32:00,530 --> 00:32:02,050
Actors on a stage,it's a play.

599
00:32:02,640 --> 00:32:03,720
It's a psychodrama.

600
00:32:06,530 --> 00:32:07,210
What's that?

601
00:32:07,500 --> 00:32:11,540
It's a form of psychotherapy whereby actors serve as surrogates for actual people in the patient's life.

602
00:32:12,180 --> 00:32:14,640
Incorporates many elements of theatre,including an audience.

603
00:32:15,270 --> 00:32:16,590
There's a very famous pilot program 

604
00:32:16,590 --> 00:32:18,940
at the san luis obispo county jail in the mid-nineties.

605
00:32:19,280 --> 00:32:20,910
Isn't that just a couple hours away from here?

606
00:32:21,930 --> 00:32:23,190
Let's go over the suspect list and 

607
00:32:23,190 --> 00:32:25,420
see how many of them did time in san luis obispo.

608
00:32:26,730 --> 00:32:27,610
The answer is 4.

609
00:32:27,820 --> 00:32:29,890
Come on. Tell me you narrowed it down a little more than that.

610
00:32:30,090 --> 00:32:31,540
Only 2 live in state,

611
00:32:31,540 --> 00:32:32,790
but only 1 lives in L.A.

612
00:32:32,940 --> 00:32:33,830
Ha,that a girL.

613
00:32:34,440 --> 00:32:37,950
Caleb dale sheppard,last known address 236 harbor lane,inglewood.

614
00:32:37,950 --> 00:32:38,810
Thanks,mama.

615
00:32:39,240 --> 00:32:41,480
That's only 1.6 miles from the last restaurant he hit.

616
00:32:43,340 --> 00:32:44,990
I've been studying a lot of L.A. Maps.

617
00:32:45,060 --> 00:32:46,570
If he's been attacking that close to home,

618
00:32:46,570 --> 00:32:48,870
he's given up any interest in protecting his identity.

619
00:32:48,870 --> 00:32:51,510
You all go down there and split up,half to his address,

620
00:32:51,510 --> 00:32:53,960
half patrol around the restaurant in case he's on the hunt.

621
00:33:22,280 --> 00:33:24,400
Mrs. Sheppard,do you know where your son is?

622
00:33:24,400 --> 00:33:25,900
Dale doesn't live here anymore.

623
00:33:27,180 --> 00:33:28,270
Where is he,mrs. Sheppard?

624
00:33:29,170 --> 00:33:30,190
He's a grown man.

625
00:33:32,020 --> 00:33:34,330
You have any idea how much trouble your son could be in?

626
00:33:34,870 --> 00:33:35,610
Jail?

627
00:33:36,310 --> 00:33:37,350
He's a good boy.

628
00:33:38,070 --> 00:33:39,450
Lost his way a bit,that's all.

629
00:33:39,680 --> 00:33:41,810
Well,that's one way to look at 12 years in and out of prison.

630
00:33:42,760 --> 00:33:43,920
You've never made a mistake?

631
00:33:45,130 --> 00:33:47,010
Your son spent time in a juvenile home?

632
00:33:48,280 --> 00:33:49,230
He was out of control,

633
00:33:50,290 --> 00:33:51,800
even attacked his own sister once,

634
00:33:52,790 --> 00:33:53,790
but his father died.

635
00:33:54,640 --> 00:33:55,690
It wasn't his fault.

636
00:33:55,690 --> 00:33:56,730
Was it yours?

637
00:33:57,990 --> 00:33:58,890
What?

638
00:33:58,890 --> 00:34:01,240
Was it your fault?

639
00:34:04,640 --> 00:34:06,260
How many of these did you take today,mrs. Sheppard?

640
00:34:07,400 --> 00:34:10,590
I had back problems my whole life.

641
00:34:16,210 --> 00:34:17,500
She's completely out of her mind.

642
00:34:17,600 --> 00:34:20,330
She's so lonely she'll just keep talking to us.

643
00:34:21,310 --> 00:34:22,790
I doubt she'll tell us where he is.

644
00:34:23,230 --> 00:34:23,910
That was garcia.

645
00:34:23,910 --> 00:34:27,720
Apparently sheppard's sister died 12 years ago,suicide.

646
00:34:29,510 --> 00:34:31,220
Lady sure did a number on her kids.

647
00:34:32,550 --> 00:34:35,140
She's probably lonely after the husband died and on painkillers,

648
00:34:35,140 --> 00:34:36,510
not in her right mind,

649
00:34:36,510 --> 00:34:38,830
nobody there to turn to but sheppard and his sister.

650
00:34:39,420 --> 00:34:41,660
So,now he's symbolically punishing his mother?

651
00:34:41,950 --> 00:34:43,130
He's playing out a fantasy.

652
00:34:43,910 --> 00:34:46,210
Sons gaining total control over their mothers.

653
00:34:46,950 --> 00:34:47,880
We got something.

654
00:34:50,880 --> 00:34:51,930
"Dale daybreak hotel."

655
00:35:11,840 --> 00:35:14,320
Sheppard,F.B.I.

656
00:35:14,510 --> 00:35:15,200
Key?

657
00:35:16,100 --> 00:35:17,130
No,I got one.

658
00:35:26,950 --> 00:35:28,030
Clear!

659
00:35:28,900 --> 00:35:30,910
Yeah,it's clear here,too.

660
00:35:43,040 --> 00:35:44,070
Morgan.

661
00:35:44,070 --> 00:35:45,020
Crystal meth.

662
00:35:47,050 --> 00:35:48,640
Oh,he's got to be halfway out of his mind by now.

663
00:35:48,910 --> 00:35:50,660
Which would explain why he left this behind.

664
00:35:57,510 --> 00:35:59,350
Well,it looks like he's on foot.Here's his bike.

665
00:36:00,700 --> 00:36:01,580
I'm calling hotch.

666
00:36:16,790 --> 00:36:17,580
Yeah?

667
00:36:17,580 --> 00:36:18,420
Look,he's not here.

668
00:36:18,420 --> 00:36:20,210
From the looks of it,he just left.

669
00:36:20,210 --> 00:36:21,270
Hotch,he's tweakin'.

670
00:36:21,870 --> 00:36:23,440
He's unmasked and he's probably on foot.

671
00:36:23,550 --> 00:36:25,520
All right,stay there.Call if there's any sign of him.

672
00:36:25,520 --> 00:36:26,690
Ok. You. Too.

673
00:36:26,830 --> 00:36:29,140
If he's on foot,he must still be in the neighborhood.

674
00:36:29,260 --> 00:36:30,180
How do we find him?

675
00:36:30,740 --> 00:36:33,620
At this point,he'll probably hit the first thing that catches his attention.

676
00:36:33,620 --> 00:36:34,640
Families.

677
00:36:35,180 --> 00:36:36,040
Public places.

678
00:36:36,040 --> 00:36:38,520
If the trend continues,he'll look for a bigger audience.

679
00:36:38,520 --> 00:36:39,950
Public place with families.

680
00:36:40,030 --> 00:36:41,830
Guys,there's a public park not far from here.

681
00:36:41,830 --> 00:36:42,380
Where?

682
00:36:42,380 --> 00:36:43,720
.6 miles from where we are now.

683
00:36:43,720 --> 00:36:45,770
.9 miles from the hotel where the unsub's staying,

684
00:36:45,770 --> 00:36:48,050
which we'll actually pass if we take a right at the next light.

685
00:36:49,010 --> 00:36:51,430
It doesn't matter what they say

686
00:36:51,430 --> 00:36:56,660
in the jealous games people play,hey ey ey

687
00:37:22,700 --> 00:37:23,500
There's no sign of him.

688
00:37:27,210 --> 00:37:29,130
We've got cruisers everywhere.Where could he be?

689
00:37:29,810 --> 00:37:31,820
There's only a few blocks betweenhere and his hotel.

690
00:37:32,940 --> 00:37:34,040
He's got to be really close.

691
00:38:00,590 --> 00:38:01,800
-Do it. -No.

692
00:38:02,990 --> 00:38:03,890
I said,do it.

693
00:38:03,890 --> 00:38:04,940
No.

694
00:38:04,940 --> 00:38:06,330
Do it.It's ok.

695
00:38:06,780 --> 00:38:08,060
Come on,you can do it.

696
00:38:08,060 --> 00:38:08,870
No,no.

697
00:38:08,870 --> 00:38:10,750
Please,just do what he says,please.

698
00:38:11,280 --> 00:38:12,130
I said do it!

699
00:38:12,130 --> 00:38:13,350
Please,do what he says.

700
00:38:13,350 --> 00:38:15,050
It's ok,sweethearT.

701
00:38:15,760 --> 00:38:16,610
Mommy says it's ok.

702
00:38:21,690 --> 00:38:23,860
Put it down.

703
00:38:23,860 --> 00:38:24,700
Drop the knife.

704
00:38:25,840 --> 00:38:27,030
It won't fix you,sheppard.

705
00:38:27,340 --> 00:38:28,730
It doesn't matter what you make them do,

706
00:38:29,050 --> 00:38:30,540
how many people are watching you.

707
00:38:36,430 --> 00:38:37,740
Oh,my god.

708
00:38:37,740 --> 00:38:39,460
Got him.

709
00:38:39,460 --> 00:38:41,050
It's ok.

710
00:38:45,710 --> 00:38:46,780
Look at these people.

711
00:38:46,780 --> 00:38:47,990
Look at them!

712
00:38:48,780 --> 00:38:49,530
They're children.

713
00:38:50,520 --> 00:38:51,620
They're children,

714
00:38:51,620 --> 00:38:52,660
for god's sake.

715
00:39:00,850 --> 00:39:02,230
I need something that kills.

716
00:39:02,610 --> 00:39:03,360
Give me something.

717
00:39:03,360 --> 00:39:05,020
I need something. Aah!

718
00:39:06,830 --> 00:39:07,760
You shot me!

719
00:39:07,960 --> 00:39:10,040
You had a hunting knife to a little boy's throat.

720
00:39:10,040 --> 00:39:12,060
Just give me something for the pain,

721
00:39:12,060 --> 00:39:13,780
you son of a bitch!

722
00:39:16,540 --> 00:39:17,310
She did it!

723
00:39:17,620 --> 00:39:18,380
Who did?

724
00:39:18,670 --> 00:39:19,630
My mama.

725
00:39:20,080 --> 00:39:21,410
You don't know what she did to me.

726
00:39:21,410 --> 00:39:23,420
Did you really think you were going to get back at your mom 

727
00:39:23,420 --> 00:39:25,000
by attacking all these other people?

728
00:39:25,360 --> 00:39:26,680
The bitch deserved it.

729
00:39:26,680 --> 00:39:28,150
Except you didn't go after her,

730
00:39:28,150 --> 00:39:29,500
you went after all these other women.

731
00:39:29,600 --> 00:39:30,100
So what?

732
00:39:30,100 --> 00:39:31,180
You went after children.

733
00:39:31,380 --> 00:39:33,060
They're going to have to learn sooner or later.

734
00:39:33,060 --> 00:39:34,050
What are they going to have to learn?

735
00:39:34,050 --> 00:39:35,780
That no one's there for you.

736
00:39:37,570 --> 00:39:39,040
He's a drug addict.He's detoxing.

737
00:39:39,040 --> 00:39:40,400
I don't care what he asks for.

738
00:39:40,400 --> 00:39:41,430
Don't give him anything.

739
00:39:41,430 --> 00:39:42,030
Come on.

740
00:39:43,260 --> 00:39:44,740
He's not a doctor.

741
00:39:45,160 --> 00:39:48,720
He's right.I'm an F.B.I. Agent,and he killed a 14-year-old boy today.

742
00:40:02,610 --> 00:40:05,800
"The basis of shame is not some personal mistake of ours,

743
00:40:06,340 --> 00:40:09,200
but that this humiliation is seen by everyone."

744
00:40:10,310 --> 00:40:11,310
Milan kundera.

745
00:40:28,670 --> 00:40:29,480
You ok?

746
00:40:30,380 --> 00:40:33,270
I was showing those trainees around the offices the other day.

747
00:40:33,440 --> 00:40:35,010
They all want to be in the bau.

748
00:40:37,410 --> 00:40:39,110
I told them what a great job it is.

749
00:40:40,700 --> 00:40:43,830
And they even applauded when the tour was over.

750
00:40:45,980 --> 00:40:47,030
I heard.

751
00:40:47,440 --> 00:40:48,950
Yeah,but I really didn't tell them the truth.

752
00:40:48,950 --> 00:40:51,490
I didn't tell them what it's like to spend your days in this hell.

753
00:40:52,470 --> 00:40:53,610
It's fun,huh?

754
00:40:54,620 --> 00:40:56,840
I mean,who's to blame for somebody like sheppard?

755
00:40:58,490 --> 00:40:59,410
His mother?

756
00:40:59,740 --> 00:41:00,620
Broken home?

757
00:41:01,920 --> 00:41:02,470
Society?

758
00:41:02,470 --> 00:41:03,040
All of it?

759
00:41:03,040 --> 00:41:03,670
None of it?

760
00:41:06,720 --> 00:41:08,420
It gets worse and worse with each case.

761
00:41:10,410 --> 00:41:12,540
Save one life,we save the world.

762
00:41:14,970 --> 00:41:15,830
Yeah.

763
00:41:19,460 --> 00:41:21,380
Well,the one thing I didn't tell the trainees.

764
00:41:21,760 --> 00:41:22,500
What's that?

765
00:41:22,860 --> 00:41:24,190
We do not get paid enough.

766
00:41:26,500 --> 00:41:27,670
You got that right.

767
00:41:28,230 --> 00:41:33,530
criminal minds Season 02 Episode 04

768
00:41:34,270 --> 00:41:38,130
SYNC:YTET-cauorr -=bbs.ydy.com=-

769
00:41:38,760 --> 00:41:43,440
--------------------------  bbs.ydy.com Proudly Presents  --------------------------
