1
00:00:02,520 --> 00:00:06,500
<font color=orange>south san francisco,ca</font>

2
00:00:44,220 --> 00:00:45,580
Mom,dad! Dad,we have to go!

3
00:00:45,580 --> 00:00:46,180
What?

4
00:00:46,180 --> 00:00:47,930
The house is on fire,we have to get out of here!

5
00:00:48,300 --> 00:00:49,290
Come on,we have to go!

6
00:00:50,210 --> 00:00:52,240
The phone's dead--go!Come on,we gotta go!

7
00:00:52,240 --> 00:00:54,010
Come on.Stay down.

8
00:00:54,110 --> 00:00:55,500
Stay down.

9
00:02:21,330 --> 00:02:22,470
Somebody!

10
00:02:23,610 --> 00:02:24,850
Somebody!

11
00:02:27,250 --> 00:02:28,720
Somebody,please help us!

12
00:03:47,410 --> 00:03:53,180
<font color=#38B0DE>-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents</font>

13
00:03:53,370 --> 00:04:01,580
<font color=#38B0DE>Sync: YTET-cauorr 芝士蛋糕
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-</font>

14
00:04:01,760 --> 00:04:12,000
<font color=#38B0DE>criminal minds
Season2 Episode19</font>

15
00:04:18,370 --> 00:04:21,650
"The torture of a bad conscience is the hell of a living soul."

16
00:04:22,330 --> 00:04:23,500
John calvin.

17
00:04:24,670 --> 00:04:26,780
Two fires,two families in three weeks.

18
00:04:27,190 --> 00:04:29,120
The first family,the jarvis',

19
00:04:29,310 --> 00:04:30,610
all died.

20
00:04:30,610 --> 00:04:32,370
Last night,the cutlers.

21
00:04:32,750 --> 00:04:34,650
Only one survivor,charlotte cutler,

22
00:04:34,650 --> 00:04:38,730
she's in critical condition with burns to over 60% of her bodY.

23
00:04:38,730 --> 00:04:39,780
Well,it's no accident.

24
00:04:39,780 --> 00:04:42,730
It's the same M.O. No fuses,kerosene,

25
00:04:43,260 --> 00:04:44,550
multiple points of origin,

26
00:04:44,550 --> 00:04:47,430
families targeted at home while they slept.

27
00:04:47,650 --> 00:04:49,340
The bay area has a serial arsonist.

28
00:04:49,340 --> 00:04:52,430
Statistically,94% of all serial arsonists are male,

29
00:04:52,430 --> 00:04:55,030
75% are white,and few,

30
00:04:55,030 --> 00:04:56,520
if any,are ever caught.

31
00:04:56,520 --> 00:04:57,520
Few?

32
00:04:57,760 --> 00:04:58,800
You don't have a percentage?

33
00:04:58,800 --> 00:04:59,850
About 16%,

34
00:04:59,990 --> 00:05:02,930
and those 16% set 30-plus fires before they were ever apprehended.

35
00:05:02,930 --> 00:05:04,630
I'm trying to be more conversational.

36
00:05:05,260 --> 00:05:06,840
Oh.It's not working.

37
00:05:07,930 --> 00:05:10,610
Most serial arsonists don't intend to inflict harm.

38
00:05:10,820 --> 00:05:12,700
Injuries or death,those are accidental.

39
00:05:12,850 --> 00:05:14,090
It's not about violence.

40
00:05:14,090 --> 00:05:15,150
For this one it is.

41
00:05:16,040 --> 00:05:17,360
It's also about power.

42
00:05:17,860 --> 00:05:20,110
Seeing the destructive force of their fires.

43
00:05:20,320 --> 00:05:21,660
Watching the chaos,

44
00:05:22,340 --> 00:05:25,090
for them,fire's just a substitute for sexual release.

45
00:05:25,090 --> 00:05:28,030
Oh,great,so if these guys don't get laid,they start fires?

46
00:05:28,030 --> 00:05:30,530
Or in this case,burn entire families to death.

47
00:05:32,540 --> 00:05:34,060
-No statistic?
-Nope.

48
00:05:34,950 --> 00:05:36,510
They don't have statistics on this guy.

49
00:05:37,660 --> 00:05:38,440
One of a kind.

50
00:05:38,670 --> 00:05:39,850
Thank god.

51
00:05:40,080 --> 00:05:45,390
Three weeks ago,this serial arsonist escalated into a serial killer whose weapon is fire.

52
00:05:45,770 --> 00:05:46,580
Why?

53
00:05:46,750 --> 00:05:48,090
Major event.

54
00:05:48,530 --> 00:05:51,340
Possibly the breakup of his primary sexual outlet.

55
00:05:51,770 --> 00:05:53,520
The separation,the loss.

56
00:05:54,100 --> 00:05:55,140
all right What about the victims?

57
00:05:55,360 --> 00:05:57,830
Sfpd can't connect the jarvis' and the cutlers,

58
00:05:57,830 --> 00:06:02,880
but witnesses put an unidentified late model gold sedan near both fires.

59
00:06:03,040 --> 00:06:03,670
Run the car.

60
00:06:03,670 --> 00:06:05,340
Garcia,run the victims through the system,

61
00:06:05,340 --> 00:06:06,910
if there's any connection we need to find it.

62
00:06:06,910 --> 00:06:07,560
Yes,sir.

63
00:06:07,560 --> 00:06:08,640
We need victimology.

64
00:06:09,420 --> 00:06:10,980
I'll go see charlotte cutler.

65
00:06:11,590 --> 00:06:12,940
You took the burn one last timE.

66
00:06:13,550 --> 00:06:14,480
It's all right.I got it.

67
00:06:34,250 --> 00:06:36,070
Has she said anything about the fires?

68
00:06:36,470 --> 00:06:38,500
I'm giving her as much painkiller as I can.

69
00:06:39,040 --> 00:06:40,540
She asked about her husband and son.

70
00:06:40,980 --> 00:06:43,230
She passed out again before I had to answer.

71
00:06:43,350 --> 00:06:44,520
So she doesn't know.

72
00:06:46,630 --> 00:06:47,940
Whatever you tell her,

73
00:06:47,940 --> 00:06:50,130
she won't live long enough to know different.

74
00:06:52,250 --> 00:06:53,670
I'll be right back.

75
00:06:56,200 --> 00:06:59,710
-Did she just tell us to lie to a material witness?
-No.

76
00:07:01,620 --> 00:07:03,630
She told us that we could.

77
00:07:13,180 --> 00:07:14,970
Welcome.Ricardo vega,sffdr.

78
00:07:15,450 --> 00:07:17,670
Hi.Jason gideon,this is derek morgan.

79
00:07:18,000 --> 00:07:19,980
Most likely the arson suspect is a first responder

80
00:07:19,980 --> 00:07:24,060
who set both fires with premeditative intent to return to it within a professional capacity.

81
00:07:24,060 --> 00:07:24,960
You read my paper.

82
00:07:24,960 --> 00:07:26,270
"Profiles of a serial arsonist,"

83
00:07:26,270 --> 00:07:27,810
I make everyone on my team read it.

84
00:07:28,090 --> 00:07:29,680
I've run the first responders of both fires,

85
00:07:29,680 --> 00:07:32,080
these are the pedigrees of everyone that was here that night.

86
00:07:32,540 --> 00:07:34,800
No fire,police,or emt responded to both.

87
00:07:35,520 --> 00:07:36,700
-No one 
-except me,

88
00:07:36,820 --> 00:07:39,670
which is why I've included copies of my department performance reviews,

89
00:07:39,670 --> 00:07:41,000
medical records,and psych-evals.

90
00:07:41,000 --> 00:07:42,810
-It's unnecessary.
-No,it's not.

91
00:07:43,470 --> 00:07:46,640
Your best suspect is a fireman who saw both fires burning.That's me.

92
00:07:47,870 --> 00:07:49,120
I'm saving you time.

93
00:07:49,890 --> 00:07:51,100
Come on,I'll walk you through it.

94
00:07:56,980 --> 00:07:58,290
Mrs. Cutler?

95
00:07:59,330 --> 00:08:00,910
I'm special agent aaron hotchner,

96
00:08:01,290 --> 00:08:03,280
-this is special agent emily prentiss.
-Hello.

97
00:08:04,750 --> 00:08:06,130
Where's paul?

98
00:08:06,680 --> 00:08:07,770
Your son

99
00:08:08,290 --> 00:08:09,580
was with you the night of the fire.

100
00:08:09,580 --> 00:08:10,720
That's why we're here.

101
00:08:11,500 --> 00:08:12,900
I don't understand.

102
00:08:13,390 --> 00:08:14,680
We're fbi agents.

103
00:08:15,220 --> 00:08:17,710
We think that the fire may have been set intentionallY.

104
00:08:18,000 --> 00:08:19,640
I'm very tired.

105
00:08:20,300 --> 00:08:21,360
I understand.

106
00:08:21,500 --> 00:08:23,050
This is very important.

107
00:08:23,050 --> 00:08:25,570
Do you think you could just give us a couple of minutes?

108
00:08:28,220 --> 00:08:30,110
I want you to think back to that night.

109
00:08:30,510 --> 00:08:32,450
Was there anything out of the ordinary?

110
00:08:35,610 --> 00:08:38,840
Think about the things that you normally do.

111
00:08:40,100 --> 00:08:41,250
Uh,get undressed,

112
00:08:41,250 --> 00:08:42,330
wash your face

113
00:08:42,550 --> 00:08:44,290
I couldn't brush my teeth.

114
00:08:44,940 --> 00:08:46,040
Dennis?

115
00:08:46,040 --> 00:08:47,610
The water's not working.

116
00:08:48,500 --> 00:08:49,500
I'll check it out.

117
00:08:50,820 --> 00:08:53,610
Dennis got the water back on.

118
00:08:55,190 --> 00:08:56,720
Then

119
00:08:57,630 --> 00:09:00,180
then you went to bed?

120
00:09:02,580 --> 00:09:04,330
Do you remember what woke you up?

121
00:09:04,980 --> 00:09:07,710
-Paul.
-Not the smoke alarms?

122
00:09:10,940 --> 00:09:12,210
It was paul.

123
00:09:13,250 --> 00:09:14,780
What else do you remember?

124
00:09:19,050 --> 00:09:21,160
Dennis unlocked it and it wouldn't open.

125
00:09:22,530 --> 00:09:23,430
He unlocked what?

126
00:09:23,430 --> 00:09:24,910
The front door!

127
00:09:25,200 --> 00:09:28,330
Somebody please help us,please!

128
00:09:33,240 --> 00:09:34,510
What's wrong?!

129
00:09:34,510 --> 00:09:35,780
I ca

130
00:09:41,250 --> 00:09:42,720
Somebody!

131
00:09:45,050 --> 00:09:47,560
Somebody,Please help us,please

132
00:09:53,440 --> 00:09:55,170
And then I saw the fireman.

133
00:09:57,980 --> 00:09:59,670
and****ok

134
00:10:02,250 --> 00:10:03,680
Dennis?

135
00:10:03,680 --> 00:10:06,140
Paul where's my baby?

136
00:10:06,140 --> 00:10:08,280
Paul.Where are they?Are they ok?

137
00:10:08,870 --> 00:10:10,050
They're fine.

138
00:10:10,820 --> 00:10:12,420
They're just outside in the waiting room.

139
00:10:13,860 --> 00:10:20,280
Ohh  oh,right.

140
00:10:27,170 --> 00:10:29,340
I don't want them to see me like this.

141
00:10:30,450 --> 00:10:31,920
No,I'm not ready.Could you--

142
00:10:32,460 --> 00:10:34,990
please tell them to wait a minute,please?

143
00:10:34,990 --> 00:10:36,470
I'm not ready.

144
00:10:37,110 --> 00:10:38,740
Agent prentiss will tell them.

145
00:10:39,040 --> 00:10:40,580
You call gideon and morgan?

146
00:10:47,670 --> 00:10:49,840
I can stay with you until you're ready.

147
00:10:50,610 --> 00:10:52,230
If you'd like.

148
00:10:54,340 --> 00:10:56,630
I'd like that.

149
00:11:15,840 --> 00:11:18,220
She told her husband there was no water.

150
00:11:19,660 --> 00:11:21,110
Where's the shut-off?

151
00:11:21,110 --> 00:11:22,660
Runs up the sidewalk.

152
00:11:24,350 --> 00:11:25,970
Ok,so I'm the unsub.

153
00:11:33,810 --> 00:11:35,260
I need to get in the house.

154
00:11:38,730 --> 00:11:40,900
So I turn the water off right here.

155
00:11:44,160 --> 00:11:46,230
And then I wait.

156
00:11:53,310 --> 00:11:55,190
I wait for him to come outside.

157
00:12:03,380 --> 00:12:05,110
I wait for them to go to sleep

158
00:12:10,610 --> 00:12:12,430
and then I carefully pour the fuel.

159
00:12:19,070 --> 00:12:20,860
Cutting access to the back door.

160
00:12:23,520 --> 00:12:25,570
I leave them only one way to get out.

161
00:12:33,080 --> 00:12:35,340
<font color=orange>S.F.F.D. Headquarters 
SAN FRANCISCO,CA</font>

162
00:12:35,420 --> 00:12:37,400
This place is great!They have their own espresso machine.

163
00:12:37,700 --> 00:12:40,120
Dr. Reid,this is detective castro,

164
00:12:40,120 --> 00:12:42,260
she is with the sfpd liaison.

165
00:12:42,260 --> 00:12:44,370
Burned my hand on that espresso machine.

166
00:12:44,370 --> 00:12:45,340
Ooh!

167
00:12:45,340 --> 00:12:46,430
A genius,you said?

168
00:12:46,430 --> 00:12:47,040
Yeah,uh,

169
00:12:47,040 --> 00:12:49,570
his coordination drops off when he's thinking.

170
00:12:49,570 --> 00:12:50,120
Good.

171
00:12:50,120 --> 00:12:53,280
'Cause we need to figure out why this psycho chooses these families.

172
00:12:53,870 --> 00:12:55,570
He's most likely targeting the men.

173
00:12:55,860 --> 00:12:57,900
They're the only similar members of the two families.

174
00:12:57,900 --> 00:13:00,400
C. Jarvis,29,worked full-time.

175
00:13:00,400 --> 00:13:02,770
Charlotte cutler,39,was a stay-at-home mom.

176
00:13:02,770 --> 00:13:05,670
The jarvis' had two girls in public grade school,

177
00:13:05,910 --> 00:13:07,540
cutler's had a son in private high school.

178
00:13:07,540 --> 00:13:09,470
The jarvis' went to church,the cutlers didn'T.

179
00:13:09,470 --> 00:13:10,580
Nothing holds.

180
00:13:10,580 --> 00:13:11,370
Except with the men--

181
00:13:11,370 --> 00:13:12,950
both in their late thirties,white,

182
00:13:12,950 --> 00:13:15,290
approximately 6-feet tall,brown hair,

183
00:13:15,290 --> 00:13:17,980
nice homes,nice families,good jobs,

184
00:13:18,120 --> 00:13:19,290
that's the connection.

185
00:13:19,640 --> 00:13:20,630
What connection?

186
00:13:20,850 --> 00:13:21,720
Cutler was a lawyer,

187
00:13:21,720 --> 00:13:22,970
jarvis an executive.

188
00:13:22,970 --> 00:13:24,330
There's no evidence they ever met.

189
00:13:24,330 --> 00:13:25,510
But they're of the same type.

190
00:13:25,510 --> 00:13:27,840
We know that most serial arsonists are white males.

191
00:13:27,840 --> 00:13:29,910
A complex M.O.Develops over time.

192
00:13:30,600 --> 00:13:31,680
This guy is in his mid-thirties,

193
00:13:31,680 --> 00:13:34,880
he sees the victims as successful versions of himself.

194
00:13:34,880 --> 00:13:36,340
And he resents them for it.

195
00:13:38,000 --> 00:13:39,070
I'll issue an A.P.B.

196
00:13:39,650 --> 00:13:41,050
For a resentful 6-foot white guy.

197
00:13:48,100 --> 00:13:50,580
Ok,great.I got it.Thanks.

198
00:13:51,050 --> 00:13:52,240
Charlotte cutler died.

199
00:13:53,120 --> 00:13:54,050
I'm sorry.

200
00:13:54,050 --> 00:13:54,930
Next time I'll go.

201
00:13:54,930 --> 00:13:56,350
What have we got on the vehicle?

202
00:13:56,350 --> 00:13:59,750
Uh,it is a 1999 gold ford taurus.

203
00:13:59,750 --> 00:14:04,210
85% of that model color-combo were sold domestically as fleet vehicles.

204
00:14:04,210 --> 00:14:05,160
Company cars,

205
00:14:05,160 --> 00:14:06,680
rental fleets.

206
00:14:07,080 --> 00:14:08,040
Did you check all agencies?

207
00:14:08,040 --> 00:14:09,870
Yeah,none of them kept them for the past three weeks,

208
00:14:09,870 --> 00:14:10,870
or rented during both fires,

209
00:14:10,870 --> 00:14:11,960
so

210
00:14:11,960 --> 00:14:15,120
who keeps a rental car for three weeks?

211
00:14:15,120 --> 00:14:15,990
Then it's not a rental.

212
00:14:15,990 --> 00:14:17,430
It would have to be a company car.

213
00:14:17,430 --> 00:14:20,000
This guy,he had to have time to stalk his victims.

214
00:14:20,990 --> 00:14:22,020
And if his job involves driving--

215
00:14:22,020 --> 00:14:25,050
there was a serial arsonist up in seattle,early nineties

216
00:14:25,280 --> 00:14:26,630
-paul kenneth keller.
-Yeah.

217
00:14:26,880 --> 00:14:28,420
He used to drive around all day selling

218
00:14:28,420 --> 00:14:30,170
advertising for his dad's agency,

219
00:14:30,650 --> 00:14:32,020
picking out places to burn.

220
00:14:32,560 --> 00:14:34,190
Company car.Good work,J.J.

221
00:14:35,380 --> 00:14:36,740
Let's do the profile.

222
00:14:39,310 --> 00:14:41,870
The unsub we're looking for is a highly intelligent,

223
00:14:41,870 --> 00:14:44,900
under-achieving,35 to 45-year-old white male

224
00:14:44,900 --> 00:14:47,270
with a severe narcissistic character disorder.

225
00:14:47,970 --> 00:14:49,700
Nothing in his life works for long.

226
00:14:50,730 --> 00:14:52,190
If he was married,he's now divorced.

227
00:14:53,050 --> 00:14:54,450
If employed,it won't last.

228
00:14:55,070 --> 00:14:56,380
What he wants is admiration,

229
00:14:56,600 --> 00:14:58,390
but he's got no respect for others--

230
00:14:58,390 --> 00:15:00,870
not their feelings,and most certainly not their safety.

231
00:15:00,870 --> 00:15:02,210
He feels entitled.

232
00:15:02,390 --> 00:15:04,030
He's like a petulant adolescent.

233
00:15:04,030 --> 00:15:07,810
He both resents and he absolutely expects everyone to take care of him.

234
00:15:07,810 --> 00:15:10,040
And given that a male relative wouldn't tolerate this behavior,

235
00:15:10,040 --> 00:15:12,410
he most likely lives with a female relative

236
00:15:12,410 --> 00:15:14,940
his mother,grandmother,aunt,whom he exploits.

237
00:15:15,120 --> 00:15:16,590
His arson kit is expensive.

238
00:15:17,360 --> 00:15:18,390
Fire suit,

239
00:15:18,390 --> 00:15:19,460
oxygen mask.

240
00:15:19,980 --> 00:15:20,970
This suggests that he may be employed,

241
00:15:20,970 --> 00:15:25,050
but his personality will not allow him to work closely with others in an office setting.

242
00:15:25,050 --> 00:15:28,200
This along with the information about his vehicle lead us to believe that

243
00:15:29,160 --> 00:15:30,840
he's a traveling salesman of some sort,

244
00:15:30,840 --> 00:15:34,270
who works for a company big enough not to notice that he's a sociopath.

245
00:15:35,060 --> 00:15:37,220
Ok,this scumbag has issues,we all get it.

246
00:15:38,570 --> 00:15:39,640
But why fire?

247
00:15:39,640 --> 00:15:41,660
He's like a drug addict.

248
00:15:41,660 --> 00:15:43,430
Only fire's his drug.

249
00:15:43,430 --> 00:15:44,890
Each time an addict needs a fix,

250
00:15:44,890 --> 00:15:46,710
they need more of the drug to get off.

251
00:15:46,710 --> 00:15:48,980
So his crimes most likely get much worse.

252
00:15:49,490 --> 00:15:52,260
It would be almost impossible for him to quit without help.

253
00:15:57,720 --> 00:15:59,160
Thank you very much.

254
00:16:00,110 --> 00:16:02,410
She shoots  she scores!

255
00:16:02,540 --> 00:16:05,250
The crowd goes wild.

256
00:16:06,530 --> 00:16:08,610
I just put the entire department on tac alert.

257
00:16:09,950 --> 00:16:11,230
Garcia's on line one.

258
00:16:13,540 --> 00:16:14,650
Brace yourselves.

259
00:16:14,650 --> 00:16:16,660
I'm gonna teach you the meaning of lust.

260
00:16:17,150 --> 00:16:18,250
-Did she say lust?
-Mm-hmm.

261
00:16:18,730 --> 00:16:21,310
I cross-referenced every known fact on the victims,

262
00:16:21,310 --> 00:16:24,100
and I just found a website that links both dennis cutler

263
00:16:24,100 --> 00:16:29,040
and matthew jarvis' companies on a list of businesses guilty of L.U.S.T.

264
00:16:29,040 --> 00:16:30,090
I'm missing something.

265
00:16:30,090 --> 00:16:31,780
Leaking underground storage tanks.

266
00:16:32,320 --> 00:16:36,350
The website belongs to a recently founded san francisco chapter of the earth defense front.

267
00:16:36,350 --> 00:16:37,360
The edf?

268
00:16:37,670 --> 00:16:38,960
The eco-terrorist group?

269
00:16:38,960 --> 00:16:41,180
They aren't eco-terrorists,they're environmental activists.

270
00:16:41,180 --> 00:16:43,410
Dennis cutler and matthew jarvis may disagree with you.

271
00:16:43,410 --> 00:16:48,160
I'm pretty sure some edf people were sent up for torching an suv dealership a while back in san diego.

272
00:16:48,160 --> 00:16:49,430
Nobody died in those fires.

273
00:16:49,480 --> 00:16:50,840
Maybe they got lucky.

274
00:16:50,840 --> 00:16:52,110
No,it's not luck.

275
00:16:52,110 --> 00:16:54,070
This group's dedicated to protecting life.

276
00:16:54,070 --> 00:16:56,810
What,do they wait until no one's home and then light the place up?

277
00:16:56,810 --> 00:16:58,030
That's exactly what they do.

278
00:16:58,560 --> 00:17:00,220
So tell me who we're playing again today.

279
00:17:00,220 --> 00:17:00,840
We play the jets.

280
00:17:00,840 --> 00:17:02,180
The jets,right,ok.

281
00:17:02,330 --> 00:17:04,180
I'll be-- in a second.

282
00:17:05,140 --> 00:17:05,770
Katie!

283
00:17:06,220 --> 00:17:08,720
Come on.We're not gonna be late twice in one week.

284
00:17:10,400 --> 00:17:13,040
-Yeah?
-I'coming!

285
00:17:14,000 --> 00:17:15,020
Come on,sweetie.

286
00:17:15,340 --> 00:17:16,600
RighT.

287
00:17:17,290 --> 00:17:18,740
No,I got that.

288
00:17:19,180 --> 00:17:19,760
Yeah.

289
00:17:19,790 --> 00:17:20,420
No,we're leavin'--

290
00:17:20,420 --> 00:17:21,720
we're leavin' right now.

291
00:17:21,720 --> 00:17:22,820
Yeah.

292
00:17:25,060 --> 00:17:26,340
All right,guys.

293
00:17:26,340 --> 00:17:27,560
We ready?

294
00:17:29,290 --> 00:17:30,490
Belt.

295
00:17:30,490 --> 00:17:31,870
Oh,yeah.

296
00:17:34,240 --> 00:17:35,440
-What's wrong?
-I don't know.

297
00:17:35,670 --> 00:17:36,890
It's not opening.

298
00:17:36,890 --> 00:17:38,920
Are you telling me that the fbi doesn't have

299
00:17:39,380 --> 00:17:42,430
files on organizations like this?Lists and members?

300
00:17:42,830 --> 00:17:45,540
Domestic groups like the edf aren't the bureau's top priority right now.

301
00:17:45,540 --> 00:17:48,050
Besides,they're more of a movement than an organization.

302
00:17:48,430 --> 00:17:49,850
There's a central ideology,

303
00:17:50,580 --> 00:17:51,350
but-- chapters are independent,

304
00:17:51,350 --> 00:17:53,850
they don't pay dues and they don't keep membership lists.

305
00:17:54,100 --> 00:17:57,690
What if one of the chapters has broken ranks and has a new belief?

306
00:17:58,090 --> 00:17:59,250
dad?

307
00:17:59,940 --> 00:18:01,140
What are you doing?!

308
00:18:01,690 --> 00:18:02,710
Hey!Get out,guys,

309
00:18:02,710 --> 00:18:03,440
get out!Get out!

310
00:18:03,500 --> 00:18:04,620
-get out!kids,Get out now!
-dad,It's not opening!

311
00:18:04,620 --> 00:18:06,300
-Come on,It won't open,dad!
-Open the door!Get out!

312
00:18:10,990 --> 00:18:12,170
Hurting people's never been part of it.

313
00:18:12,170 --> 00:18:13,030
Doesn't track.

314
00:18:13,320 --> 00:18:14,350
Doesn't fit the profile.

315
00:18:14,540 --> 00:18:18,050
Garcia,can you identify how many members are in this particular edf chapter?

316
00:18:18,050 --> 00:18:21,700
Uh,it looks like  a hundred to 150.

317
00:18:21,700 --> 00:18:23,720
-What are you doing?!
-It's not opening!

318
00:18:24,780 --> 00:18:28,050
-I'm scared,dad!I'm scared!
-Doors open--open!

319
00:18:28,480 --> 00:18:30,890
Start the car!I'm trying-- it won't start.

320
00:18:30,930 --> 00:18:31,930
Hurry!

321
00:18:31,930 --> 00:18:33,080
I'm scared,dad,I'm scared!

322
00:18:33,080 --> 00:18:34,590
Come on,get out!

323
00:18:35,440 --> 00:18:35,980
Get out!Keep trying!Keep trying!

324
00:18:35,980 --> 00:18:38,960
Come on!Keep trying-- what are you doing?!

325
00:19:01,330 --> 00:19:04,020
Thomas R. Dunleavy,dunbrook development group.

326
00:19:06,230 --> 00:19:07,020
On the list.

327
00:19:07,020 --> 00:19:10,670
Ok,I'm sending you a file on the edf leader.

328
00:19:10,990 --> 00:19:14,210
Evan abby,41,5'11'',185 pounds.

329
00:19:14,570 --> 00:19:15,460
Thanks,garcia.

330
00:19:15,460 --> 00:19:18,110
Pardon me for asking,sir,but how do we even know he's involved?

331
00:19:18,160 --> 00:19:20,540
We don'T.That's why we're interviewing abby at the crime scene.

332
00:19:20,790 --> 00:19:22,210
If he is the leader of the edf,

333
00:19:22,550 --> 00:19:25,190
his reaction to all this should tell us exactly what we need to know.

334
00:19:29,590 --> 00:19:30,580
Where do you guys want it?

335
00:19:30,970 --> 00:19:32,030
This is the spot.

336
00:19:32,200 --> 00:19:32,990
When he arrives,

337
00:19:32,990 --> 00:19:34,820
bring the fake bodies right past us

338
00:19:35,030 --> 00:19:35,990
nice and slow.

339
00:19:36,700 --> 00:19:37,970
I want him to get a good look.

340
00:19:38,580 --> 00:19:40,320
Remind me to never play poker with you guys.

341
00:19:43,800 --> 00:19:45,100
So what do we have on this guy?

342
00:19:45,850 --> 00:19:47,280
-Hotch!
-What?

343
00:19:47,590 --> 00:19:49,100
What do we have on the edf leader?

344
00:19:49,100 --> 00:19:52,830
Evan abby,41,divorced,father of liam,14.

345
00:19:53,110 --> 00:19:54,260
Environmental engineer,

346
00:19:54,810 --> 00:19:56,950
does consults on real estate projects,

347
00:19:56,950 --> 00:19:58,970
has worked with every company on the edf list.

348
00:19:59,780 --> 00:20:00,900
Can't wait to meet him.

349
00:20:07,660 --> 00:20:10,450
Mr. Abby,these are special agents jason gideon and aaron hotchner.

350
00:20:10,450 --> 00:20:11,840
Thank you for coming.

351
00:20:12,460 --> 00:20:16,070
Um,agent prentiss said you needed my help with a L.U.S.T.Related fire?

352
00:20:16,070 --> 00:20:17,670
Yeah,it's pretty bad.

353
00:20:18,770 --> 00:20:20,330
Tom,brad,katie dunleavy.

354
00:20:21,050 --> 00:20:22,060
All burned to death.

355
00:20:23,590 --> 00:20:24,810
Whew.

356
00:20:25,660 --> 00:20:27,520
Uh so,um,where's the--

357
00:20:27,520 --> 00:20:29,180
uh,where's the leaking storage tank?

358
00:20:29,180 --> 00:20:30,280
Katie was only 12.

359
00:20:32,230 --> 00:20:33,960
You've got a son about that age,don't you?

360
00:20:36,170 --> 00:20:37,630
Did you know tom dunleavy?

361
00:20:39,450 --> 00:20:40,120
What is this?

362
00:20:40,120 --> 00:20:41,880
He worked for dunbrook development group.

363
00:20:42,450 --> 00:20:43,760
Why are you asking me these questions?

364
00:20:43,760 --> 00:20:45,380
You posted dunbrook on your website.

365
00:20:46,100 --> 00:20:46,910
My website?

366
00:20:46,910 --> 00:20:48,930
Look,I came down here voluntarily

367
00:20:48,930 --> 00:20:51,250
because I was told you needed help with a L.U.S.T.Related fire.

368
00:20:51,250 --> 00:20:52,740
Three fires .

369
00:20:53,460 --> 00:20:54,870
three families

370
00:20:56,080 --> 00:20:56,880
three fathers

371
00:20:57,450 --> 00:21:00,100
who worked for companies posted on your edf website.

372
00:21:00,100 --> 00:21:01,130
All burned to death.

373
00:21:01,560 --> 00:21:03,750
You worked for these companies-- every one on your list.

374
00:21:04,330 --> 00:21:05,670
Are you accusing me of a crime?

375
00:21:06,430 --> 00:21:07,410
What do you think?

376
00:21:07,410 --> 00:21:09,640
Mr. Abby,I support your cause.

377
00:21:10,190 --> 00:21:11,560
But I reject these methods.

378
00:21:12,190 --> 00:21:15,190
I don't know what cause or methods you're referring to.

379
00:21:15,190 --> 00:21:16,200
You created the site,

380
00:21:16,200 --> 00:21:18,300
you posted the list,you're the leader of the edf.

381
00:21:18,880 --> 00:21:21,500
Well,if you could prove that,we wouldn't be having this conversation,would we?

382
00:21:22,300 --> 00:21:23,910
Mr. Abby,people are dying.

383
00:21:24,830 --> 00:21:26,010
Children,mr. Abby.

384
00:21:26,520 --> 00:21:29,420
We know edf's strategy has always supported violence.

385
00:21:29,420 --> 00:21:32,470
I'm asking you,has edf's strategy changed?

386
00:21:33,740 --> 00:21:35,310
No.It hasn'T.

387
00:21:41,500 --> 00:21:42,970
He could barely look at this.

388
00:21:44,120 --> 00:21:46,640
A serial arsonist wouldn't be able to peel his eyes away.

389
00:21:46,830 --> 00:21:48,080
He's hiding somethinG.

390
00:21:48,080 --> 00:21:50,320
More than just his support for the edf.

391
00:21:50,320 --> 00:21:51,300
Hey,it occurred to me

392
00:21:51,650 --> 00:21:56,260
if all I knew about the edf was that they went around burning down suv dealerships

393
00:21:56,260 --> 00:21:58,500
and housing developments

394
00:21:58,500 --> 00:22:00,010
well,that's a common misconception.

395
00:22:00,430 --> 00:22:01,500
That's my point.

396
00:22:02,110 --> 00:22:03,700
What if our profile is right--

397
00:22:03,700 --> 00:22:06,160
and the unsub held the same misconception?

398
00:22:06,160 --> 00:22:07,120
He wants to fit in,

399
00:22:07,560 --> 00:22:09,640
he wants people around him to appreciate what he does,

400
00:22:10,400 --> 00:22:13,750
isn't it possible that the unsub joined the edf  thinking--

401
00:22:13,750 --> 00:22:15,350
it was an arsonist's club?

402
00:22:15,350 --> 00:22:17,030
Sure.That's possible.

403
00:22:17,090 --> 00:22:21,200
If we give abby our unsub's profile could he help us identify him?

404
00:22:21,200 --> 00:22:22,450
We can't give abby the profile,

405
00:22:22,450 --> 00:22:24,160
not until we find out what he's hiding.

406
00:22:24,380 --> 00:22:28,180
Still,it seems abby's our best chance of finding the unsub.

407
00:22:28,180 --> 00:22:29,640
You want abby or the ex-wife?

408
00:22:30,040 --> 00:22:31,000
Abby.

409
00:22:38,900 --> 00:22:41,700
At berkeley 20 years ago,evan was a different person.

1
00:22:38,690 --> 00:22:39,860
At berkeley 20 years ago,

2
00:22:39,910 --> 00:22:42,170
evan was a different person.

3
00:22:42,270 --> 00:22:43,400
In every way.

4
00:22:43,680 --> 00:22:46,320
Warm,funny,honest.

5
00:22:46,810 --> 00:22:48,320
Even naive.

6
00:22:48,410 --> 00:22:49,310
What happened?

7
00:22:49,370 --> 00:22:50,710
We had school loans,

8
00:22:50,780 --> 00:22:52,770
I got pregnant   

9
00:22:53,560 --> 00:22:55,350
his job 

10
00:22:56,190 --> 00:22:58,990
evan was an environmental consultant.

11
00:22:59,070 --> 00:23:02,100
Builder's hired him to help them
clean up their sites.

12
00:23:02,480 --> 00:23:04,450
Make sure they were up to epa code.

13
00:23:04,530 --> 00:23:07,310
Evan thought they hired him
to do the right thing.

14
00:23:07,400 --> 00:23:08,150
- Did he? - No.

15
00:23:08,210 --> 00:23:11,350
Developers don't care about mercury
in the groundwater.

16
00:23:11,440 --> 00:23:15,400
They just want to pass inspection as fast
and cheap as possible.

17
00:23:15,490 --> 00:23:16,940
He had a budget,

18
00:23:17,000 --> 00:23:18,990
it was never enough,

19
00:23:19,040 --> 00:23:21,250
but they didn't care how he spent it,

20
00:23:21,310 --> 00:23:23,790
as long as they passed inspection.

21
00:23:23,880 --> 00:23:25,710
Well,how did evan deal with that?

22
00:23:25,790 --> 00:23:27,340
He drank.

23
00:23:28,290 --> 00:23:29,400
It got bad.

24
00:23:30,180 --> 00:23:31,070
How bad?

25
00:23:31,160 --> 00:23:33,200
I thought he might hurt himself.

26
00:23:33,280 --> 00:23:35,220
I didn't know if he could live with it.

27
00:23:36,290 --> 00:23:38,610
How's his relationship with your son liam?

28
00:23:38,670 --> 00:23:40,280
He doesn't have one.

29
00:23:40,580 --> 00:23:45,050
I had to threaten to take him to court
to get him to pay child support.

30
00:23:45,600 --> 00:23:50,850
Must've either scared the hell out of him
or really pissed him off.

31
00:23:51,200 --> 00:23:51,940
Why's that?

32
00:23:51,990 --> 00:23:56,240
Because every sunday night
for the past 9 months 

33
00:23:56,310 --> 00:24:00,360
he tosses $2,000 cash
through the mail slot.

34
00:24:01,300 --> 00:24:03,740
He left long before I threw him out.

35
00:24:05,910 --> 00:24:07,160
I don't know.

36
00:24:09,080 --> 00:24:09,940
I will.

37
00:24:10,710 --> 00:24:12,900
But I promise
I'm going to give it to you.

38
00:24:13,000 --> 00:24:13,750
Ok.

39
00:24:13,840 --> 00:24:14,840
I love you,too.

40
00:24:17,440 --> 00:24:18,750
 Everything ok?

41
00:24:19,080 --> 00:24:19,780
Yeah.

42
00:24:20,020 --> 00:24:21,410
You know,
for a guy claiming to be innocent,

43
00:24:21,480 --> 00:24:23,230
he's acting pretty guilty.

44
00:24:23,360 --> 00:24:27,920
I never underestimate the effect being confronted
by the fbi will have on a suspect.

45
00:24:28,030 --> 00:24:29,120
I don't think he's effected,

46
00:24:29,210 --> 00:24:30,580
I think he's freaked out.

47
00:24:30,660 --> 00:24:31,960
In the time we've been watching him,

48
00:24:32,020 --> 00:24:34,580
he's packed his belongings into
cardboard boxes,

49
00:24:34,640 --> 00:24:37,210
hit his attorney's office and 4 banks.

50
00:24:37,480 --> 00:24:39,410
It does look like
he's getting ready to run.

51
00:24:39,490 --> 00:24:41,070
The question is,what do we do?

52
00:24:43,970 --> 00:24:45,070
For now,nothing.

53
00:24:45,600 --> 00:24:46,910
We just watcH.

54
00:24:54,430 --> 00:24:55,850
All those people?

55
00:24:55,940 --> 00:24:57,580
No booze or music?

56
00:24:57,710 --> 00:25:01,250
That's either a very lame
going away party or an edf meeting.

57
00:25:01,600 --> 00:25:03,650
We need to set surveillance up.
Grab your camera.

58
00:25:03,690 --> 00:25:04,750
Where should I set up?

59
00:25:04,830 --> 00:25:05,800
Right here.

60
00:25:06,290 --> 00:25:07,470
If he's hiding something,

61
00:25:07,560 --> 00:25:08,350
we don't have a warrant,

62
00:25:08,430 --> 00:25:09,750
we don't have supplies,

63
00:25:09,890 --> 00:25:11,470
you want to intimidate him.

64
00:25:11,520 --> 00:25:14,180
I want another chance to find out
what he's hiding.

65
00:25:14,970 --> 00:25:15,970
Ok 

66
00:25:18,260 --> 00:25:19,880
smile,everybody.

67
00:25:50,020 --> 00:25:51,980
it looks like intimidation worked.

68
00:26:00,430 --> 00:26:01,970
So what is it with you?

69
00:26:02,580 --> 00:26:04,400
Shoving a bunch of dead kids
in my face wasn't enough?

70
00:26:04,470 --> 00:26:06,900
Thought I needed a little harassment,too?

71
00:26:07,300 --> 00:26:08,600
It's over,all right?

72
00:26:08,670 --> 00:26:10,830
I denounced the fires
and the people responsible for them,

73
00:26:10,890 --> 00:26:12,730
and I just disbanded the edf.

74
00:26:12,770 --> 00:26:14,440
If the edf had nothing to do with the fires,

75
00:26:14,510 --> 00:26:15,750
why would you disband?

76
00:26:15,820 --> 00:26:18,150
Do you have kids,agent hotchner?

77
00:26:18,230 --> 00:26:19,420
I have a son like you.

78
00:26:19,510 --> 00:26:20,540
Good.Then I'm gonna tell you this,

79
00:26:20,550 --> 00:26:21,990
one father to another.

80
00:26:22,350 --> 00:26:24,260
I started the edf for my son.

81
00:26:24,380 --> 00:26:25,210
And yours.

82
00:26:25,800 --> 00:26:28,170
Not to have some other guy's son
burn to death.

83
00:26:30,280 --> 00:26:31,980
Hope your pictures come out.

84
00:26:34,810 --> 00:26:37,330
Prentiss,does he look like
he weighs 185 to you?

85
00:26:37,400 --> 00:26:39,080
165,maybe.

86
00:26:39,130 --> 00:26:42,140
Why would he hold a meeting
when he knew we were watching?

87
00:26:42,180 --> 00:26:43,530
He wanted us to see it.

88
00:26:44,760 --> 00:26:47,970
He wanted to make sure that we saw him
trying to do the right thing.

89
00:26:48,260 --> 00:26:49,580
You don't believe him?

90
00:26:54,640 --> 00:26:56,010
I don't know.

91
00:26:57,230 --> 00:27:00,320
He seemed pretty angry for a guy
who's trying to do the right thing.

92
00:27:00,400 --> 00:27:02,760
That's why we need to
get those photos to garcia.

93
00:27:02,860 --> 00:27:04,080
What do you mean?

94
00:27:04,170 --> 00:27:06,870
Either he's angry because
he's guilty of a wrongdoing,

95
00:27:07,750 --> 00:27:11,720
or he's angry because his attempts to do the
right thing with the edf have gotten people killed,

96
00:27:11,800 --> 00:27:15,870
but either way  the arsonist was here tonight.

97
00:27:18,110 --> 00:27:20,530
Yeah,I'll show you a sick,deranged coward,

98
00:27:20,680 --> 00:27:22,650
you ignorant son of a bitch.

99
00:27:40,680 --> 00:27:42,370
Deranged coward.

100
00:27:51,560 --> 00:27:53,710
I'll show you a deranged coward.

101
00:28:54,500 --> 00:28:56,250
The victim was a cpa.

102
00:28:56,370 --> 00:29:00,500
Greg ballou,39,white,6-feet,handsome.

103
00:29:00,580 --> 00:29:02,740
He was talking to his fiance
on his cell when it happened.

104
00:29:02,810 --> 00:29:05,790
This kerosene is the same exact type
used in the other fires.

105
00:29:05,870 --> 00:29:07,990
Well,hotch had abby under surveillance
at the time of the attack,

106
00:29:08,040 --> 00:29:09,380
so we know abby's not the unsub.

107
00:29:09,430 --> 00:29:10,700
Witnesses put the gold sedan here,

108
00:29:10,750 --> 00:29:11,790
so we know this is our guy.

109
00:29:11,860 --> 00:29:13,720
And given that the attack occurred
less than 30 minutes 

110
00:29:13,770 --> 00:29:16,910
after the edf meeting and abby's house
is less than a mile from here.

111
00:29:16,960 --> 00:29:19,090
Chances are the unsub
was at abby's house.

112
00:29:19,190 --> 00:29:21,430
He parked some distance away
and walked.

113
00:29:21,490 --> 00:29:23,940
This victim wasn't even connected
to the edf list.

114
00:29:24,010 --> 00:29:27,230
He was just a guy who looked like
he had a nice life like the others.

115
00:29:27,420 --> 00:29:28,750
The unsub didn't go into a house,

116
00:29:28,810 --> 00:29:30,850
he barely even got out of his car.

117
00:29:30,950 --> 00:29:32,870
There was no planning whatsoever.
Why?

118
00:29:32,950 --> 00:29:34,150
He's evolving.

119
00:29:34,280 --> 00:29:35,290
He's doing it fast.

120
00:29:35,400 --> 00:29:36,560
He's smarter than that.

121
00:29:36,650 --> 00:29:39,530
This was random,impulsive,adolescent.

122
00:29:39,540 --> 00:29:40,350
Like a tantrum.

123
00:29:40,360 --> 00:29:41,260
He's got displaced aggression.

124
00:29:41,270 --> 00:29:43,120
He listens to abby denounce him
and his work,

125
00:29:43,200 --> 00:29:44,740
it enrages him,

126
00:29:44,930 --> 00:29:46,750
and so that's the trigger.

127
00:29:46,830 --> 00:29:48,900
Unsub lashes out immediately.

128
00:29:48,990 --> 00:29:50,730
Well,if he was at abby's
we have him on camera.

129
00:29:50,810 --> 00:29:53,300
It's just a matter of time
before garcia has a suspect list.

130
00:29:53,350 --> 00:29:54,400
He's evolving too rapidly.

131
00:29:54,500 --> 00:29:56,250
He's gonna attack again soon.

132
00:29:56,890 --> 00:29:58,670
We're gonna have to trust
this abby guy with the profile.

133
00:29:58,750 --> 00:29:59,630
Let's go.

134
00:30:08,200 --> 00:30:10,210
He's leaving,
but not the way we thought.

135
00:30:10,310 --> 00:30:10,980
What do you mean?

136
00:30:11,050 --> 00:30:12,760
He's seeing his oncologist.

137
00:30:12,850 --> 00:30:14,260
Ohh,god.

138
00:30:15,820 --> 00:30:17,410
It makes sense.

139
00:30:17,520 --> 00:30:18,090
The banks,

140
00:30:18,170 --> 00:30:19,580
the attorney.

141
00:30:19,770 --> 00:30:21,710
He's putting his affairs in order.

142
00:30:21,810 --> 00:30:22,810
Yeah.

143
00:30:38,020 --> 00:30:39,640
Which one is your son?

144
00:30:42,740 --> 00:30:44,210
Catcher.

145
00:30:44,550 --> 00:30:45,580
Does he know you're here?

146
00:30:45,650 --> 00:30:49,050
I think so,
but we have an arrangement.

147
00:30:49,120 --> 00:30:50,400
What's that?

148
00:30:51,680 --> 00:30:53,690
We both pretend I'm not.

149
00:30:56,010 --> 00:30:56,960
I'm sorry.

150
00:31:02,360 --> 00:31:04,050
How long do you have?

151
00:31:09,430 --> 00:31:11,760
6 months would be a miracle.

152
00:31:11,840 --> 00:31:13,810
And you haven't told anyone?

153
00:31:13,900 --> 00:31:14,960
No.

154
00:31:17,380 --> 00:31:19,060
It's leukemia.

155
00:31:20,450 --> 00:31:22,400
Lust can be lethal.

156
00:31:23,450 --> 00:31:26,530
I started the edf right
after I was diagnosed.

157
00:31:28,280 --> 00:31:29,940
How did you know?

158
00:31:30,230 --> 00:31:32,290
My father,when I was in high school

159
00:31:33,350 --> 00:31:35,000
everyone knew he had affairs

160
00:31:35,100 --> 00:31:36,730
even my mother--
but nobody talked about it,

161
00:31:36,810 --> 00:31:38,860
so i decided to confront him.

162
00:31:39,610 --> 00:31:41,110
And I followed him-- 

163
00:31:42,030 --> 00:31:43,870
the lawyer's,the doctor'S  

164
00:31:44,780 --> 00:31:46,790
the banks, the weight-loss,

165
00:31:47,310 --> 00:31:49,060
and it all came back.

166
00:31:49,760 --> 00:31:51,390
He had lung cancer.

167
00:31:55,910 --> 00:31:58,200
Well,you know what benzene is?

168
00:31:58,370 --> 00:32:00,310
I know it causes cancer.

169
00:32:01,760 --> 00:32:03,120
Leukemia.

170
00:32:04,360 --> 00:32:06,420
It's also highly flammable.

171
00:32:07,540 --> 00:32:09,420
They kept it in underground tanks.

172
00:32:09,530 --> 00:32:11,630
It's expensive to clean up--

173
00:32:11,730 --> 00:32:12,850
 cheaper to hide.

174
00:32:13,730 --> 00:32:15,190
My specialty.

175
00:32:16,530 --> 00:32:19,840
Most of the properties were zoned "cr",

176
00:32:19,970 --> 00:32:23,250
commercial--
warehouses where nobody worked,

177
00:32:23,340 --> 00:32:24,710
so what's the harm,right?

178
00:32:26,540 --> 00:32:33,870
I just found out that one of those jobs
was sold and rezoned "es".

179
00:32:34,950 --> 00:32:36,670
Elementary school.

180
00:32:37,410 --> 00:32:38,970
And you didn't report it?

181
00:32:39,460 --> 00:32:40,860
I report it,

182
00:32:40,990 --> 00:32:42,530
they come after me  

183
00:32:42,960 --> 00:32:44,740
and I leave nothing for my son.

184
00:32:44,850 --> 00:32:46,330
That's why I started the edf,

185
00:32:46,450 --> 00:32:47,940
the L.U.S.T. List.

186
00:32:49,290 --> 00:32:51,090
I was trying to do the right thing.

187
00:32:51,410 --> 00:32:52,730
You still can.

188
00:32:53,080 --> 00:32:55,020
I don't know who he is.

189
00:32:55,100 --> 00:32:57,790
He was at your house last night  

190
00:32:57,890 --> 00:32:59,240
and he was angry.

191
00:32:59,320 --> 00:33:01,160
Everybody was angry last night,

192
00:33:01,230 --> 00:33:03,690
they were furious
that I shut it all down.

193
00:33:03,790 --> 00:33:06,090
He was angry for a different reason.

194
00:33:06,310 --> 00:33:07,930
What you said enraged him.

195
00:33:08,060 --> 00:33:10,240
But he's a coward,
he wouldn't confront you.

196
00:33:10,360 --> 00:33:12,690
He was probably the only one
who wasn't angry at the time.

197
00:33:12,800 --> 00:33:14,970
He didn't express anything  

198
00:33:15,050 --> 00:33:16,820
until after he left.

199
00:33:24,820 --> 00:33:26,140
Vincent stiles.

200
00:33:31,430 --> 00:33:32,410
Thank you.

201
00:33:37,960 --> 00:33:39,520
Vincent stiles.

202
00:33:39,890 --> 00:33:41,160
Abby's leaving, keep a trail on him

203
00:33:41,190 --> 00:33:43,150
until we have stiles just to be sure.

204
00:33:43,240 --> 00:33:44,820
Copy that.I have abby.

205
00:34:24,480 --> 00:34:25,300
Clear.

206
00:34:25,400 --> 00:34:26,400
Gideon,he's not here.

207
00:34:32,500 --> 00:34:35,120
He got the company names
from the edf website,

208
00:34:35,220 --> 00:34:38,640
then he watched the offices until
he found employees that suited his taste.

209
00:34:39,070 --> 00:34:40,320
He just left.

210
00:34:40,430 --> 00:34:41,460
A neighbor saw him leave.

211
00:34:41,560 --> 00:34:43,140
He's a pharmaceutical sales rep,

212
00:34:43,220 --> 00:34:45,100
he's been living here
since his divorce 6 weeks ago.

213
00:34:45,160 --> 00:34:46,310
That's the stressor.

214
00:34:46,880 --> 00:34:48,090
Yeah,talk to me.

215
00:34:48,860 --> 00:34:50,220
Yeah,I'll let him know.

216
00:34:50,280 --> 00:34:51,210
What?

217
00:34:51,550 --> 00:34:53,430
Abby shook the tail we had on him.

218
00:35:10,570 --> 00:35:12,550
Bet you were afraid I wasn't coming,huh?

219
00:35:12,920 --> 00:35:14,000
Look.

220
00:35:14,510 --> 00:35:16,310
Those things that I said about you  

221
00:35:17,190 --> 00:35:18,240
I'm sorry.

222
00:35:18,790 --> 00:35:20,160
I had to say them.

223
00:35:22,430 --> 00:35:25,530
I know  you're an artist.

224
00:35:25,610 --> 00:35:26,920
A genius.

225
00:35:27,310 --> 00:35:29,510
I appreciate your true value.

226
00:35:30,900 --> 00:35:33,080
So what,
you just came here to apologize?

227
00:35:33,160 --> 00:35:37,120
No  I came here
because I respect your talent.

228
00:35:38,240 --> 00:35:40,130
And I want to take full advantage of it.

229
00:35:50,760 --> 00:35:52,140
Garcia checked abby's phone records,

230
00:35:52,220 --> 00:35:55,370
and he called stiles right
after I left him.

231
00:35:55,430 --> 00:35:57,820
Well,you saw someone abby identified with.

232
00:36:01,290 --> 00:36:03,510
I can't killers, I save lives, I'm a hero,

233
00:36:03,570 --> 00:36:05,140
until my key hits my front door,

234
00:36:05,210 --> 00:36:08,030
and then i'm just the father
and the husband who's never there.

235
00:36:08,120 --> 00:36:09,450
I got that one.

236
00:36:09,890 --> 00:36:11,030
Here's the thing.

237
00:36:11,160 --> 00:36:11,680
When I'm home,

238
00:36:11,800 --> 00:36:14,980
I'm in this silent panic 

239
00:36:15,040 --> 00:36:19,150
because I know that I have to be
as good as I can as fast as I can,

240
00:36:19,210 --> 00:36:21,570
because any minute the phone
is gonna ring and my time is up,

241
00:36:21,630 --> 00:36:24,200
and that panic is exactly
what I saw in abby.

242
00:36:24,280 --> 00:36:25,200
Good. You're abby.

243
00:36:25,260 --> 00:36:26,880
You're a dead man walking, 
you gotta make this right.

244
00:36:26,910 --> 00:36:28,760
You have no time left, how do you do it?

245
00:36:28,830 --> 00:36:30,690
Come on,don't think about it,
you know the answer.What is it?

246
00:36:30,760 --> 00:36:31,770
I'd stop him.

247
00:36:31,840 --> 00:36:32,800
How?

248
00:36:32,880 --> 00:36:34,190
I'd burn him.

249
00:36:35,540 --> 00:36:37,320
The same way he killed them.

250
00:36:37,540 --> 00:36:39,870
I'd do it where nobody could get hurt.

251
00:36:41,620 --> 00:36:44,210
Which is why I would call it in first.

252
00:36:46,490 --> 00:36:49,250
We got a 9-1-1 anonymous tip
for a fire in the harbor district.

253
00:36:49,300 --> 00:36:49,990
Is it a warehouse?

254
00:36:50,050 --> 00:36:51,880
Yeah.6000 san alameda.

255
00:36:51,960 --> 00:36:53,000
- Can you call garcia?
- She's right here.

256
00:36:53,040 --> 00:36:57,060
Hey,garcia, can you check the zoning code
on a warehouse at 6000 san alameda?

257
00:36:57,120 --> 00:36:58,510
Yeah,I certainly can.

258
00:36:58,570 --> 00:37:00,530
The sfpd chopper circled the harbor twice.

259
00:37:00,590 --> 00:37:01,830
There's no sign of fire.

260
00:37:01,880 --> 00:37:05,500
Ok,6000 san alameda
is a commercial storage facility.

261
00:37:05,560 --> 00:37:07,210
But it looks like the property was just sold 

262
00:37:07,290 --> 00:37:10,070
and the lot was approved
for zone conversion.

263
00:37:10,130 --> 00:37:11,040
"Cr" to "es".

264
00:37:11,100 --> 00:37:11,890
Yeah,that's right.

265
00:37:11,960 --> 00:37:13,640
"Cr",commercial,what's "es"?

266
00:37:13,710 --> 00:37:16,020
Elementary school,and there's
a leaking benzene tank underneath it.

267
00:37:16,090 --> 00:37:17,270
It's not a false alarm.

268
00:37:17,310 --> 00:37:18,590
But there's no fire there.

269
00:37:18,660 --> 00:37:19,880
There's about to be.

270
00:37:32,750 --> 00:37:34,100
I started without you.

271
00:37:37,610 --> 00:37:39,640
This is how you do it, right?

272
00:37:40,530 --> 00:37:42,190
Well,fire's a fire.

273
00:37:42,600 --> 00:37:44,480
Once it gets going,
it don't matter.

274
00:37:47,850 --> 00:37:49,000
That's not--

275
00:37:49,060 --> 00:37:50,470
 that's not really true,though,is it?

276
00:37:52,670 --> 00:37:54,460
I don't know what you're talking about.

277
00:37:54,540 --> 00:37:58,480
There's something missing from this scenario,
don't you think?

278
00:37:59,660 --> 00:38:01,350
I'm sorry, you lost me.

279
00:38:02,120 --> 00:38:03,730
The innocent family.

280
00:38:04,420 --> 00:38:05,740
You know, the victims.

281
00:38:06,040 --> 00:38:08,070
That's what the suit's for, right?

282
00:38:08,430 --> 00:38:12,420
So you can see the terror
on their faces as they burn?

283
00:38:16,160 --> 00:38:19,530
But of course,then,
you're here to kill me,right?

284
00:38:25,860 --> 00:38:27,120
You're dead right.

285
00:38:31,390 --> 00:38:33,740
We can't put a benzene fire
out with water.

286
00:38:33,840 --> 00:38:35,330
All water does is spread it around,

287
00:38:35,340 --> 00:38:36,720
it burns too hot.

288
00:38:36,760 --> 00:38:38,410
Contaminates the ground table.

289
00:38:38,470 --> 00:38:39,470
So we'll let it burn.

290
00:38:39,480 --> 00:38:40,280
We exhaust the fuel.

291
00:38:40,290 --> 00:38:42,300
All we can do is cordon it off,
stop it from spreading,

292
00:38:42,330 --> 00:38:43,640
and let the benzene burn out.

293
00:38:43,680 --> 00:38:44,580
Do you understand?

294
00:38:44,660 --> 00:38:45,610
Yeah,I got it.

295
00:38:45,680 --> 00:38:47,030
Does hotchner?

296
00:38:49,630 --> 00:38:50,590
Yeah,what's up?

297
00:38:50,660 --> 00:38:52,060
Don't put me on speaker.

298
00:38:52,140 --> 00:38:53,450
Just listen.

299
00:38:53,490 --> 00:38:56,890
Well,you know,
you can go ahead and shoot me,

300
00:38:56,950 --> 00:38:59,400
and then you set this place
off like a bomb.

301
00:39:03,280 --> 00:39:04,530
No?

302
00:39:11,400 --> 00:39:15,610
you know,this suit can handle
over 1,500 degrees.

303
00:39:15,670 --> 00:39:17,480
Benzene burns so fast,

304
00:39:17,520 --> 00:39:19,900
I won't go through half my air
before it goes out.

305
00:39:19,970 --> 00:39:22,040
Oh,you won't even go through that much.

306
00:39:22,470 --> 00:39:25,680
See,benzene burns at twice that.

307
00:39:28,050 --> 00:39:29,510
What are you doing?

308
00:39:31,250 --> 00:39:32,490
The right thing.

309
00:39:32,670 --> 00:39:33,550
Why?

310
00:39:33,620 --> 00:39:35,360
You didn't know any of those people.

311
00:39:36,060 --> 00:39:37,570
Neither did you!

312
00:39:37,890 --> 00:39:39,970
This fire will spread!

313
00:39:40,190 --> 00:39:41,480
Fire department's on its way.

314
00:39:41,570 --> 00:39:44,190
They can't fight a benzene fire.

315
00:39:44,250 --> 00:39:45,380
They'll contain it.

316
00:39:45,920 --> 00:39:47,520
Seriously,what--

317
00:39:47,580 --> 00:39:49,610
how do you plan
on getting out of here?

318
00:39:54,580 --> 00:39:55,700
I don'T.

319
00:40:03,080 --> 00:40:07,600
**********6000 block of san alameda 

320
00:40:14,690 --> 00:40:16,050
Morgan,what are you doing?

321
00:40:17,870 --> 00:40:19,870
Hotch,it's too late, man,
I'm sorry.

322
00:40:23,020 --> 00:40:24,120
Hotch--stop!

323
00:40:24,150 --> 00:40:25,550
Stop,stop!

324
00:40:25,640 --> 00:40:27,660
He's burning to death
and we're just gonna stand here?

325
00:40:27,670 --> 00:40:29,390
Look at it, man! It's over!

326
00:40:40,360 --> 00:40:42,400
He wanted his death
to mean somethinG.

327
00:41:16,040 --> 00:41:17,520
I found this in abby's car.

328
00:41:31,620 --> 00:41:35,390
Gandhi said,
"live as if you were to die tomorrow.

329
00:41:35,460 --> 00:41:38,290
Learn as if you were to live forever."

330
00:41:39,410 --> 00:41:41,600
- Here he is.
- Thanks.

331
00:41:42,520 --> 00:41:43,670
Mom,what's going on?

332
00:41:43,770 --> 00:41:45,020
It's ok,liam.

333
00:41:45,110 --> 00:41:45,930
Liam?

334
00:41:46,310 --> 00:41:47,540
My name's aaron.

335
00:41:48,010 --> 00:41:49,500
I was a friend of your dad'S.

336
00:41:49,580 --> 00:41:51,300
I saw you with him at my practice.

337
00:41:51,460 --> 00:41:52,530
That's right.

338
00:41:53,060 --> 00:41:54,550
You weren't at his funeral.

339
00:41:55,050 --> 00:41:56,110
I couldn't be there.

340
00:41:56,180 --> 00:41:57,680
I had to be with my family.

341
00:41:59,050 --> 00:42:02,930
But I was thinking of him  and you.

342
00:42:07,500 --> 00:42:09,560
Your dad asked me to give you this.

343
00:42:13,590 --> 00:42:15,140
Why you?

344
00:42:15,450 --> 00:42:16,490
I don't know.

345
00:42:16,570 --> 00:42:18,890
Maybe because I was young
when my dad died.

346
00:42:23,210 --> 00:42:27,260
Anyway,you may have some questions
some day,

347
00:42:27,330 --> 00:42:30,900
and,uh  please feel free to call me,

348
00:42:30,940 --> 00:42:33,760
I'll do everything I can to answer them.

349
00:42:39,270 --> 00:42:42,180
<font color="#ffff00">-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents</font>

350
00:42:43,360 --> 00:42:46,970
<font color=#38B0DE>Sync: YTET-cauorr 芝士蛋糕
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-</font>

351
00:42:47,970 --> 00:42:50,970
<font color="#ffff00">Criminal Minds
Season 02 Episode 19</font>




